=== NER Partial Match Error Analysis ===

--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
GOLD MENTIONS:
Mention object: [Mention(entity_type='PER', start='8', end='9', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='8', end='9', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='9', end='10', text='NikoWavy'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='9', end='10', text='NikoWavy'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='16', end='17', text='Terio')]
  - "@" [PER] (8:9)
  - "@" [PER] (8:9)
  - "NikoWavy" [PER] (9:10)
  - "NikoWavy" [PER] (9:10)
  - "Terio" [PER] (16:17)

PREDICTIONS:
  - "@" [PER] (8:9)
  - "NikoWavy" [PER] (9:10)

PARTIAL MATCH METRICS:
Exact Match F1: 0.8000
Left Boundary Match F1: 1.1429
Right Boundary Match F1: 1.1429
Partial Overlap F1: 1.1429
Overlap Percentage F1: 0.5714

DETAILED ANALYSIS:

  Gold: "@" [PER] vs Pred: "@" [PER]
  Overlap: "t" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "@" [PER] vs Pred: "@" [PER]
  Overlap: "t" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "NikoWavy" [PER] vs Pred: "NikoWavy" [PER]
  Overlap: "h" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "NikoWavy" [PER] vs Pred: "NikoWavy" [PER]
  Overlap: "h" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

================================================================================

Sentence 4: RT @ david_myers77 : " Idk I 'm seepin " @ TheNickSavoia
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
GOLD MENTIONS:
Mention object: [Mention(entity_type='PER', start='1', end='2', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='1', end='2', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='2', end='3', text='david_myers77'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='2', end='3', text='david_myers77'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='10', end='11', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='11', end='12', text='TheNickSavoia'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='11', end='12', text='TheNickSavoia')]
  - "@" [PER] (1:2)
  - "@" [PER] (1:2)
  - "david_myers77" [PER] (2:3)
  - "david_myers77" [PER] (2:3)
  - "@" [PER] (10:11)
  - "TheNickSavoia" [PER] (11:12)
  - "TheNickSavoia" [PER] (11:12)

PREDICTIONS:
  - "@" [PER] (1:2)
  - "david_myers77" [PER] (2:3)
  - "TheNickSavoia" [PER] (11:12)

PARTIAL MATCH METRICS:
Exact Match F1: 0.8571
Left Boundary Match F1: 1.2000
Right Boundary Match F1: 1.2000
Partial Overlap F1: 1.2000
Overlap Percentage F1: 0.6000

DETAILED ANALYSIS:

  Gold: "@" [PER] vs Pred: "@" [PER]
  Overlap: "T" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "@" [PER] vs Pred: "@" [PER]
  Overlap: "T" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "david_myers77" [PER] vs Pred: "david_myers77" [PER]
  Overlap: " " (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "david_myers77" [PER] vs Pred: "david_myers77" [PER]
  Overlap: " " (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "TheNickSavoia" [PER] vs Pred: "TheNickSavoia" [PER]
  Overlap: "m" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "TheNickSavoia" [PER] vs Pred: "TheNickSavoia" [PER]
  Overlap: "m" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

================================================================================

--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
GOLD MENTIONS:
Mention object: [Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='0', end='1', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='0', end='1', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='1', end='2', text='Comp_Finance'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='1', end='2', text='Comp_Finance'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='2', end='3', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='2', end='3', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='3', end='4', text='DrBruceBaird'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='3', end='4', text='DrBruceBaird'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='9', end='10', text='Bruce'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='9', end='10', text='Bruce')]
  - "@" [ORG] (0:1)
  - "@" [PER] (0:1)
  - "Comp_Finance" [ORG] (1:2)
  - "Comp_Finance" [PER] (1:2)
  - "@" [PER] (2:3)
  - "@" [PER] (2:3)
  - "DrBruceBaird" [PER] (3:4)
  - "DrBruceBaird" [PER] (3:4)
  - "Bruce" [PER] (9:10)
  - "Bruce" [PER] (9:10)

PREDICTIONS:
  - "@" [PER] (0:1)
  - "Comp_Finance" [PER] (1:2)
  - "@" [PER] (2:3)
  - "DrBruceBaird" [PER] (3:4)
  - "Bruce" [PER] (9:10)

PARTIAL MATCH METRICS:
Exact Match F1: 0.8333
Left Boundary Match F1: 1.0667
Right Boundary Match F1: 1.0667
Partial Overlap F1: 1.0667
Overlap Percentage F1: 0.6667

DETAILED ANALYSIS:

  Gold: "@" [ORG] vs Pred: "@" [PER]
  Overlap: "@" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "@" [PER] vs Pred: "@" [PER]
  Overlap: "@" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "Comp_Finance" [ORG] vs Pred: "Comp_Finance" [PER]
  Overlap: " " (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "Comp_Finance" [PER] vs Pred: "Comp_Finance" [PER]
  Overlap: " " (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "@" [PER] vs Pred: "@" [PER]
  Overlap: "C" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "@" [PER] vs Pred: "@" [PER]
  Overlap: "C" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "DrBruceBaird" [PER] vs Pred: "DrBruceBaird" [PER]
  Overlap: "o" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "DrBruceBaird" [PER] vs Pred: "DrBruceBaird" [PER]
  Overlap: "o" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "Bruce" [PER] vs Pred: "Bruce" [PER]
  Overlap: "n" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "Bruce" [PER] vs Pred: "Bruce" [PER]
  Overlap: "n" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

================================================================================

--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
GOLD MENTIONS:
Mention object: [Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='1', end='2', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='1', end='2', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='2', end='3', text='mychemicaljulia'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='2', end='3', text='mychemicaljulia'), Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='4', end='5', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='4', end='5', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='5', end='6', text='shuutheamazing'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='5', end='6', text='shuutheamazing')]
  - "@" [ORG] (1:2)
  - "@" [PER] (1:2)
  - "mychemicaljulia" [ORG] (2:3)
  - "mychemicaljulia" [PER] (2:3)
  - "@" [ORG] (4:5)
  - "@" [PER] (4:5)
  - "shuutheamazing" [ORG] (5:6)
  - "shuutheamazing" [PER] (5:6)

PREDICTIONS:
  - "@" [PER] (1:2)
  - "mychemicaljulia" [PER] (2:3)
  - "@" [PER] (4:5)
  - "shuutheamazing" [PER] (5:6)

PARTIAL MATCH METRICS:
Exact Match F1: 0.6667
Left Boundary Match F1: 0.6667
Right Boundary Match F1: 0.6667
Partial Overlap F1: 0.6667
Overlap Percentage F1: 0.6667

DETAILED ANALYSIS:

  Gold: "@" [ORG] vs Pred: "@" [PER]
  Overlap: "T" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "@" [PER] vs Pred: "@" [PER]
  Overlap: "T" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "mychemicaljulia" [ORG] vs Pred: "mychemicaljulia" [PER]
  Overlap: " " (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "mychemicaljulia" [PER] vs Pred: "mychemicaljulia" [PER]
  Overlap: " " (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "@" [ORG] vs Pred: "@" [PER]
  Overlap: " " (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "@" [PER] vs Pred: "@" [PER]
  Overlap: " " (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "shuutheamazing" [ORG] vs Pred: "shuutheamazing" [PER]
  Overlap: "m" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "shuutheamazing" [PER] vs Pred: "shuutheamazing" [PER]
  Overlap: "m" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

================================================================================

--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
GOLD MENTIONS:
Mention object: [Mention(entity_type='LOC', start='7', end='8', text='Sayulita'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='7', end='8', text='Sayulita')]
  - "Sayulita" [LOC] (7:8)
  - "Sayulita" [PER] (7:8)

PREDICTIONS:
  - "Sayulita" [PER] (7:8)

PARTIAL MATCH METRICS:
Exact Match F1: 0.6667
Left Boundary Match F1: 0.6667
Right Boundary Match F1: 0.6667
Partial Overlap F1: 0.6667
Overlap Percentage F1: 0.6667

DETAILED ANALYSIS:

  Gold: "Sayulita" [LOC] vs Pred: "Sayulita" [PER]
  Overlap: "w" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "Sayulita" [PER] vs Pred: "Sayulita" [PER]
  Overlap: "w" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

================================================================================

--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
GOLD MENTIONS:
Mention object: [Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='0', end='1', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='0', end='1', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='1', end='2', text='Luke5SOS'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='1', end='2', text='Luke5SOS')]
  - "@" [ORG] (0:1)
  - "@" [PER] (0:1)
  - "Luke5SOS" [ORG] (1:2)
  - "Luke5SOS" [PER] (1:2)

PREDICTIONS:
  - "@" [PER] (0:1)
  - "Luke5SOS" [PER] (1:2)

PARTIAL MATCH METRICS:
Exact Match F1: 0.6667
Left Boundary Match F1: 0.6667
Right Boundary Match F1: 0.6667
Partial Overlap F1: 0.6667
Overlap Percentage F1: 0.6667

DETAILED ANALYSIS:

  Gold: "@" [ORG] vs Pred: "@" [PER]
  Overlap: "@" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "@" [PER] vs Pred: "@" [PER]
  Overlap: "@" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "Luke5SOS" [ORG] vs Pred: "Luke5SOS" [PER]
  Overlap: " " (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "Luke5SOS" [PER] vs Pred: "Luke5SOS" [PER]
  Overlap: " " (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

================================================================================

--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
GOLD MENTIONS:
Mention object: [Mention(entity_type='PER', start='1', end='2', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='1', end='2', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='2', end='3', text='LaLaDessie'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='2', end='3', text='LaLaDessie'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='5', end='6', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='6', end='7', text='SoDamnReaI'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='6', end='7', text='SoDamnReaI'), Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='11', end='12', text='snapchats')]
  - "@" [PER] (1:2)
  - "@" [PER] (1:2)
  - "LaLaDessie" [PER] (2:3)
  - "LaLaDessie" [PER] (2:3)
  - "@" [PER] (5:6)
  - "SoDamnReaI" [PER] (6:7)
  - "SoDamnReaI" [PER] (6:7)
  - "snapchats" [ORG] (11:12)

PREDICTIONS:
  - "@" [PER] (1:2)
  - "LaLaDessie" [PER] (2:3)
  - "SoDamnReaI" [PER] (6:7)

PARTIAL MATCH METRICS:
Exact Match F1: 0.7500
Left Boundary Match F1: 1.0909
Right Boundary Match F1: 1.0909
Partial Overlap F1: 1.0909
Overlap Percentage F1: 0.5455

DETAILED ANALYSIS:

  Gold: "@" [PER] vs Pred: "@" [PER]
  Overlap: "T" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "@" [PER] vs Pred: "@" [PER]
  Overlap: "T" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "LaLaDessie" [PER] vs Pred: "LaLaDessie" [PER]
  Overlap: " " (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "LaLaDessie" [PER] vs Pred: "LaLaDessie" [PER]
  Overlap: " " (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "SoDamnReaI" [PER] vs Pred: "SoDamnReaI" [PER]
  Overlap: "a" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "SoDamnReaI" [PER] vs Pred: "SoDamnReaI" [PER]
  Overlap: "a" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

================================================================================

--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
GOLD MENTIONS:
Mention object: [Mention(entity_type='PER', start='0', end='1', text='Justin'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='0', end='1', text='Justin'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='21', end='22', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='21', end='22', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='22', end='23', text='shafeeva1'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='22', end='23', text='shafeeva1'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='25', end='26', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='26', end='27', text='justinbieber'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='26', end='27', text='justinbieber')]
  - "Justin" [PER] (0:1)
  - "Justin" [PER] (0:1)
  - "@" [PER] (21:22)
  - "@" [PER] (21:22)
  - "shafeeva1" [PER] (22:23)
  - "shafeeva1" [PER] (22:23)
  - "@" [PER] (25:26)
  - "justinbieber" [PER] (26:27)
  - "justinbieber" [PER] (26:27)

PREDICTIONS:
  - "Justin" [PER] (0:1)
  - "@" [PER] (21:22)
  - "shafeeva1" [PER] (22:23)
  - "justinbieber" [PER] (26:27)

PARTIAL MATCH METRICS:
Exact Match F1: 0.8889
Left Boundary Match F1: 1.2308
Right Boundary Match F1: 1.2308
Partial Overlap F1: 1.2308
Overlap Percentage F1: 0.6154

DETAILED ANALYSIS:

  Gold: "Justin" [PER] vs Pred: "Justin" [PER]
  Overlap: "J" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "Justin" [PER] vs Pred: "Justin" [PER]
  Overlap: "J" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "@" [PER] vs Pred: "@" [PER]
  Overlap: "o" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "@" [PER] vs Pred: "@" [PER]
  Overlap: "o" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "shafeeva1" [PER] vs Pred: "shafeeva1" [PER]
  Overlap: "r" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "shafeeva1" [PER] vs Pred: "shafeeva1" [PER]
  Overlap: "r" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "justinbieber" [PER] vs Pred: "justinbieber" [PER]
  Overlap: " " (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "justinbieber" [PER] vs Pred: "justinbieber" [PER]
  Overlap: " " (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

================================================================================

--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
GOLD MENTIONS:
Mention object: [Mention(entity_type='PER', start='0', end='1', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='0', end='1', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='1', end='2', text='Frenzeeeee'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='1', end='2', text='Frenzeeeee'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='2', end='3', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='2', end='3', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='3', end='4', text='RussellCosta3'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='3', end='4', text='RussellCosta3'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='4', end='5', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='4', end='5', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='5', end='6', text='Dave_Sciarra1'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='5', end='6', text='Dave_Sciarra1'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='6', end='7', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='6', end='7', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='7', end='8', text='APesky11'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='7', end='8', text='APesky11'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='9', end='10', text='madden')]
  - "@" [PER] (0:1)
  - "@" [PER] (0:1)
  - "Frenzeeeee" [PER] (1:2)
  - "Frenzeeeee" [PER] (1:2)
  - "@" [PER] (2:3)
  - "@" [PER] (2:3)
  - "RussellCosta3" [PER] (3:4)
  - "RussellCosta3" [PER] (3:4)
  - "@" [PER] (4:5)
  - "@" [PER] (4:5)
  - "Dave_Sciarra1" [PER] (5:6)
  - "Dave_Sciarra1" [PER] (5:6)
  - "@" [PER] (6:7)
  - "@" [PER] (6:7)
  - "APesky11" [PER] (7:8)
  - "APesky11" [PER] (7:8)
  - "madden" [PER] (9:10)

PREDICTIONS:
  - "@" [PER] (0:1)
  - "Frenzeeeee" [PER] (1:2)
  - "@" [PER] (2:3)
  - "RussellCosta3" [PER] (3:4)
  - "@" [PER] (4:5)
  - "Dave_Sciarra1" [PER] (5:6)
  - "@" [PER] (6:7)
  - "APesky11" [PER] (7:8)

PARTIAL MATCH METRICS:
Exact Match F1: 0.9412
Left Boundary Match F1: 1.2800
Right Boundary Match F1: 1.2800
Partial Overlap F1: 1.2800
Overlap Percentage F1: 0.6400

DETAILED ANALYSIS:

  Gold: "@" [PER] vs Pred: "@" [PER]
  Overlap: "@" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "@" [PER] vs Pred: "@" [PER]
  Overlap: "@" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "Frenzeeeee" [PER] vs Pred: "Frenzeeeee" [PER]
  Overlap: " " (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "Frenzeeeee" [PER] vs Pred: "Frenzeeeee" [PER]
  Overlap: " " (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "@" [PER] vs Pred: "@" [PER]
  Overlap: "F" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "@" [PER] vs Pred: "@" [PER]
  Overlap: "F" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "RussellCosta3" [PER] vs Pred: "RussellCosta3" [PER]
  Overlap: "r" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "RussellCosta3" [PER] vs Pred: "RussellCosta3" [PER]
  Overlap: "r" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "@" [PER] vs Pred: "@" [PER]
  Overlap: "e" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "@" [PER] vs Pred: "@" [PER]
  Overlap: "e" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "Dave_Sciarra1" [PER] vs Pred: "Dave_Sciarra1" [PER]
  Overlap: "n" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "Dave_Sciarra1" [PER] vs Pred: "Dave_Sciarra1" [PER]
  Overlap: "n" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "@" [PER] vs Pred: "@" [PER]
  Overlap: "z" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "@" [PER] vs Pred: "@" [PER]
  Overlap: "z" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "APesky11" [PER] vs Pred: "APesky11" [PER]
  Overlap: "e" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "APesky11" [PER] vs Pred: "APesky11" [PER]
  Overlap: "e" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

================================================================================

--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
GOLD MENTIONS:
Mention object: [Mention(entity_type='PER', start='3', end='4', text='Rog'), Mention(entity_type='LOC', start='5', end='6', text='Arena'), Mention(entity_type='LOC', start='5', end='6', text='Arena')]
  - "Rog" [PER] (3:4)
  - "Arena" [LOC] (5:6)
  - "Arena" [LOC] (5:6)

PREDICTIONS:
  - "Arena" [LOC] (5:6)

PARTIAL MATCH METRICS:
Exact Match F1: 0.6667
Left Boundary Match F1: 1.0000
Right Boundary Match F1: 1.0000
Partial Overlap F1: 1.0000
Overlap Percentage F1: 0.5000

DETAILED ANALYSIS:

  Gold: "Arena" [LOC] vs Pred: "Arena" [LOC]
  Overlap: "i" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "Arena" [LOC] vs Pred: "Arena" [LOC]
  Overlap: "i" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

================================================================================

--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
GOLD MENTIONS:
Mention object: [Mention(entity_type='LOC', start='2', end='4', text='New Hampshire'), Mention(entity_type='LOC', start='3', end='4', text='Hampshire')]
  - "New Hampshire" [LOC] (2:4)
  - "Hampshire" [LOC] (3:4)

PREDICTIONS:
  - "Hampshire" [LOC] (3:4)

PARTIAL MATCH METRICS:
Exact Match F1: 0.6667
Left Boundary Match F1: 0.6667
Right Boundary Match F1: 1.3333
Partial Overlap F1: 1.3333
Overlap Percentage F1: 0.6667

DETAILED ANALYSIS:

  Gold: "New Hampshire" [LOC] vs Pred: "Hampshire" [LOC]
  Overlap: "B" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 50.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MISMATCH: Gold=2, Pred=3, Offset=1
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "Hampshire" [LOC] vs Pred: "Hampshire" [LOC]
  Overlap: "B" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

================================================================================

--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
GOLD MENTIONS:
Mention object: [Mention(entity_type='PER', start='7', end='8', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='7', end='8', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='8', end='9', text='StormyTeacup_LK'), Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='8', end='9', text='StormyTeacup_LK')]
  - "@" [PER] (7:8)
  - "@" [ORG] (7:8)
  - "StormyTeacup_LK" [PER] (8:9)
  - "StormyTeacup_LK" [ORG] (8:9)

PREDICTIONS:
  - "@" [ORG] (7:8)
  - "StormyTeacup_LK" [ORG] (8:9)

PARTIAL MATCH METRICS:
Exact Match F1: 0.6667
Left Boundary Match F1: 0.6667
Right Boundary Match F1: 0.6667
Partial Overlap F1: 0.6667
Overlap Percentage F1: 0.6667

DETAILED ANALYSIS:

  Gold: "@" [PER] vs Pred: "@" [ORG]
  Overlap: "h" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "@" [ORG] vs Pred: "@" [ORG]
  Overlap: "h" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "StormyTeacup_LK" [PER] vs Pred: "StormyTeacup_LK" [ORG]
  Overlap: "e" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "StormyTeacup_LK" [ORG] vs Pred: "StormyTeacup_LK" [ORG]
  Overlap: "e" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

================================================================================

--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
GOLD MENTIONS:
Mention object: [Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='6', end='11', text='The Health and Safety Executive'), Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='7', end='11', text='Health and Safety Executive')]
  - "The Health and Safety Executive" [ORG] (6:11)
  - "Health and Safety Executive" [ORG] (7:11)

PREDICTIONS:
  - "Health and Safety Executive" [ORG] (7:11)

PARTIAL MATCH METRICS:
Exact Match F1: 0.6667
Left Boundary Match F1: 0.6667
Right Boundary Match F1: 1.3333
Partial Overlap F1: 1.3333
Overlap Percentage F1: 0.6667

DETAILED ANALYSIS:

  Gold: "The Health and Safety Executive" [ORG] vs Pred: "Health and Safety Executive" [ORG]
  Overlap: "e bl" (4 chars)
  Overlap covers 80.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MISMATCH: Gold=6, Pred=7, Offset=1
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "Health and Safety Executive" [ORG] vs Pred: "Health and Safety Executive" [ORG]
  Overlap: "e bl" (4 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

================================================================================

--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
GOLD MENTIONS:
Mention object: [Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='1', end='2', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='1', end='2', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='2', end='3', text='mandateconf'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='2', end='3', text='mandateconf')]
  - "@" [ORG] (1:2)
  - "@" [PER] (1:2)
  - "mandateconf" [ORG] (2:3)
  - "mandateconf" [PER] (2:3)

PREDICTIONS:
  - "@" [PER] (1:2)
  - "mandateconf" [PER] (2:3)

PARTIAL MATCH METRICS:
Exact Match F1: 0.6667
Left Boundary Match F1: 0.6667
Right Boundary Match F1: 0.6667
Partial Overlap F1: 0.6667
Overlap Percentage F1: 0.6667

DETAILED ANALYSIS:

  Gold: "@" [ORG] vs Pred: "@" [PER]
  Overlap: "T" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "@" [PER] vs Pred: "@" [PER]
  Overlap: "T" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "mandateconf" [ORG] vs Pred: "mandateconf" [PER]
  Overlap: " " (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "mandateconf" [PER] vs Pred: "mandateconf" [PER]
  Overlap: " " (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

================================================================================

--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
GOLD MENTIONS:
Mention object: [Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='3', end='6', text='Clash of Clans'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='8', end='9', text='Jorge'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='8', end='9', text='Jorge'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='13', end='14', text='#MiGuleSalero')]
  - "Clash of Clans" [ORG] (3:6)
  - "Jorge" [PER] (8:9)
  - "Jorge" [PER] (8:9)
  - "#MiGuleSalero" [PER] (13:14)

PREDICTIONS:
  - "Jorge" [PER] (8:9)

PARTIAL MATCH METRICS:
Exact Match F1: 0.5000
Left Boundary Match F1: 0.8000
Right Boundary Match F1: 0.8000
Partial Overlap F1: 0.8000
Overlap Percentage F1: 0.4000

DETAILED ANALYSIS:

  Gold: "Jorge" [PER] vs Pred: "Jorge" [PER]
  Overlap: "4" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "Jorge" [PER] vs Pred: "Jorge" [PER]
  Overlap: "4" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

================================================================================

--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
GOLD MENTIONS:
Mention object: [Mention(entity_type='PER', start='0', end='1', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='0', end='1', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='1', end='2', text='theresaaang_'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='1', end='2', text='theresaaang_'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='2', end='3', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='2', end='3', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='3', end='4', text='DanicasandreasD'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='3', end='4', text='DanicasandreasD'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='4', end='5', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='4', end='5', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='5', end='6', text='Aileenrms'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='5', end='6', text='Aileenrms'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='9', end='10', text='aminado')]
  - "@" [PER] (0:1)
  - "@" [PER] (0:1)
  - "theresaaang_" [PER] (1:2)
  - "theresaaang_" [PER] (1:2)
  - "@" [PER] (2:3)
  - "@" [PER] (2:3)
  - "DanicasandreasD" [PER] (3:4)
  - "DanicasandreasD" [PER] (3:4)
  - "@" [PER] (4:5)
  - "@" [PER] (4:5)
  - "Aileenrms" [PER] (5:6)
  - "Aileenrms" [PER] (5:6)
  - "aminado" [PER] (9:10)

PREDICTIONS:
  - "@" [PER] (0:1)
  - "theresaaang_" [PER] (1:2)
  - "@" [PER] (2:3)
  - "DanicasandreasD" [PER] (3:4)
  - "@" [PER] (4:5)
  - "Aileenrms" [PER] (5:6)

PARTIAL MATCH METRICS:
Exact Match F1: 0.9231
Left Boundary Match F1: 1.2632
Right Boundary Match F1: 1.2632
Partial Overlap F1: 1.2632
Overlap Percentage F1: 0.6316

DETAILED ANALYSIS:

  Gold: "@" [PER] vs Pred: "@" [PER]
  Overlap: "@" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "@" [PER] vs Pred: "@" [PER]
  Overlap: "@" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "theresaaang_" [PER] vs Pred: "theresaaang_" [PER]
  Overlap: " " (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "theresaaang_" [PER] vs Pred: "theresaaang_" [PER]
  Overlap: " " (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "@" [PER] vs Pred: "@" [PER]
  Overlap: "t" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "@" [PER] vs Pred: "@" [PER]
  Overlap: "t" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "DanicasandreasD" [PER] vs Pred: "DanicasandreasD" [PER]
  Overlap: "h" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "DanicasandreasD" [PER] vs Pred: "DanicasandreasD" [PER]
  Overlap: "h" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "@" [PER] vs Pred: "@" [PER]
  Overlap: "e" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "@" [PER] vs Pred: "@" [PER]
  Overlap: "e" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "Aileenrms" [PER] vs Pred: "Aileenrms" [PER]
  Overlap: "r" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "Aileenrms" [PER] vs Pred: "Aileenrms" [PER]
  Overlap: "r" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

================================================================================

--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
GOLD MENTIONS:
Mention object: [Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='0', end='1', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='0', end='1', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='1', end='2', text='TheManicMedium'), Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='1', end='2', text='TheManicMedium'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='6', end='7', text='Kent'), Mention(entity_type='LOC', start='6', end='7', text='Kent')]
  - "@" [ORG] (0:1)
  - "@" [ORG] (0:1)
  - "TheManicMedium" [ORG] (1:2)
  - "TheManicMedium" [ORG] (1:2)
  - "Kent" [PER] (6:7)
  - "Kent" [LOC] (6:7)

PREDICTIONS:
  - "@" [ORG] (0:1)
  - "TheManicMedium" [ORG] (1:2)
  - "Kent" [LOC] (6:7)

PARTIAL MATCH METRICS:
Exact Match F1: 0.8571
Left Boundary Match F1: 1.1111
Right Boundary Match F1: 1.1111
Partial Overlap F1: 1.1111
Overlap Percentage F1: 0.6667

DETAILED ANALYSIS:

  Gold: "@" [ORG] vs Pred: "@" [ORG]
  Overlap: "@" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "@" [ORG] vs Pred: "@" [ORG]
  Overlap: "@" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "TheManicMedium" [ORG] vs Pred: "TheManicMedium" [ORG]
  Overlap: " " (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "TheManicMedium" [ORG] vs Pred: "TheManicMedium" [ORG]
  Overlap: " " (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "Kent" [PER] vs Pred: "Kent" [LOC]
  Overlap: "a" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "Kent" [LOC] vs Pred: "Kent" [LOC]
  Overlap: "a" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

================================================================================

--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
GOLD MENTIONS:
Mention object: [Mention(entity_type='LOC', start='3', end='7', text='Universidade Federal do Tocantins'), Mention(entity_type='LOC', start='3', end='5', text='Universidade Federal'), Mention(entity_type='LOC', start='6', end='7', text='Tocantins'), Mention(entity_type='LOC', start='8', end='9', text='UFT'), Mention(entity_type='LOC', start='13', end='16', text='Palmas , TO')]
  - "Universidade Federal do Tocantins" [LOC] (3:7)
  - "Universidade Federal" [LOC] (3:5)
  - "Tocantins" [LOC] (6:7)
  - "UFT" [LOC] (8:9)
  - "Palmas , TO" [LOC] (13:16)

PREDICTIONS:
  - "Universidade Federal" [LOC] (3:5)
  - "Tocantins" [LOC] (6:7)

PARTIAL MATCH METRICS:
Exact Match F1: 0.5714
Left Boundary Match F1: 0.8571
Right Boundary Match F1: 0.8571
Partial Overlap F1: 0.8571
Overlap Percentage F1: 0.5714

DETAILED ANALYSIS:

  Gold: "Universidade Federal do Tocantins" [LOC] vs Pred: "Universidade Federal" [LOC]
  Overlap: "m " (2 chars)
  Overlap covers 50.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MISMATCH: Gold=7, Pred=5, Offset=-2

  Gold: "Universidade Federal do Tocantins" [LOC] vs Pred: "Tocantins" [LOC]
  Overlap: "t" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 25.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MISMATCH: Gold=3, Pred=6, Offset=3
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "Universidade Federal" [LOC] vs Pred: "Universidade Federal" [LOC]
  Overlap: "m " (2 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "Tocantins" [LOC] vs Pred: "Tocantins" [LOC]
  Overlap: "t" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

================================================================================

--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
GOLD MENTIONS:
Mention object: [Mention(entity_type='PER', start='0', end='1', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='0', end='1', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='1', end='2', text='StephenGrootes'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='1', end='2', text='StephenGrootes'), Mention(entity_type='LOC', start='12', end='15', text='bryneven primary school')]
  - "@" [PER] (0:1)
  - "@" [PER] (0:1)
  - "StephenGrootes" [PER] (1:2)
  - "StephenGrootes" [PER] (1:2)
  - "bryneven primary school" [LOC] (12:15)

PREDICTIONS:
  - "@" [PER] (0:1)
  - "StephenGrootes" [PER] (1:2)

PARTIAL MATCH METRICS:
Exact Match F1: 0.8000
Left Boundary Match F1: 1.1429
Right Boundary Match F1: 1.1429
Partial Overlap F1: 1.1429
Overlap Percentage F1: 0.5714

DETAILED ANALYSIS:

  Gold: "@" [PER] vs Pred: "@" [PER]
  Overlap: "@" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "@" [PER] vs Pred: "@" [PER]
  Overlap: "@" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "StephenGrootes" [PER] vs Pred: "StephenGrootes" [PER]
  Overlap: " " (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "StephenGrootes" [PER] vs Pred: "StephenGrootes" [PER]
  Overlap: " " (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

================================================================================

--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
GOLD MENTIONS:
Mention object: [Mention(entity_type='PER', start='1', end='2', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='1', end='2', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='2', end='3', text='HorrorPlaces'), Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='2', end='3', text='HorrorPlaces'), Mention(entity_type='LOC', start='4', end='7', text='Family Doctors Clinic'), Mention(entity_type='LOC', start='8', end='9', text='Germany'), Mention(entity_type='LOC', start='8', end='9', text='Germany')]
  - "@" [PER] (1:2)
  - "@" [ORG] (1:2)
  - "HorrorPlaces" [PER] (2:3)
  - "HorrorPlaces" [ORG] (2:3)
  - "Family Doctors Clinic" [LOC] (4:7)
  - "Germany" [LOC] (8:9)
  - "Germany" [LOC] (8:9)

PREDICTIONS:
  - "@" [ORG] (1:2)
  - "HorrorPlaces" [ORG] (2:3)
  - "Germany" [LOC] (8:9)

PARTIAL MATCH METRICS:
Exact Match F1: 0.6667
Left Boundary Match F1: 0.8000
Right Boundary Match F1: 0.8000
Partial Overlap F1: 0.8000
Overlap Percentage F1: 0.6000

DETAILED ANALYSIS:

  Gold: "@" [PER] vs Pred: "@" [ORG]
  Overlap: "T" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "@" [ORG] vs Pred: "@" [ORG]
  Overlap: "T" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "HorrorPlaces" [PER] vs Pred: "HorrorPlaces" [ORG]
  Overlap: " " (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "HorrorPlaces" [ORG] vs Pred: "HorrorPlaces" [ORG]
  Overlap: " " (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "Germany" [LOC] vs Pred: "Germany" [LOC]
  Overlap: "r" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "Germany" [LOC] vs Pred: "Germany" [LOC]
  Overlap: "r" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

================================================================================

Sentence 75: @ Comoaloy kapan ?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
GOLD MENTIONS:
Mention object: [Mention(entity_type='PER', start='0', end='1', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='0', end='1', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='1', end='2', text='Comoaloy'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='1', end='2', text='Comoaloy'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='2', end='3', text='kapan')]
  - "@" [PER] (0:1)
  - "@" [PER] (0:1)
  - "Comoaloy" [PER] (1:2)
  - "Comoaloy" [PER] (1:2)
  - "kapan" [PER] (2:3)

PREDICTIONS:
  - "@" [PER] (0:1)
  - "Comoaloy" [PER] (1:2)

PARTIAL MATCH METRICS:
Exact Match F1: 0.8000
Left Boundary Match F1: 1.1429
Right Boundary Match F1: 1.1429
Partial Overlap F1: 1.1429
Overlap Percentage F1: 0.5714

DETAILED ANALYSIS:

  Gold: "@" [PER] vs Pred: "@" [PER]
  Overlap: "@" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "@" [PER] vs Pred: "@" [PER]
  Overlap: "@" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "Comoaloy" [PER] vs Pred: "Comoaloy" [PER]
  Overlap: " " (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "Comoaloy" [PER] vs Pred: "Comoaloy" [PER]
  Overlap: " " (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

================================================================================

--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
GOLD MENTIONS:
Mention object: [Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='0', end='1', text='APPLE'), Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='0', end='1', text='APPLE'), Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='13', end='15', text='VERIZON WIRELESS'), Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='13', end='14', text='VERIZON')]
  - "APPLE" [ORG] (0:1)
  - "APPLE" [ORG] (0:1)
  - "VERIZON WIRELESS" [ORG] (13:15)
  - "VERIZON" [ORG] (13:14)

PREDICTIONS:
  - "APPLE" [ORG] (0:1)
  - "VERIZON" [ORG] (13:14)

PARTIAL MATCH METRICS:
Exact Match F1: 0.8000
Left Boundary Match F1: 1.3333
Right Boundary Match F1: 1.0000
Partial Overlap F1: 1.3333
Overlap Percentage F1: 0.6667

DETAILED ANALYSIS:

  Gold: "APPLE" [ORG] vs Pred: "APPLE" [ORG]
  Overlap: "A" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "APPLE" [ORG] vs Pred: "APPLE" [ORG]
  Overlap: "A" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "VERIZON WIRELESS" [ORG] vs Pred: "VERIZON" [ORG]
  Overlap: "4" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 50.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MISMATCH: Gold=15, Pred=14, Offset=-1

  Gold: "VERIZON" [ORG] vs Pred: "VERIZON" [ORG]
  Overlap: "4" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

================================================================================

--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
GOLD MENTIONS:
Mention object: [Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='8', end='9', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='8', end='9', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='9', end='10', text='thefworduk'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='9', end='10', text='thefworduk')]
  - "@" [ORG] (8:9)
  - "@" [PER] (8:9)
  - "thefworduk" [ORG] (9:10)
  - "thefworduk" [PER] (9:10)

PREDICTIONS:
  - "@" [PER] (8:9)
  - "thefworduk" [PER] (9:10)

PARTIAL MATCH METRICS:
Exact Match F1: 0.6667
Left Boundary Match F1: 0.6667
Right Boundary Match F1: 0.6667
Partial Overlap F1: 0.6667
Overlap Percentage F1: 0.6667

DETAILED ANALYSIS:

  Gold: "@" [ORG] vs Pred: "@" [PER]
  Overlap: "c" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "@" [PER] vs Pred: "@" [PER]
  Overlap: "c" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "thefworduk" [ORG] vs Pred: "thefworduk" [PER]
  Overlap: "e" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "thefworduk" [PER] vs Pred: "thefworduk" [PER]
  Overlap: "e" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

================================================================================

--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
GOLD MENTIONS:
Mention object: [Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='7', end='8', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='7', end='8', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='8', end='9', text='WestEndHouseBGC'), Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='8', end='9', text='WestEndHouseBGC'), Mention(entity_type='LOC', start='19', end='20', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='19', end='20', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='LOC', start='20', end='21', text='WorkbridgeMA'), Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='20', end='21', text='WorkbridgeMA')]
  - "@" [ORG] (7:8)
  - "@" [ORG] (7:8)
  - "WestEndHouseBGC" [ORG] (8:9)
  - "WestEndHouseBGC" [ORG] (8:9)
  - "@" [LOC] (19:20)
  - "@" [ORG] (19:20)
  - "WorkbridgeMA" [LOC] (20:21)
  - "WorkbridgeMA" [ORG] (20:21)

PREDICTIONS:
  - "@" [ORG] (7:8)
  - "WestEndHouseBGC" [ORG] (8:9)
  - "@" [ORG] (19:20)
  - "WorkbridgeMA" [ORG] (20:21)

PARTIAL MATCH METRICS:
Exact Match F1: 0.8000
Left Boundary Match F1: 1.0000
Right Boundary Match F1: 1.0000
Partial Overlap F1: 1.0000
Overlap Percentage F1: 0.6667

DETAILED ANALYSIS:

  Gold: "@" [ORG] vs Pred: "@" [ORG]
  Overlap: "s" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "@" [ORG] vs Pred: "@" [ORG]
  Overlap: "s" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "WestEndHouseBGC" [ORG] vs Pred: "WestEndHouseBGC" [ORG]
  Overlap: "u" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "WestEndHouseBGC" [ORG] vs Pred: "WestEndHouseBGC" [ORG]
  Overlap: "u" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "@" [LOC] vs Pred: "@" [ORG]
  Overlap: " " (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "@" [ORG] vs Pred: "@" [ORG]
  Overlap: " " (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "WorkbridgeMA" [LOC] vs Pred: "WorkbridgeMA" [ORG]
  Overlap: "t" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "WorkbridgeMA" [ORG] vs Pred: "WorkbridgeMA" [ORG]
  Overlap: "t" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

================================================================================

--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
GOLD MENTIONS:
Mention object: [Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='6', end='7', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='7', end='8', text='dat_VALCO_gee'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='7', end='8', text='dat_VALCO_gee')]
  - "@" [ORG] (6:7)
  - "dat_VALCO_gee" [ORG] (7:8)
  - "dat_VALCO_gee" [PER] (7:8)

PREDICTIONS:
  - "dat_VALCO_gee" [PER] (7:8)

PARTIAL MATCH METRICS:
Exact Match F1: 0.5000
Left Boundary Match F1: 0.5000
Right Boundary Match F1: 0.5000
Partial Overlap F1: 0.5000
Overlap Percentage F1: 0.5000

DETAILED ANALYSIS:

  Gold: "dat_VALCO_gee" [ORG] vs Pred: "dat_VALCO_gee" [PER]
  Overlap: "e" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "dat_VALCO_gee" [PER] vs Pred: "dat_VALCO_gee" [PER]
  Overlap: "e" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

================================================================================

--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
GOLD MENTIONS:
Mention object: [Mention(entity_type='PER', start='1', end='2', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='1', end='2', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='2', end='3', text='bibimBANG_TH'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='2', end='3', text='bibimBANG_TH'), Mention(entity_type='LOC', start='10', end='12', text='Earth LA')]
  - "@" [PER] (1:2)
  - "@" [PER] (1:2)
  - "bibimBANG_TH" [PER] (2:3)
  - "bibimBANG_TH" [PER] (2:3)
  - "Earth LA" [LOC] (10:12)

PREDICTIONS:
  - "@" [PER] (1:2)
  - "bibimBANG_TH" [PER] (2:3)

PARTIAL MATCH METRICS:
Exact Match F1: 0.8000
Left Boundary Match F1: 1.1429
Right Boundary Match F1: 1.1429
Partial Overlap F1: 1.1429
Overlap Percentage F1: 0.5714

DETAILED ANALYSIS:

  Gold: "@" [PER] vs Pred: "@" [PER]
  Overlap: "T" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "@" [PER] vs Pred: "@" [PER]
  Overlap: "T" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "bibimBANG_TH" [PER] vs Pred: "bibimBANG_TH" [PER]
  Overlap: " " (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "bibimBANG_TH" [PER] vs Pred: "bibimBANG_TH" [PER]
  Overlap: " " (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

================================================================================

--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
GOLD MENTIONS:
Mention object: [Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='3', end='5', text='Philips AVENT'), Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='3', end='4', text='Philips'), Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='11', end='13', text='Philips AVENT')]
  - "Philips AVENT" [ORG] (3:5)
  - "Philips" [ORG] (3:4)
  - "Philips AVENT" [ORG] (11:13)

PREDICTIONS:
  - "Philips" [ORG] (3:4)

PARTIAL MATCH METRICS:
Exact Match F1: 0.5000
Left Boundary Match F1: 1.0000
Right Boundary Match F1: 0.5000
Partial Overlap F1: 1.0000
Overlap Percentage F1: 0.5000

DETAILED ANALYSIS:

  Gold: "Philips AVENT" [ORG] vs Pred: "Philips" [ORG]
  Overlap: " " (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 50.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MISMATCH: Gold=5, Pred=4, Offset=-1

  Gold: "Philips" [ORG] vs Pred: "Philips" [ORG]
  Overlap: " " (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

================================================================================

--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
GOLD MENTIONS:
Mention object: [Mention(entity_type='PER', start='1', end='2', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='1', end='2', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='2', end='3', text='astronomicniall'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='2', end='3', text='astronomicniall'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='23', end='24', text='nialls')]
  - "@" [PER] (1:2)
  - "@" [PER] (1:2)
  - "astronomicniall" [PER] (2:3)
  - "astronomicniall" [PER] (2:3)
  - "nialls" [PER] (23:24)

PREDICTIONS:
  - "@" [PER] (1:2)
  - "astronomicniall" [PER] (2:3)

PARTIAL MATCH METRICS:
Exact Match F1: 0.8000
Left Boundary Match F1: 1.1429
Right Boundary Match F1: 1.1429
Partial Overlap F1: 1.1429
Overlap Percentage F1: 0.5714

DETAILED ANALYSIS:

  Gold: "@" [PER] vs Pred: "@" [PER]
  Overlap: "T" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "@" [PER] vs Pred: "@" [PER]
  Overlap: "T" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "astronomicniall" [PER] vs Pred: "astronomicniall" [PER]
  Overlap: " " (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "astronomicniall" [PER] vs Pred: "astronomicniall" [PER]
  Overlap: " " (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

================================================================================

--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
GOLD MENTIONS:
Mention object: [Mention(entity_type='LOC', start='1', end='2', text='World'), Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='16', end='17', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='16', end='17', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='17', end='18', text='BloombergNews'), Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='17', end='18', text='BloombergNews')]
  - "World" [LOC] (1:2)
  - "@" [ORG] (16:17)
  - "@" [ORG] (16:17)
  - "BloombergNews" [ORG] (17:18)
  - "BloombergNews" [ORG] (17:18)

PREDICTIONS:
  - "@" [ORG] (16:17)
  - "BloombergNews" [ORG] (17:18)

PARTIAL MATCH METRICS:
Exact Match F1: 0.8000
Left Boundary Match F1: 1.1429
Right Boundary Match F1: 1.1429
Partial Overlap F1: 1.1429
Overlap Percentage F1: 0.5714

DETAILED ANALYSIS:

  Gold: "@" [ORG] vs Pred: "@" [ORG]
  Overlap: "S" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "@" [ORG] vs Pred: "@" [ORG]
  Overlap: "S" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "BloombergNews" [ORG] vs Pred: "BloombergNews" [ORG]
  Overlap: "e" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "BloombergNews" [ORG] vs Pred: "BloombergNews" [ORG]
  Overlap: "e" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

================================================================================

--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
GOLD MENTIONS:
Mention object: [Mention(entity_type='PER', start='1', end='2', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='1', end='2', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='2', end='3', text='DaniellaRosita'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='2', end='3', text='DaniellaRosita'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='3', end='4', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='3', end='4', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='4', end='5', text='albertkurniawa1'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='4', end='5', text='albertkurniawa1'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='6', end='7', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='7', end='8', text='silvanaapl'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='7', end='8', text='silvanaapl')]
  - "@" [PER] (1:2)
  - "@" [PER] (1:2)
  - "DaniellaRosita" [PER] (2:3)
  - "DaniellaRosita" [PER] (2:3)
  - "@" [PER] (3:4)
  - "@" [PER] (3:4)
  - "albertkurniawa1" [PER] (4:5)
  - "albertkurniawa1" [PER] (4:5)
  - "@" [PER] (6:7)
  - "silvanaapl" [PER] (7:8)
  - "silvanaapl" [PER] (7:8)

PREDICTIONS:
  - "@" [PER] (1:2)
  - "DaniellaRosita" [PER] (2:3)
  - "@" [PER] (3:4)
  - "albertkurniawa1" [PER] (4:5)
  - "silvanaapl" [PER] (7:8)

PARTIAL MATCH METRICS:
Exact Match F1: 0.9091
Left Boundary Match F1: 1.2500
Right Boundary Match F1: 1.2500
Partial Overlap F1: 1.2500
Overlap Percentage F1: 0.6250

DETAILED ANALYSIS:

  Gold: "@" [PER] vs Pred: "@" [PER]
  Overlap: "l" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "@" [PER] vs Pred: "@" [PER]
  Overlap: "l" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "DaniellaRosita" [PER] vs Pred: "DaniellaRosita" [PER]
  Overlap: "i" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "DaniellaRosita" [PER] vs Pred: "DaniellaRosita" [PER]
  Overlap: "i" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "@" [PER] vs Pred: "@" [PER]
  Overlap: "v" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "@" [PER] vs Pred: "@" [PER]
  Overlap: "v" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "albertkurniawa1" [PER] vs Pred: "albertkurniawa1" [PER]
  Overlap: "i" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "albertkurniawa1" [PER] vs Pred: "albertkurniawa1" [PER]
  Overlap: "i" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "silvanaapl" [PER] vs Pred: "silvanaapl" [PER]
  Overlap: "o" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "silvanaapl" [PER] vs Pred: "silvanaapl" [PER]
  Overlap: "o" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

================================================================================

--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
GOLD MENTIONS:
Mention object: [Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='1', end='2', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='1', end='2', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='2', end='3', text='lesleysfarm'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='2', end='3', text='lesleysfarm')]
  - "@" [ORG] (1:2)
  - "@" [PER] (1:2)
  - "lesleysfarm" [ORG] (2:3)
  - "lesleysfarm" [PER] (2:3)

PREDICTIONS:
  - "@" [PER] (1:2)
  - "lesleysfarm" [PER] (2:3)

PARTIAL MATCH METRICS:
Exact Match F1: 0.6667
Left Boundary Match F1: 0.6667
Right Boundary Match F1: 0.6667
Partial Overlap F1: 0.6667
Overlap Percentage F1: 0.6667

DETAILED ANALYSIS:

  Gold: "@" [ORG] vs Pred: "@" [PER]
  Overlap: "T" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "@" [PER] vs Pred: "@" [PER]
  Overlap: "T" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "lesleysfarm" [ORG] vs Pred: "lesleysfarm" [PER]
  Overlap: " " (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "lesleysfarm" [PER] vs Pred: "lesleysfarm" [PER]
  Overlap: " " (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

================================================================================

--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
GOLD MENTIONS:
Mention object: [Mention(entity_type='PER', start='1', end='2', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='1', end='2', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='2', end='3', text='mansell79'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='2', end='3', text='mansell79'), Mention(entity_type='LOC', start='13', end='16', text='jubilee hotel Letterston')]
  - "@" [PER] (1:2)
  - "@" [PER] (1:2)
  - "mansell79" [PER] (2:3)
  - "mansell79" [PER] (2:3)
  - "jubilee hotel Letterston" [LOC] (13:16)

PREDICTIONS:
  - "@" [PER] (1:2)
  - "mansell79" [PER] (2:3)

PARTIAL MATCH METRICS:
Exact Match F1: 0.8000
Left Boundary Match F1: 1.1429
Right Boundary Match F1: 1.1429
Partial Overlap F1: 1.1429
Overlap Percentage F1: 0.5714

DETAILED ANALYSIS:

  Gold: "@" [PER] vs Pred: "@" [PER]
  Overlap: "T" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "@" [PER] vs Pred: "@" [PER]
  Overlap: "T" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "mansell79" [PER] vs Pred: "mansell79" [PER]
  Overlap: " " (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "mansell79" [PER] vs Pred: "mansell79" [PER]
  Overlap: " " (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

================================================================================

--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
GOLD MENTIONS:
Mention object: [Mention(entity_type='LOC', start='4', end='7', text='#BTV Ward 8'), Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='10', end='11', text='NPA'), Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='10', end='11', text='NPA')]
  - "#BTV Ward 8" [LOC] (4:7)
  - "NPA" [ORG] (10:11)
  - "NPA" [ORG] (10:11)

PREDICTIONS:
  - "NPA" [ORG] (10:11)

PARTIAL MATCH METRICS:
Exact Match F1: 0.6667
Left Boundary Match F1: 1.0000
Right Boundary Match F1: 1.0000
Partial Overlap F1: 1.0000
Overlap Percentage F1: 0.5000

DETAILED ANALYSIS:

  Gold: "NPA" [ORG] vs Pred: "NPA" [ORG]
  Overlap: "l" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "NPA" [ORG] vs Pred: "NPA" [ORG]
  Overlap: "l" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

================================================================================

Sentence 135: @ APNEUNJII thanks
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
GOLD MENTIONS:
Mention object: [Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='0', end='1', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='0', end='1', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='1', end='2', text='APNEUNJII'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='1', end='2', text='APNEUNJII')]
  - "@" [ORG] (0:1)
  - "@" [PER] (0:1)
  - "APNEUNJII" [ORG] (1:2)
  - "APNEUNJII" [PER] (1:2)

PREDICTIONS:
  - "@" [PER] (0:1)
  - "APNEUNJII" [PER] (1:2)

PARTIAL MATCH METRICS:
Exact Match F1: 0.6667
Left Boundary Match F1: 0.6667
Right Boundary Match F1: 0.6667
Partial Overlap F1: 0.6667
Overlap Percentage F1: 0.6667

DETAILED ANALYSIS:

  Gold: "@" [ORG] vs Pred: "@" [PER]
  Overlap: "@" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "@" [PER] vs Pred: "@" [PER]
  Overlap: "@" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "APNEUNJII" [ORG] vs Pred: "APNEUNJII" [PER]
  Overlap: " " (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "APNEUNJII" [PER] vs Pred: "APNEUNJII" [PER]
  Overlap: " " (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

================================================================================

--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
GOLD MENTIONS:
Mention object: [Mention(entity_type='LOC', start='1', end='2', text='Chelmsford'), Mention(entity_type='LOC', start='1', end='2', text='Chelmsford'), Mention(entity_type='LOC', start='13', end='15', text='Gerard Gardens'), Mention(entity_type='LOC', start='13', end='15', text='Gerard Gardens'), Mention(entity_type='LOC', start='16', end='17', text='Chelmsford'), Mention(entity_type='LOC', start='16', end='17', text='Chelmsford'), Mention(entity_type='LOC', start='18', end='19', text='Essex'), Mention(entity_type='LOC', start='18', end='19', text='Essex'), Mention(entity_type='LOC', start='20', end='22', text='CM 2')]
  - "Chelmsford" [LOC] (1:2)
  - "Chelmsford" [LOC] (1:2)
  - "Gerard Gardens" [LOC] (13:15)
  - "Gerard Gardens" [LOC] (13:15)
  - "Chelmsford" [LOC] (16:17)
  - "Chelmsford" [LOC] (16:17)
  - "Essex" [LOC] (18:19)
  - "Essex" [LOC] (18:19)
  - "CM 2" [LOC] (20:22)

PREDICTIONS:
  - "Chelmsford" [LOC] (1:2)
  - "Gerard Gardens" [LOC] (13:15)
  - "Chelmsford" [LOC] (16:17)
  - "Essex" [LOC] (18:19)

PARTIAL MATCH METRICS:
Exact Match F1: 0.8889
Left Boundary Match F1: 1.2308
Right Boundary Match F1: 1.2308
Partial Overlap F1: 1.2308
Overlap Percentage F1: 0.6154

DETAILED ANALYSIS:

  Gold: "Chelmsford" [LOC] vs Pred: "Chelmsford" [LOC]
  Overlap: "e" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "Chelmsford" [LOC] vs Pred: "Chelmsford" [LOC]
  Overlap: "e" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "Gerard Gardens" [LOC] vs Pred: "Gerard Gardens" [LOC]
  Overlap: "rd" (2 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "Gerard Gardens" [LOC] vs Pred: "Gerard Gardens" [LOC]
  Overlap: "rd" (2 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "Chelmsford" [LOC] vs Pred: "Chelmsford" [LOC]
  Overlap: ":" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "Chelmsford" [LOC] vs Pred: "Chelmsford" [LOC]
  Overlap: ":" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "Essex" [LOC] vs Pred: "Essex" [LOC]
  Overlap: "£" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "Essex" [LOC] vs Pred: "Essex" [LOC]
  Overlap: "£" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

================================================================================

--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
GOLD MENTIONS:
Mention object: [Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='0', end='1', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='0', end='1', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='1', end='2', text='HorneyMedia'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='1', end='2', text='HorneyMedia'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='10', end='11', text='#AlanPardew')]
  - "@" [ORG] (0:1)
  - "@" [PER] (0:1)
  - "HorneyMedia" [ORG] (1:2)
  - "HorneyMedia" [PER] (1:2)
  - "#AlanPardew" [PER] (10:11)

PREDICTIONS:
  - "@" [PER] (0:1)
  - "HorneyMedia" [PER] (1:2)

PARTIAL MATCH METRICS:
Exact Match F1: 0.5714
Left Boundary Match F1: 0.5714
Right Boundary Match F1: 0.5714
Partial Overlap F1: 0.5714
Overlap Percentage F1: 0.5714

DETAILED ANALYSIS:

  Gold: "@" [ORG] vs Pred: "@" [PER]
  Overlap: "@" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "@" [PER] vs Pred: "@" [PER]
  Overlap: "@" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "HorneyMedia" [ORG] vs Pred: "HorneyMedia" [PER]
  Overlap: " " (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "HorneyMedia" [PER] vs Pred: "HorneyMedia" [PER]
  Overlap: " " (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

================================================================================

--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
GOLD MENTIONS:
Mention object: [Mention(entity_type='PER', start='0', end='1', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='0', end='1', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='1', end='2', text='omegaPoint'), Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='1', end='2', text='omegaPoint'), Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='16', end='17', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='17', end='18', text='firefox'), Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='17', end='18', text='firefox')]
  - "@" [PER] (0:1)
  - "@" [ORG] (0:1)
  - "omegaPoint" [PER] (1:2)
  - "omegaPoint" [ORG] (1:2)
  - "@" [ORG] (16:17)
  - "firefox" [ORG] (17:18)
  - "firefox" [ORG] (17:18)

PREDICTIONS:
  - "@" [ORG] (0:1)
  - "omegaPoint" [ORG] (1:2)
  - "firefox" [ORG] (17:18)

PARTIAL MATCH METRICS:
Exact Match F1: 0.6667
Left Boundary Match F1: 0.8000
Right Boundary Match F1: 0.8000
Partial Overlap F1: 0.8000
Overlap Percentage F1: 0.6000

DETAILED ANALYSIS:

  Gold: "@" [PER] vs Pred: "@" [ORG]
  Overlap: "@" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "@" [ORG] vs Pred: "@" [ORG]
  Overlap: "@" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "omegaPoint" [PER] vs Pred: "omegaPoint" [ORG]
  Overlap: " " (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "omegaPoint" [ORG] vs Pred: "omegaPoint" [ORG]
  Overlap: " " (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "firefox" [ORG] vs Pred: "firefox" [ORG]
  Overlap: "s" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "firefox" [ORG] vs Pred: "firefox" [ORG]
  Overlap: "s" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

================================================================================

--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
GOLD MENTIONS:
Mention object: [Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='3', end='6', text='Yume & Co'), Mention(entity_type='LOC', start='3', end='7', text='Yume & Co Grimsby'), Mention(entity_type='LOC', start='6', end='7', text='Grimsby'), Mention(entity_type='LOC', start='8', end='11', text='North East Lincolnshire'), Mention(entity_type='LOC', start='8', end='11', text='North East Lincolnshire')]
  - "Yume & Co" [ORG] (3:6)
  - "Yume & Co Grimsby" [LOC] (3:7)
  - "Grimsby" [LOC] (6:7)
  - "North East Lincolnshire" [LOC] (8:11)
  - "North East Lincolnshire" [LOC] (8:11)

PREDICTIONS:
  - "Yume & Co Grimsby" [LOC] (3:7)
  - "North East Lincolnshire" [LOC] (8:11)

PARTIAL MATCH METRICS:
Exact Match F1: 0.6667
Left Boundary Match F1: 0.8571
Right Boundary Match F1: 1.1429
Partial Overlap F1: 1.1429
Overlap Percentage F1: 0.5714

DETAILED ANALYSIS:

  Gold: "Yume & Co" [ORG] vs Pred: "Yume & Co Grimsby" [LOC]
  Overlap: "m a" (3 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 75.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MISMATCH: Gold=6, Pred=7, Offset=1

  Gold: "Yume & Co Grimsby" [LOC] vs Pred: "Yume & Co Grimsby" [LOC]
  Overlap: "m at" (4 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "Grimsby" [LOC] vs Pred: "Yume & Co Grimsby" [LOC]
  Overlap: "t" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 25.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MISMATCH: Gold=6, Pred=3, Offset=-3
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "North East Lincolnshire" [LOC] vs Pred: "North East Lincolnshire" [LOC]
  Overlap: "Yum" (3 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "North East Lincolnshire" [LOC] vs Pred: "North East Lincolnshire" [LOC]
  Overlap: "Yum" (3 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

================================================================================

--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
GOLD MENTIONS:
Mention object: [Mention(entity_type='PER', start='1', end='2', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='1', end='2', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='2', end='3', text='WillauerProsky'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='2', end='3', text='WillauerProsky'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='9', end='10', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='10', end='11', text='halburd1'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='10', end='11', text='halburd1'), Mention(entity_type='LOC', start='12', end='14', text='Wall Street'), Mention(entity_type='LOC', start='12', end='14', text='Wall Street')]
  - "@" [PER] (1:2)
  - "@" [PER] (1:2)
  - "WillauerProsky" [PER] (2:3)
  - "WillauerProsky" [PER] (2:3)
  - "@" [PER] (9:10)
  - "halburd1" [PER] (10:11)
  - "halburd1" [PER] (10:11)
  - "Wall Street" [LOC] (12:14)
  - "Wall Street" [LOC] (12:14)

PREDICTIONS:
  - "@" [PER] (1:2)
  - "WillauerProsky" [PER] (2:3)
  - "halburd1" [PER] (10:11)
  - "Wall Street" [LOC] (12:14)

PARTIAL MATCH METRICS:
Exact Match F1: 0.8889
Left Boundary Match F1: 1.2308
Right Boundary Match F1: 1.2308
Partial Overlap F1: 1.2308
Overlap Percentage F1: 0.6154

DETAILED ANALYSIS:

  Gold: "@" [PER] vs Pred: "@" [PER]
  Overlap: "T" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "@" [PER] vs Pred: "@" [PER]
  Overlap: "T" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "WillauerProsky" [PER] vs Pred: "WillauerProsky" [PER]
  Overlap: " " (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "WillauerProsky" [PER] vs Pred: "WillauerProsky" [PER]
  Overlap: " " (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "halburd1" [PER] vs Pred: "halburd1" [PER]
  Overlap: "u" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "halburd1" [PER] vs Pred: "halburd1" [PER]
  Overlap: "u" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "Wall Street" [LOC] vs Pred: "Wall Street" [LOC]
  Overlap: "rP" (2 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "Wall Street" [LOC] vs Pred: "Wall Street" [LOC]
  Overlap: "rP" (2 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

================================================================================

--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
GOLD MENTIONS:
Mention object: [Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='1', end='2', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='1', end='2', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='2', end='3', text='dcunited'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='2', end='3', text='dcunited'), Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='8', end='9', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='8', end='9', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='9', end='10', text='RichmondKickers'), Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='9', end='10', text='RichmondKickers'), Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='14', end='15', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='14', end='15', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='15', end='16', text='MarylandMSoccer'), Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='15', end='16', text='MarylandMSoccer')]
  - "@" [ORG] (1:2)
  - "@" [PER] (1:2)
  - "dcunited" [ORG] (2:3)
  - "dcunited" [PER] (2:3)
  - "@" [ORG] (8:9)
  - "@" [ORG] (8:9)
  - "RichmondKickers" [ORG] (9:10)
  - "RichmondKickers" [ORG] (9:10)
  - "@" [ORG] (14:15)
  - "@" [ORG] (14:15)
  - "MarylandMSoccer" [ORG] (15:16)
  - "MarylandMSoccer" [ORG] (15:16)

PREDICTIONS:
  - "@" [PER] (1:2)
  - "dcunited" [PER] (2:3)
  - "@" [ORG] (8:9)
  - "RichmondKickers" [ORG] (9:10)
  - "@" [ORG] (14:15)
  - "MarylandMSoccer" [ORG] (15:16)

PARTIAL MATCH METRICS:
Exact Match F1: 0.8571
Left Boundary Match F1: 1.1111
Right Boundary Match F1: 1.1111
Partial Overlap F1: 1.1111
Overlap Percentage F1: 0.6667

DETAILED ANALYSIS:

  Gold: "@" [ORG] vs Pred: "@" [PER]
  Overlap: "T" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "@" [PER] vs Pred: "@" [PER]
  Overlap: "T" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "dcunited" [ORG] vs Pred: "dcunited" [PER]
  Overlap: " " (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "dcunited" [PER] vs Pred: "dcunited" [PER]
  Overlap: " " (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "@" [ORG] vs Pred: "@" [ORG]
  Overlap: "n" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "@" [ORG] vs Pred: "@" [ORG]
  Overlap: "n" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "RichmondKickers" [ORG] vs Pred: "RichmondKickers" [ORG]
  Overlap: "i" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "RichmondKickers" [ORG] vs Pred: "RichmondKickers" [ORG]
  Overlap: "i" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "@" [ORG] vs Pred: "@" [ORG]
  Overlap: ":" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "@" [ORG] vs Pred: "@" [ORG]
  Overlap: ":" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "MarylandMSoccer" [ORG] vs Pred: "MarylandMSoccer" [ORG]
  Overlap: " " (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "MarylandMSoccer" [ORG] vs Pred: "MarylandMSoccer" [ORG]
  Overlap: " " (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

================================================================================

Sentence 162: @ IndianaAL thanks for the great #Hot9at9 tonight
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
GOLD MENTIONS:
Mention object: [Mention(entity_type='PER', start='0', end='1', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='0', end='1', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='1', end='2', text='IndianaAL'), Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='1', end='2', text='IndianaAL'), Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='6', end='7', text='#Hot9at9')]
  - "@" [PER] (0:1)
  - "@" [ORG] (0:1)
  - "IndianaAL" [PER] (1:2)
  - "IndianaAL" [ORG] (1:2)
  - "#Hot9at9" [ORG] (6:7)

PREDICTIONS:
  - "@" [ORG] (0:1)
  - "IndianaAL" [ORG] (1:2)

PARTIAL MATCH METRICS:
Exact Match F1: 0.5714
Left Boundary Match F1: 0.5714
Right Boundary Match F1: 0.5714
Partial Overlap F1: 0.5714
Overlap Percentage F1: 0.5714

DETAILED ANALYSIS:

  Gold: "@" [PER] vs Pred: "@" [ORG]
  Overlap: "@" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "@" [ORG] vs Pred: "@" [ORG]
  Overlap: "@" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "IndianaAL" [PER] vs Pred: "IndianaAL" [ORG]
  Overlap: " " (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "IndianaAL" [ORG] vs Pred: "IndianaAL" [ORG]
  Overlap: " " (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

================================================================================

--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
GOLD MENTIONS:
Mention object: [Mention(entity_type='PER', start='4', end='5', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='5', end='6', text='chantell_price'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='5', end='6', text='chantell_price'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='10', end='11', text='Kevin'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='10', end='11', text='Kevin')]
  - "@" [PER] (4:5)
  - "chantell_price" [PER] (5:6)
  - "chantell_price" [PER] (5:6)
  - "Kevin" [PER] (10:11)
  - "Kevin" [PER] (10:11)

PREDICTIONS:
  - "chantell_price" [PER] (5:6)
  - "Kevin" [PER] (10:11)

PARTIAL MATCH METRICS:
Exact Match F1: 0.8000
Left Boundary Match F1: 1.1429
Right Boundary Match F1: 1.1429
Partial Overlap F1: 1.1429
Overlap Percentage F1: 0.5714

DETAILED ANALYSIS:

  Gold: "chantell_price" [PER] vs Pred: "chantell_price" [PER]
  Overlap: "h" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "chantell_price" [PER] vs Pred: "chantell_price" [PER]
  Overlap: "h" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "Kevin" [PER] vs Pred: "Kevin" [PER]
  Overlap: "_" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "Kevin" [PER] vs Pred: "Kevin" [PER]
  Overlap: "_" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

================================================================================

Sentence 166: @ wansibly bah bly main fisik gessss
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
GOLD MENTIONS:
Mention object: [Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='0', end='1', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='0', end='1', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='1', end='2', text='wansibly'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='1', end='2', text='wansibly')]
  - "@" [ORG] (0:1)
  - "@" [PER] (0:1)
  - "wansibly" [ORG] (1:2)
  - "wansibly" [PER] (1:2)

PREDICTIONS:
  - "@" [PER] (0:1)
  - "wansibly" [PER] (1:2)

PARTIAL MATCH METRICS:
Exact Match F1: 0.6667
Left Boundary Match F1: 0.6667
Right Boundary Match F1: 0.6667
Partial Overlap F1: 0.6667
Overlap Percentage F1: 0.6667

DETAILED ANALYSIS:

  Gold: "@" [ORG] vs Pred: "@" [PER]
  Overlap: "@" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "@" [PER] vs Pred: "@" [PER]
  Overlap: "@" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "wansibly" [ORG] vs Pred: "wansibly" [PER]
  Overlap: " " (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "wansibly" [PER] vs Pred: "wansibly" [PER]
  Overlap: " " (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

================================================================================

--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
GOLD MENTIONS:
Mention object: [Mention(entity_type='LOC', start='4', end='6', text='Kugluktuk HS'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='10', end='11', text='Godson'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='10', end='11', text='Godson'), Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='13', end='14', text='NAC'), Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='13', end='14', text='NAC')]
  - "Kugluktuk HS" [LOC] (4:6)
  - "Godson" [PER] (10:11)
  - "Godson" [PER] (10:11)
  - "NAC" [ORG] (13:14)
  - "NAC" [ORG] (13:14)

PREDICTIONS:
  - "Godson" [PER] (10:11)
  - "NAC" [ORG] (13:14)

PARTIAL MATCH METRICS:
Exact Match F1: 0.8000
Left Boundary Match F1: 1.1429
Right Boundary Match F1: 1.1429
Partial Overlap F1: 1.1429
Overlap Percentage F1: 0.5714

DETAILED ANALYSIS:

  Gold: "Godson" [PER] vs Pred: "Godson" [PER]
  Overlap: "i" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "Godson" [PER] vs Pred: "Godson" [PER]
  Overlap: "i" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "NAC" [ORG] vs Pred: "NAC" [ORG]
  Overlap: "v" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "NAC" [ORG] vs Pred: "NAC" [ORG]
  Overlap: "v" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

================================================================================

--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
GOLD MENTIONS:
Mention object: [Mention(entity_type='PER', start='1', end='2', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='1', end='2', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='2', end='3', text='Leeh_Horan_1'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='2', end='3', text='Leeh_Horan_1'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='4', end='5', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='5', end='6', text='Real_Liam_Payne'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='5', end='6', text='Real_Liam_Payne'), Mention(entity_type='LOC', start='11', end='12', text='BRAZIL'), Mention(entity_type='LOC', start='11', end='12', text='BRAZIL')]
  - "@" [PER] (1:2)
  - "@" [PER] (1:2)
  - "Leeh_Horan_1" [PER] (2:3)
  - "Leeh_Horan_1" [PER] (2:3)
  - "@" [PER] (4:5)
  - "Real_Liam_Payne" [PER] (5:6)
  - "Real_Liam_Payne" [PER] (5:6)
  - "BRAZIL" [LOC] (11:12)
  - "BRAZIL" [LOC] (11:12)

PREDICTIONS:
  - "@" [PER] (1:2)
  - "Leeh_Horan_1" [PER] (2:3)
  - "Real_Liam_Payne" [PER] (5:6)
  - "BRAZIL" [LOC] (11:12)

PARTIAL MATCH METRICS:
Exact Match F1: 0.8889
Left Boundary Match F1: 1.2308
Right Boundary Match F1: 1.2308
Partial Overlap F1: 1.2308
Overlap Percentage F1: 0.6154

DETAILED ANALYSIS:

  Gold: "@" [PER] vs Pred: "@" [PER]
  Overlap: "T" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "@" [PER] vs Pred: "@" [PER]
  Overlap: "T" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "Leeh_Horan_1" [PER] vs Pred: "Leeh_Horan_1" [PER]
  Overlap: " " (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "Leeh_Horan_1" [PER] vs Pred: "Leeh_Horan_1" [PER]
  Overlap: " " (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "Real_Liam_Payne" [PER] vs Pred: "Real_Liam_Payne" [PER]
  Overlap: "L" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "Real_Liam_Payne" [PER] vs Pred: "Real_Liam_Payne" [PER]
  Overlap: "L" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "BRAZIL" [LOC] vs Pred: "BRAZIL" [LOC]
  Overlap: "o" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "BRAZIL" [LOC] vs Pred: "BRAZIL" [LOC]
  Overlap: "o" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

================================================================================

--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
GOLD MENTIONS:
Mention object: [Mention(entity_type='PER', start='0', end='1', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='0', end='1', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='1', end='2', text='PetitePants'), Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='1', end='2', text='PetitePants'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='2', end='3', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='2', end='3', text='@'), Mention(entity_type='PER', start='3', end='4', text='EasilyTempted'), Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='3', end='4', text='EasilyTempted'), Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='15', end='16', text='Twitter'), Mention(entity_type='ORG', start='15', end='16', text='Twitter')]
  - "@" [PER] (0:1)
  - "@" [ORG] (0:1)
  - "PetitePants" [PER] (1:2)
  - "PetitePants" [ORG] (1:2)
  - "@" [PER] (2:3)
  - "@" [ORG] (2:3)
  - "EasilyTempted" [PER] (3:4)
  - "EasilyTempted" [ORG] (3:4)
  - "Twitter" [ORG] (15:16)
  - "Twitter" [ORG] (15:16)

PREDICTIONS:
  - "@" [ORG] (0:1)
  - "PetitePants" [ORG] (1:2)
  - "@" [ORG] (2:3)
  - "EasilyTempted" [ORG] (3:4)
  - "Twitter" [ORG] (15:16)

PARTIAL MATCH METRICS:
Exact Match F1: 0.7143
Left Boundary Match F1: 0.8000
Right Boundary Match F1: 0.8000
Partial Overlap F1: 0.8000
Overlap Percentage F1: 0.6667

DETAILED ANALYSIS:

  Gold: "@" [PER] vs Pred: "@" [ORG]
  Overlap: "@" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "@" [ORG] vs Pred: "@" [ORG]
  Overlap: "@" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "PetitePants" [PER] vs Pred: "PetitePants" [ORG]
  Overlap: " " (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "PetitePants" [ORG] vs Pred: "PetitePants" [ORG]
  Overlap: " " (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "@" [PER] vs Pred: "@" [ORG]
  Overlap: "P" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "@" [ORG] vs Pred: "@" [ORG]
  Overlap: "P" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "EasilyTempted" [PER] vs Pred: "EasilyTempted" [ORG]
  Overlap: "e" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "EasilyTempted" [ORG] vs Pred: "EasilyTempted" [ORG]
  Overlap: "e" (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "Twitter" [ORG] vs Pred: "Twitter" [ORG]
  Overlap: " " (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

  Gold: "Twitter" [ORG] vs Pred: "Twitter" [ORG]
  Overlap: " " (1 chars)
  Overlap covers 100.0% of gold and 100.0% of prediction
  LEFT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes
  RIGHT BOUNDARY MATCH: Yes

================================================================================
