Morning	O
5km	O
run	O
with	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
for	O
breast	O
cancer	O
awareness	O
#	O
pinkoctober	B-event
#	O
breastcancerawareness	B-event
#	O
zalorafit	O
#	O
zalorafitxbnwrc	O
@	O
The	O
Central	B-location
Park	I-location
,	I-location
Desa	I-location
Parkcity	I-location
{{URL}}	O

President	B-person
Trump	I-person
Arrives	O
at	O
UFC	B-corporation
244	I-corporation
in	O
New	B-location
York	I-location
to	O
Cheers	O
from	O
Crowd	O
(	O
VIDEO	O
)	O
{{URL}}	O
via	O
{{USERNAME}}	O

"	O
I	O
've	O
been	O
in	O
law	O
enforcement	O
for	O
23	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
've	O
never	O
seen	O
this	O
in	O
this	O
city	O
and	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
never	O
see	O
it	O
again	O
"	O
-	O
Buffalo	B-corporation
Police	I-corporation
Captain	O
Jeff	B-person
Rinaldo	I-person
{{USERNAME}}	O
#	O
Buffalo	B-event
protest	I-event

I	O
got	O
mine	O
yesterday	O
!	O
****	O
Doctors	O
say	O
:	O
Now	O
's	O
the	O
time	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
flu	O
shot	O
-	O
Eyewitness	B-corporation
News	I-corporation
WTVO	I-corporation
WQRF	I-corporation
{{URL}}	O
via	O
{@Google News@}	B-product

Mayo	B-product
Breast	I-product
Cancer	I-product
Vaccine	I-product
Could	O
Be	O
Available	O
In	O
Less	O
Than	O
A	O
Decade	O
via	O
{@Forbes@}	B-product
{{URL}}	O

Animated	O
Atrocities	O
||	O
Bart	B-person
vs	O
.	O
Itchy	B-creative_work
and	I-creative_work
Scratchy	I-creative_work
[	O
The	B-creative_work
Simpsons	I-creative_work
]	O
{{URL}}	O
via	O
{@YouTube@}	B-product
Wow	O
the	B-creative_work
Simpsons	I-creative_work
has	O
really	O
..	O
.	O
yeesh	O
.	O

100	O
photos	O
from	O
Women	O
's	O
3-nations	B-event
final	I-event
game	I-event
in	O
Salo	B-location
.	O
{{URL}}	O
#	O
floorball	B-product
#	O
salibandy	B-product
{{USERNAME}}	O
{{USERNAME}}	O

Join	O
us	O
LIVE	O
from	O
day	O
2	O
of	O
#	O
LAB19	O
with	O
{@SERA - Labour's Environment Campaign@}	B-corporation
for	O
their	O
Uplands	B-location
,	O
National	B-location
Parks	I-location
&	O
Climate	O
Change	O
:	O
Supporting	B-creative_work
Nature	I-creative_work
for	O
the	O
Many	O
fringe	B-event
event	I-event
featuring	O
{@Daniel Zeichner@}	B-person
{{USERNAME}}	O
{@Hilary Benn@}	B-person
{{USERNAME}}	O
{@RSPB@}	B-corporation
{{URL}}	O

Live	O
now	O
!!	O
Come	O
by	O
the	O
stream	O
and	O
show	O
love	O
#	O
twitch	B-corporation
#	O
PathToAffiliate	O
#	O
Smallstreamerconnect	B-event
#	O
Warzone	B-creative_work
#	O
Streamer	O
#	O
Twitchstreaming	B-event
{{USERNAME}}	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
Twitch	B-corporation
:	O
{{URL}}	O

saw	O
my	O
boy	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
@	O
rolling	O
loud	O
today	O
during	O
travis	O
scott	O
’s	O
performance	O
.	O
NOBODY	O
CAN	O
MATCH	O
NYC	B-location
ENERGY	O

Trump	B-person
2020	O
Make	B-creative_work
Christmas	I-creative_work
Great	I-creative_work
Again	I-creative_work
6-Pack	I-creative_work
Buttons	I-creative_work
-	O
Red	B-product
and	I-product
Green	I-product
Festive	I-product
Color	I-product
Badges	I-product
-	O
Xmas	O
Tree	O
{{URL}}	O
via	O
{@Etsy@}	B-product

Check	O
out	O
my	O
new	O
album	O
"	O
Above	B-creative_work
the	I-creative_work
Rain	I-creative_work
"	O
distributed	O
by	O
{@DistroKid@}	B-product
and	O
live	O
on	O
iTunes	B-corporation
!	O
{{URL}}	O
Each	O
song	O
tells	O
a	O
story	O
That	O
may	O
resonate	O
with	O
you	O
Please	O
follow	O
and	O
retweet	O
Oh	O
,	O
and	O
download	O
,	O
thank	O
you	O
.	O
Popsd	B-person

#	O
Who	O
_	O
Is	O
_	O
Real	O
_	O
SadGuru	B-person
The	O
full	O
saint	O
describes	O
the	O
worship	O
of	O
three	O
times	O
.	O
Worshiping	O
the	O
full	O
God	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon,the	O
hospitality	O
of	O
the	O
gods	O
of	O
the	O
world	O
and	O
the	O
evening	O
aarti	O
tells	O
separately	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
benevolent	O
saint	O
Rampal	B-person
Ji	I-person
Maharaj	I-person
{{USERNAME}}	O

3-Day	O
Recap	O
:	O
-	O
8	O
Christmas	B-event
parties	I-event
-	O
5	O
hrs	O
of	O
Star	B-creative_work
Wars	I-creative_work
-	O
ran	O
13.5	O
miles	O
-	O
3	O
workouts	O
at	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
-	O
20k	O
+calories	O
consumed	O
-	O
Prep	O
for	O
trip	O
to	O
&	O
-	O
Read	O
/	O
Listen	O
to	O
books	O
-	O
Love	O
from	O
dozens	O
of	O
family	O
&	O
friends	O
Merry	B-event
Christmas	I-event
!	O

Putting	O
this	O
season	O
in	O
perspective	O
,	O
the	O
Rams	B-group
had	O
two	O
1k	O
receivers	O
,	O
Goff	B-person
easily	O
surpassed	O
4k	O
,	O
Donald	B-person
/	O
Fowler	B-person
each	O
with	O
11	O
+sacks	O
,	O
Gurley	B-person
with	O
13	O
+TD	O
’s	O
in	O
limited	O
touches	O
.	O
But	O
,	O
this	O
team	O
obviously	O
underperformed	O
for	O
a	O
variety	O
of	O
reasons	O
.	O
Not	O
just	O
one	O
key	O
thing	O
.	O
{@J.B. Long@}	B-person

.	O
{@Global Kingston@}	B-corporation
If	O
you	O
are	O
heading	O
out	O
today	O
,	O
be	O
sure	O
to	O
double	O
check	O
that	O
places	O
are	O
open	O
.	O
{@St. Lawrence College@}	B-location
is	O
experiencing	O
a	O
power	O
outage	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
advised	O
NOT	O
to	O
go	O
the	O
the	O
#	O
ygk	O
campus	B-location
.	O
#	O
windstorm	O

Lavanderboyz	B-group
chillcast	I-group
feat	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
coming	O
out	O
next	O
weekend	O
jus	O
got	O
done	O
recording	B-product

#	O
StrayKidsComback	B-group
So	O
happy	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
again	O
,	O
have	O
a	O
good	O
day	O
dont	O
forget	O
to	O
eat	O
well	O
and	O
rest	O
well	O
Stay	O
healthy	O
♥	O
I	O
LOVE	O
YOU	O
MORE	O
THAN	O
3000	O
...	O
.	O
:)	O
{@Stray Kids@}	B-group

The	O
death	O
of	O
{@Chadwick Boseman@}	B-person
hits	O
hard	O
.	O
It	O
’s	O
a	O
reminder	O
that	O
people	O
are	O
fighting	O
silent	O
battles	O
that	O
you	O
may	O
not	O
know	O
about	O
.	O
Always	O
be	O
kind	O
.	O
Do	O
not	O
assume	O
.	O
Love	O
fully	O
while	O
you	O
can	O
.	O
And	O
live	O
life	O
to	O
the	O
fullest	O
.	O
#	O
ChadwickBoseman	B-person
#	O
WakandaForever	O

I	O
am	O
0-3	O
in	O
our	O
family	O
3v3	O
games	O
.	O
Mixed	O
up	O
the	O
teams	O
after	O
Bball	B-event
and	O
now	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
defeated	O
in	O
kickball	O
and	O
Vball	O
!	O
My	O
team	O
needs	O
to	O
do	O
better	O
,	O
ca	O
n’t	O
do	O
it	O
all	O
myself	O
!	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
{{USERNAME}}	O

Awesome	O
win	O
{@Carla Esparza@}	B-person
,	O
you	O
turn	O
the	O
corner	O
on	O
those	O
takedowns	O
with	O
the	O
best	O
,	O
enjoy	O
the	O
w	O
my	O
friend	O
!	O
#	O
ufcfightisland	O
#	O
MMA	B-corporation

#	O
NowPlaying	O
Probe	B-creative_work
the	I-creative_work
Act	I-creative_work
2	I-creative_work
by	O
Official	B-person
Shiraz	I-person
/	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
listen	O
now	O
{{{URL}}}	O
#	O
dremtgi	O
#	O
dremstuff	O

Thought	O
#	O
WayneBarnes	B-person
had	O
a	O
great	O
game	O
today	O
in	O
the	O
Japan	B-location
v	O
South	B-location
Africa	I-location
game	O
!!	O
Really	O
hope	O
he	O
gets	O
to	O
referee	O
the	O
World	O
Cup	O
Final	O
{@Rugby World Cup@}	B-event
!!	O
!	O

I	O
do	O
n’t	O
celebrate	O
thanksgiving	B-event
but	O
I	O
just	O
want	O
to	O
say	O
how	O
thankful	O
I	O
am	O
for	O
{@One Direction@}	B-group
for	O
being	O
5	O
amazing	O
guys	O
with	O
5	O
wonderful	O
albums	O
!	O
I	O
love	O
and	O
miss	O
you	O
guys	O
{@Liam ☀️@}	B-person
{@zayn@}	B-person
{@Louis Tomlinson@}	B-person
{@Harry Styles.@}	B-person
{@Niall Horan@}	B-person

#	O
climatechange	B-event
#	O
ClimateEmergency	O
#	O
bushfiresNSW	B-event
#	O
bushfires	B-event
{@Gladys Berejiklian@}	B-person
{@Scott Morrison@}	B-person
raging	O
fires	O
in	O
the	O
Blue	B-corporation
Mountains	I-corporation
need	O
more	O
resources	O
both	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
air	O
.	O
Your	O
reinstatement	O
of	O
funding	O
is	O
essential	O
.	O

SO	O
THE	O
BROWNS	B-group
BEAT	O
THE	O
BREAKS	O
OFF	O
THE	O
SQUEELERS	B-group
THURSDAY	O
!	O
HOW	O
WILL	O
U	O
CELEBRATE	O
?	O
HOW	O
ABOUT	O
WITHSOME	O
FRESH	O
NEW	O
CUSTOM	B-product
BROWNS	I-product
ATTIRE	I-product
FROM	O
OUR	O
FRIENDS	O
AT	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
THEY	O
HAVE	O
EVERYTHING	O
YOU	O
NEED	O
.	O
VISIT	O
{{URL}}	O
AND	O
USE	O
CODE	O
"	O
AM1490	B-product
"	O
FOR	O
20	O
%	O
OFF	O
YOUR	O
ORDER	O
!!!	O
!	O

So	O
Gaga	B-person
and	O
Celine	B-person
doing	O
their	O
MOST	O
with	O
these	O
mics	O
and	O
John	B-person
legend	I-person
is	O
in	O
a	O
stairwell	O
with	O
a	O
single	O
air	O
pod	O
.	O
Love	O
a	O
humble	O
star	O
.	O
{@chrissy teigen@}	B-person
you	O
won	O
.	O

"	O
Social	O
security	O
schemes	O
are	O
always	O
met	O
by	O
resistance	O
across	O
the	O
world	O
,	O
as	O
in	O
our	O
country	O
.	O
We	O
seek	O
to	O
convince	O
,	O
hear	O
problems	O
and	O
amend	O
the	O
Social	B-product
Security	I-product
Fund	I-product
and	O
the	O
Act	O
were	O
it	O
is	O
possible	O
,"	O
says	O
Mr	B-person
.	O
Ramesh	B-person
Badal	I-person
,	O
Vice-president	B-person
{{USERNAME}}	O

Never	O
underestimate	O
the	O
power	O
of	O
your	O
vibe	O
.	O
DJLOONYO	B-person
OnMARSPaMoreTurns1	O
{{USERNAME}}	O

Very	O
sad	O
and	O
shock	O
great	O
NBA	B-corporation
player	O
(	O
Lakers	B-group
)	O
Kobe	B-person
Bryant	I-person
has	O
died	O
helicopter	O
crash	O
gotta	O
be	O
sad	O
.	O
Condolences	O
to	O
his	O
family	O
.	O
Some	O
others	O
who	O
had	O
perished	O
in	O
Helicopter	O
crash	O
and	O
died	O
{@CBS News@}	B-product
{@IMDb@}	B-corporation

Tropical	B-event
Storm	I-event
Cristobal	I-event
slows	O
down	O
before	O
it	O
reaches	O
Louisiana	B-location
coast	I-location
,	O
Hurricane	B-group
Center	I-group
says	O
{{URL}}	O
via	O
{@NOLA.com@}	B-corporation

Buzzer	O
beater	O
from	O
{@Cody Garbrandt@}	B-person
,	O
Walkoff	B-event
KO	I-event
from	O
{@Sean O'Malley@}	B-person
#	O
UFC250	B-event

ok	O
just	O
wanted	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
i	O
ship	B-creative_work
{@Shane Dawson@}	B-person
and	O
{@Ryland Adams@}	B-person
because	O
their	O
cute	O
together	O
and	O
not	O
because	O
i	O
have	O
the	O
most	O
weirdest	O
dreams	O
about	O
them	O
its	O
cause	O
their	O
cute	O
together	O
and	O
they	O
are	O
perfect	O
together	O
!!	O
but	O
watch	O
out	O
for	O
Cheeto	B-person
and	O
Uno	B-person
!	O

At	O
this	O
time	O
when	O
the	O
internet	O
is	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
run	O
properly	O
,	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
{@Shivraj Singh Chouhan@}	B-person
wants	O
to	O
take	O
exam	O
!	O
When	O
RGPV	B-corporation
is	O
not	O
even	O
able	O
to	O
declare	O
the	O
result	O
properly	O
without	O
crashing	O
the	O
site	O
.	O
{@Dr. Ramesh Pokhriyal Nishank@}	B-person
{@Higher Education Department, MP@}	B-group
#	O
ExamsInCovidASuicide	O
#	O
SayNoToUGCGuidlines	O
{@Kamal Nath@}	B-person

S	O
U	O
N	O
D	O
A	O
Y	O
P	O
L	O
A	O
N	O
!	O
.	O
Match	B-event
Day	I-event
Live	I-event
{{USERNAME}}	O
Liverpool	B-group
Vs	I-group
Man	I-group
United	I-group
Come	O
through	O
!	O
We	O
gonna	O
have	O
a	O
good	O
time	O
@	O
The	B-location
Irish	I-location
Corner	I-location
Limited	I-location
{{URL}}	O

Thecollaroyboys	B-group
commented	O
on	O
the	O
post	O
,	O
UK-based	B-location
F1	B-event
teams	O
responding	O
to	O
shortage	O
of	O
ventilators	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
You	O
win	O
the	O
internet	O
.	O
Very	O
nice	O
work	O
.	O
-	O
{{URL}}	O

New	B-location
Mexico	I-location
tribes	B-group
play	B-event
catch	I-event
up	O
in	O
census	O
count	O
{{URL}}	O
vai	O
{{USERNAME}}	O

I	O
've	O
been	O
laying	O
in	O
bed	O
doing	O
nothing	O
for	O
years	O
but	O
several	O
months	O
ago	O
I	O
saw	O
{@Ricky Gervais@}	B-person
talking	O
about	O
his	O
{@Netflix@}	B-product
series	O
#	O
AfterLife	B-creative_work
and	O
I	O
watched	O
it	O
and	O
enjoyed	O
it	O
but	O
now	O
I	O
've	O
been	O
waiting	O
months	O
for	O
#	O
AfterLife2	B-creative_work
.	O
The	O
living	O
have	O
a	O
responsibility	O
to	O
keep	O
the	O
dead	O
entertained	O
.	O

U.S	B-corporation
.	O
Supreme	B-group
Court	I-group
Declines	O
To	O
Hear	O
Gun	B-event
Rights	I-event
Cases	I-event
{{URL}}	O
via	O
{@LEADERSHIP NEWS@}	B-product

DeAngelo	B-person
Hall	I-person
says	O
free	O
agent	O
Chris	B-person
Harris	I-person
of	O
the	O
Broncos	O
best	O
fit	O
would	O
be	O
with	O
the	O
Super	O
Bowl	O
Champion	O
Kansas	B-location
City	I-location
{@Kansas City Chiefs@}	B-group
hey	O
Veach	O
I	O
agree	O
!	O
That	O
makes	O
our	O
secondary	B-group
one	O
of	O
the	O
best	O
in	O
the	O
{@NFL@}	B-corporation

I	O
did	O
n't	O
expect	O
Anthony	B-person
Joshua	I-person
not	O
to	O
win	O
the	O
rematch	B-event
.	O
He	O
did	O
n't	O
lose	O
the	O
first	O
bout	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
the	O
commercial	O
side	O
of	O
boxing	B-group
.	O
Why	O
not	O
eat	O
your	O
cake	O
when	O
you	O
can	O
still	O
have	O
it	O
.	O
His	B-creative_work
fights	I-creative_work
become	O
costlier	O
as	O
a	O
two-time	O
champion	O
.	O
Congratulations	O
{{USERNAME}}	O

Landry	B-person
Jones	I-person
is	O
the	O
coldest	O
Houston	B-group
Roughneck	O
on	O
the	O
field	O
{{USERNAME}}	O

.	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
is	O
so	O
obsessed	O
with	O
oil	O
I	O
'm	O
worried	O
he	O
's	O
going	O
to	O
sharpie	O
up	O
a	O
map	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
Alberta	B-location
is	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
Montana	B-location
.	O
Perhaps	O
WE	O
should	O
put	O
up	O
a	O
wall	O
.	O

Hi	O
@	O
MostRequestLive	B-corporation
&	O
{@On Air Romeo@}	B-person
！	O
Could	O
you	O
play	O
"	O
#	O
ImitationRain	B-creative_work
"	O
by	O
Japanese	O
artist	O
#	O
SixTONES	B-group
This	O
song	O
was	O
first	O
week	O
#	O
1	O
on	O
the	O
Billboard	B-product
Japan	B-location
chart	O
✨	O
#	O
MostRequestedLive	O
SixTONES	B-group
-	O
Imitation	O
Rain	O
(	O
Music	O
Video	O
)	O
[	O
YouTube	O
Ver	O
.	O
]	O
{{URL}}	O
{@YouTube@}	B-product

Manchester	B-group
City	I-group
2	I-group
-	O
Real	B-group
Madrid	I-group
1	I-group
-	O
Champions	B-event
League	I-event
CC	I-event
{{USERNAME}}	O
{{URL}}	O

Trainer	O
Kevin	B-person
Attard	I-person
will	O
send	O
out	O
a	O
pair	B-product
of	I-product
runners	I-product
in	O
search	O
of	O
his	O
second	B-event
career	I-event
victory	I-event
in	O
today	O
’s	O
$	O
225,000	B-event
Cup	I-event
and	I-event
Saucer	I-event
Stakes	I-event
for	O
Canadian-bred	O
2-year-olds	O
over	O
1	O
1	O
/	O
16	O
miles	O
on	O
the	O
E.P	O
.	O
Taylor	B-location
turf	I-location
course	I-location
at	O
Woodbine	B-location
,	O
writes	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
{{URL}}	O

I	O
do	O
n’t	O
remember	O
the	O
question	O
..	O
.	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
{@Lamar Jackson@}	B-person
is	O
the	O
answer	O
#	O
Ravens	B-group

Family	O
that	O
Star	B-creative_work
Wars	I-creative_work
together	O
,	O
stays	O
together	O
!	O
Christmas	B-event
2019	I-event
!	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
{{URL}}	O

Peter	B-person
Hujar	I-person
:	O
the	O
legacy	O
,	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
loves	O
of	O
the	O
bohemian	O
photographer	O
(	O
via	O
our	O
friends	O
{@Dazed@}	B-corporation
)	O
(	O
Listen	O
to	O
the	O
full	O
talk	O
on	O
our	O
mixcloud	O
{{URL}}	O
{{URL}}	O

Nice	O
to	O
wake	O
up	O
to	O
another	O
#	O
stlblues	O
win	O
especially	O
against	O
the	O
Jets	B-group
and	O
the	O
Avs	B-group
also	O
losing	O
win	O
streak	O
now	O
at	O
7	O
this	O
team	O
is	O
flying	O
great	O
to	O
see	O
{@Tyler Bozak@}	B-person
with	O
two	O
goals	O
&	O
{@David Perron@}	B-person
with	O
the	O
winner	O
in	O
OT	B-event
#	O
LetsGoBlues	O

DJEFF	B-person
vs	O
Projeto	B-creative_work
Kaya	I-creative_work
-	O
Beija	B-creative_work
Flor	I-creative_work
,	O
Out	O
now	O
,	O
full	O
music	O
video	O
on	O
YouTube	B-corporation
{{USERNAME}}	O
#	O
projetokaya	B-person
#	O
wdbmanagement	B-group
#	O
kazukutarecords	B-group
{{URL}}	O

Reflections	O
from	O
our	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
staff	O
.	O
"	O
My	O
feelings	O
and	O
emotions	O
are	O
my	O
own	O
during	O
this	O
difficult	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
i	O
know	O
I	O
'm	O
not	O
alone	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
support	O
of	O
my	O
work	O
family	O
at	O
Prestons	B-location
.	O
We	O
are	O
all	O
in	O
this	O
together	O
"	O

MIRROR	O
.	O
{@Mirror Politics@}	B-corporation
:	O
"	O
Kanye	B-person
West	I-person
to	O
hold	O
campaign	B-event
rally	I-event
in	O
South	B-location
Carolina	I-location
as	O
he	O
pushes	O
presidency	B-creative_work
bid	I-creative_work
"	O
{{URL}}	O

Eid	B-event
Mubarak	I-event
{{USERNAME}}	O
Hope	O
you	O
are	O
having	O
a	O
beautiful	O
time	O
AT	O
HOME	O
with	O
YOUR	O
FAMILY	O
.	O

So	O
excited	O
to	O
welcome	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
back	O
to	O
Arizona	B-location
next	O
week	O
!	O
I	O
’ve	O
been	O
so	O
impressed	O
by	O
the	O
{@Students For Trump@}	B-group
in	O
AZ	B-location
and	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
president	O
will	O
be	O
too	O
!	O
{{URL}}	O

Happy	O
Mother	B-event
’s	I-event
Day	I-event
to	O
all	O
super	O
moms	O
out	O
there	O
especially	O
to	O
my	O
mother	O
!	O
You	O
’re	O
the	O
best	O
,	O
ILY	O
ILYMa	O
from	O
SB19xA'Tin	O
{@SB19 Official 🇵🇭@}	B-group
#	O
SB19	B-group

The	O
latest	O
from	O
{@Leonard Pitts, Jr.@}	B-person
:	O
{@Colin Kaepernick@}	B-person
once	O
knelt	O
—	O
remember	O
that	O
?	O
—	O
in	O
protest	O
of	O
police	O
brutality	O
just	O
like	O
this	O
.	O
Many	O
white	O
people	O
,	O
including	O
the	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
White	B-location
House	I-location
,	O
lost	O
their	O
minds	O
over	O
that	O
.	O
Do	O
not	O
expect	O
similar	O
outrage	O
here	O
.	O
{{URL}}	O

I	O
love	O
football	B-event
,	O
but	O
it	O
’s	O
so	O
hard	O
to	O
love	O
the	O
{@NFL@}	B-corporation
Watching	O
the	O
Aaron	B-person
Hernandez	I-person
doc	B-creative_work
it	O
makes	O
me	O
feel	O
complicit	O
.	O

South	B-location
African	I-location
President	O
Cyril	B-person
Ramaphosa	I-person
has	O
declared	O
a	O
national	O
state	O
Disaster	O
due	O
to	O
the	O
Corona	B-event
Virus.Imposed	I-event
travel	O
ban	O
on	O
Italy	B-location
,	O
Iran	B-location
,	I-location
Germany,Spain	I-location
,	O
South	B-location
Korea	I-location
,	O
China	B-location
,	O
US	B-location
,	O
UK	B-location
&	O
has	O
revoked	O
visas	O
issued	O
from	O
18th	B-event
of	I-event
March	I-event
.	O
{@Laolu Akande@}	B-person
{@Ministry of Interior@}	B-group
{@Fed Min of Info & Cu@}	B-group
{@Presidency | South Africa 🇿🇦@}	B-corporation

Women	B-group
's	O
Lacrosse	B-group
News	O
The	O
team	O
is	O
hosting	O
a	O
Playday	B-event
on	O
Saturday	O
!	O
Aquinas	B-group
,	O
Lawrence	B-group
Tech	I-group
&	I-group
Lewis	I-group
will	O
be	O
involved	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
the	O
full	O
schedule	O
for	O
the	O
day	O
.	O
DU	B-group
vs	O
AQ	B-group
at	O
9am	O
Lewis	B-group
vs	O
LTU	B-corporation
at	O
10:15	O
am	O
Lewis	B-group
vs	O
AQ	B-corporation
at	O
11:20	O
am	O
DU	B-corporation
vs	O
LTU	B-group
at	O
12:35	O
pm	O
DU	B-corporation
vs	O
Lewis	B-group
at	O
1:40	O
pm	O
{{USERNAME}}	O

Ranking	O
on	O
a	O
scale	O
of	O
1-10	O
how	O
much	O
each	O
of	O
{@Taylor Swift@}	B-person
’s	O
new	O
songs	O
hurts	O
our	O
feelings	O
while	O
laying	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
with	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
A	O
thread	O
:	O
1	O
.	O
the	O
1	O
-	O
11	O
/	O
10	O
The	O
lyrics	O
are	O
too	O
real	O
and	O
they	O
hurt	O
my	O
feelings	O
quite	O
a	O
lot	O
and	O
make	O
me	O
think	O
about	O
people	O
I	O
would	O
rather	O
forget	O
.	O

Dee	B-creative_work
Koala	I-creative_work
-	O
4	B-creative_work
The	I-creative_work
Khaltsha	I-creative_work
(	O
Official	O
Music	O
Video	O
)	O
ft	O
.	O
Lookatups	O
{{URL}}	O
via	O
@	O
ChaeYunEun	B-person
@	O
DeeKoala1	B-creative_work

I	O
am	O
Home	O
I	O
am	O
Safe	O
But	O
i	O
am	O
Hungry	O
...	O
.	O
Someone	O
should	O
please	O
help	O
{@Muhammadu Buhari@}	B-person
{@APC Nigeria@}	B-corporation
{@Official PDP Nigeria@}	B-group
{@Reno Omokri@}	B-person
{{USERNAME}}	O
{@BRIGHT STAR ⭐️⭐️⭐️⭐️⭐️⭐️⭐️@}	B-corporation
{@NCDC@}	B-corporation

Why	O
associate	O
no	O
bra	B-product
with	O
breast	B-event
cancer	I-event
awareness	O
,	O
does	O
wearing	O
bra	B-product
predispose	O
women	B-group
to	O
breast	B-event
cancer	I-event
{{USERNAME}}	O

CROWD	O
ROARS	O
for	O
President	B-person
Trump	I-person
at	O
UFC	B-corporation
244	I-corporation
-	O
Winner	O
Masvidal	B-person
Says	O
He	O
Was	O
Honored	O
to	O
Fight	O
in	O
Front	O
of	O
Trump	B-person
-	O
a	O
BMF	O
!	O
(	O
VIDEO	O
)	O
{{URL}}	O
via	O
{@Gab.com@}	B-product

Live	O
Updates	O
:	O
{@SIMBA..!🦁@}	B-group
On	O
Stage	O
Sierra	B-location
Leon	I-location
National	I-location
Stadium	I-location
..	O
.	O
sold	O
out	O
#	O
KillerMe	B-product
{{URL}}	O

Many	O
fab	O
authors	O
donating	O
signed	O
books	O
and	O
illos	O
to	O
support	O
#	O
cfa	O
through	O
Twitter	B-corporation
auctions	O
looking	O
forward	O
to	O
a	O
few	O
bids	O
tomorrow	O
!	O
#	O
AuthorsForFireys	B-event
Great	O
initiative	O
by	O
{{USERNAME}}	O

'	O
He	O
calls	O
us	O
out	O
by	O
name	O
and	O
invites	O
himself	O
to	O
move	O
in	O
'..	O
.	O
love	B-group
{{USERNAME}}	O
interpretation	O
of	O
the	O
biblical	O
story	O
of	O
Zacchaeus	B-person
,	O
the	O
tax	O
collector	O
who	O
He	O
(	O
Jesus	B-person
)	O
called	O
out	O
by	O
name	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
show	O
him	O
His	O
love	B-group
...#	O
mercy	B-group
#	O
love	B-group
#	O
grace	B-group
#	O
forgiveness	B-group

Random	O
Tweet	O
but	O
{@Wizkid@}	B-person
is	O
the	O
artist	O
of	O
the	O
decade	O
and	O
is	O
going	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
artist	O
of	O
the	O
next	O
decade	O
.	O
#	O
STARBOYFEST	B-event
#	O
StarboyFestLagos	B-event
#	O
Wizkidfc	O

End	O
of	O
the	O
third	O
quarter	O
vs	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
and	O
it	O
’s	O
24-5to	O
Chester	B-group
!!!	O
Looking	O
good	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
win	O
tonight	O
!	O
!	O

Oh	O
yeah	O
that	O
's	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
I	O
#	O
asked	O
Jo	B-person
back	O
in	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
which	O
is	O
many	O
#	O
yrs	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
#	O
now	O
was	O
he	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
#	O
too	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
and	O
he	O
#	O
replied	O
with	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
.	O
Oh	O
yeah	O
and	O
I	O
#	O
had	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
#	O
other	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
with	O
the	O
{@(RED)@}	B-corporation
#	O
hair	O
and	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
#	O
make	O
a	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
which	O
you	O
just	O
#	O
rode	O
on	O
the	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
bck	O
in	O
#	O
94	O
i	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
.	O

So	O
{@Kentucky Football@}	B-group
needs	O
a	O
new	O
offensive	O
strategy	O
.	O
These	O
screen	O
passes	O
are	O
not	O
getting	O
us	O
anywhere	O
!!	O
We	O
need	O
to	O
move	O
DOWN	O
the	O
field	O
.	O
Not	O
left	O
to	O
right	O
.	O
This	O
looks	O
to	O
be	O
another	O
one	O
of	O
those	O
“	O
basketball	O
season	O
is	O
just	O
around	O
the	O
corner	O
”	O
years	O
.	O
#	O
BBN	B-event
#	O
KentuckyFootball	B-group
#	O
Kentucky	B-location

I	O
’ll	O
always	O
remember	O
Chadwick	B-person
Boseman	I-person
.	O
For	O
{@MEL Magazine@}	B-product
I	O
wrote	O
about	O
the	O
life	O
and	O
legacy	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
behind	O
the	O
mask	O
.	O
{{URL}}	O

Join	O
me	O
at	O
GITEX	B-event
Technology	I-event
Week	I-event
from	O
October	O
6th-10th	O
in	O
Dubai	B-location
World	I-location
Trade	I-location
Center	I-location
,	I-location
UAE	I-location
.	O
It	O
would	O
be	O
great	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
there	O
.	O
{{URL}}	O
{@GITEX Technology Week@}	B-event
#	O
GITEX2019	O

Really	O
good	O
piece	O
on	O
{@Birds of Prey@}	B-creative_work
,	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
it	O
last	O
night	O
and	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
best	O
films	O
I	O
'd	O
seen	O
in	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
.	O
Please	O
go	O
watch	O
it	O
!	O
{{URL}}	O

The	O
beauty	O
of	O
#	O
DTLA	B-corporation
shot	O
by	O
{@Chris Cristi@}	B-person
right	O
now	O
is	O
just	O
breathtaking	O
.	O
Please	O
stop	O
the	O
today	B-event
’s	O
insanity	B-event
and	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
our	O
city	O
.	O

I	O
'm	O
at	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
for	O
Star	B-creative_work
Wars	I-creative_work
:	O
The	B-creative_work
Rise	I-creative_work
Of	I-creative_work
Skywalker	I-creative_work
in	O
Greenville	B-location
,	O
SC	B-location
{{URL}}	O

Join	O
{@Mark Zinno@}	B-person
and	O
myself	O
as	O
we	O
broadcast	O
live	O
from	O
Life	B-location
University	I-location
this	O
afternoon	O
from	O
noon	O
to	O
three	O
.	O
Few	O
things	O
we	O
’ll	O
get	O
to	O
..	O
.	O
Did	O
Zinno	B-person
make	O
money	O
off	O
the	O
XFL	B-event
yesterday	O
?	O
Kevin	B-person
Durant	I-person
is	O
still	O
soft	O
.	O
Zinno	B-person
on	O
the	O
Red	B-event
Carpet	I-event
National	I-event
Signing	I-event
Day	I-event
{@680 The Fan@}	B-creative_work

Q	O
from	O
{@Peter Alexander@}	B-person
:	O
Why	O
did	O
President	B-person
Trump	I-person
say	O
he	O
made	O
Juneteenth	O
famous	O
and	O
that	O
no	O
one	O
knew	O
about	O
it	O
when	O
millions	O
of	O
black	O
people	O
commemorate	O
it	O
every	O
year	O
?	O
{@Jen Psaki@}	B-person
:	O
There	O
were	O
a	O
lot	O
of	O
people	O
who	O
did	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
Juneteenth	O
was	O
based	O
on	O
Google	B-corporation
searches	O
.	O

TIL	O
,	O
in	O
addition	O
to	O
speeding	O
up	O
playback	O
,	O
you	O
can	O
slow	O
down	O
playback	O
on	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
Libby	B-product
to	O
.	O
6x	O
!	O
Perfect	O
for	O
listening	O
to	O
Harry	B-creative_work
Potter	I-creative_work
y	O
la	O
piedra	O
filosofal	O
while	O
I	O
keep	O
trying	O
to	O
learn	O
Spanish	O
#	O
HarryPotterAtHome	O
{{URL}}	O

Ohhh	O
my	O
!	O
August	B-person
Alsina	I-person
really	O
turned	O
this	O
whole	O
mess	O
with	O
Jada	B-person
Smith	I-person
around	O
with	O
this	O
hot	O
track	O
#	O
Entanglement	B-creative_work
featuring	O
Rick	B-person
Ross	I-person
.	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
I	O
told	O
you	O
,	O
man	O
.	O
You	O
gotta	O
listen	O
to	O
that	O
track	O
,	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
promise	O
you	O
wo	O
n't	O
regret	O
it	O
.	O

8:00am	O
this	O
morning	O
;	O
second	O
Gold	B-event
Bracket	I-event
game	O
.	O
Please	O
watch	B-event
us	I-event
on	I-event
{{USERNAME}}	O
“	O
VA	B-creative_work
Glory	I-creative_work
14u	I-creative_work
Johnson-Avvisato	I-creative_work
.	O
”	O
Team	O
#	O
is	O
"	O
004322	O
.	O
"	O

Wait	O
it	O
is	O
n't	O
main	O
event	O
time	O
already	O
is	O
it	O
?	O
{@WWE@}	B-corporation
#	O
NXTTakeoverWarGames	B-event

HAPPY	O
NEW	B-event
YEAR	I-event
!	O
2020	B-event
!	O
Starting	O
the	O
decade	O
with	O
some	O
#	O
FortniteBattleRoyale	B-creative_work
,	O
then	O
switching	O
to	O
more	O
Sevtech	B-corporation
!	O
#	O
Minecraft	B-creative_work
{@Twitch@}	B-product
{{URL}}	O

*	O
Fixes	O
headline	O
"	O
Man	O
merely	O
being	O
detained	O
by	O
a	O
FAMILY	O
MEMBER	O
,	O
is	O
QUICKLY	O
RELEASED	O
,	O
UNHARMED	O
,	O
for	O
violating	O
the	O
law	O
and	O
encroaching	O
on	O
a	O
beach	O
in	O
San	B-location
Diego	I-location
.	O
Did	O
this	O
happen	O
to	O
FBA	B-corporation
in	O
Florida	B-location
?	O
#	O
FirstThem	O
{{URL}}	O
{@Tariq Nasheed 🇺🇸@}	B-person

I	O
want	O
to	O
give	O
{@Alison Hammond@}	B-person
a	O
hug	O
.	O
She	O
's	O
right	O
,	O
of	O
course	O
'	O
all	O
lives	O
matter	O
'	O
but	O
right	O
now	O
we	O
are	O
talking	O
about	O
black	B-group
lives	I-group
matter	I-group
.	O
Because	O
it	O
seems	O
like	O
black	B-group
lives	I-group
do	O
n't	O
matter	O
to	O
a	O
lot	O
of	O
people	O
.	O
Use	O
your	O
voice	O
,	O
speak	O
up	O
,	O
sign	O
petitions	O
and	O
donate	O
.	O
❤	O

"	O
It	O
was	O
horrible	O
out	O
there	O
.	O
"	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
and	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
'	O
s	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
Premier	B-event
League	I-event
match	I-event
was	O
this	O
afternoon	O
called	O
off	O
early	O
due	O
to	O
poor	O
weather	O
conditions	O
.	O
It	O
's	O
understood	O
the	O
game	O
will	O
be	O
completed	O
at	O
a	O
later	O
date	O
.	O
Story	O
:	O
{@Josh Bartlett@}	B-person
{{URL}}	O

Trump	B-person
’s	O
State	B-event
of	I-event
the	I-event
Union	I-event
Address	I-event
shamelessly	O
falsifies	O
facts	O
on	O
US	B-location
economy	O
{{URL}}	O
via	O
{{USERNAME}}	O

Stormy	B-person
Faye	I-person
The	O
Christian	O
Runaway	O
Answer	O
your	O
calling	O
.	O
"	O
Before	O
GOD	O
ever	O
made	O
a	O
woman	O
,	O
He	O
gave	O
Adam	O
a	O
calling	O
.	O
"	O
–	B-person
Dr	I-person
.	O
Tony	B-person
Evans	I-person
#	O
QITD	O
#	O
TonyEvans	O
drtonyevans	O
#	O
FaithForTheJourney	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
{{URL}}	O
{{URL}}	O

I	O
can	O
imagine	O
#	O
GOP	B-group
discrediting	O
whistleblower	O
report	O
of	O
#	O
Trump	B-person
extorting	O
Ukraine	B-location
as	O
"	O
hearsay	O
"	O
coming	O
from	O
a	O
{@Frank Luntz@}	B-person
focus	O
group	O
indicating	O
Trumpers	B-group
interpret	O
it	O
as	O
"	O
rumor	O
.	O
"	O
Akin	O
to	O
dismissers	O
of	O
Climate	O
Change	O
as	O
mere	O
"	O
theory	O
,"	O
because	O
many	O
Fox	B-corporation
News	I-corporation
watchers	O
hear	O
"	O
hypothesis	O
"	O

Lakers	B-group
up	O
30-26	O
on	O
New	B-group
Orleans	I-group
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
quarter	O
.	O
Earlier	O
today	O
,	O
{@Sam Amick@}	B-person
made	O
the	O
case	O
for	O
the	O
Pelicans	B-group
as	O
the	O
Lakers	B-group
most	O
likely	O
first	O
round	O
opponent	O
(	O
and	O
why	O
the	O
league	O
would	O
love	O
it	O
)	O
.	O
{{URL}}	O

on	O
{@YouTube@}	B-product
:	O
New	B-creative_work
York	I-creative_work
Giants	I-creative_work
name	B-event
Daniel	B-person
Jones	I-person
week	O
3	O
starter	O
vs	O
Tampa	B-group
Bay	I-group
Bucs	I-group
!	O
Eli	B-person
Mannings	I-person
goes	O
to	O
bench	O
{{URL}}	O

Jacinda	B-person
Ardern	I-person
said	O
today	O
that	O
the	O
Government	B-corporation
and	O
the	O
police	B-corporation
can	O
enforce	O
self-isolation	O
.	O
Example	O
the	O
Denmark	B-location
lady	O
who	O
caught	O
flight	O
from	O
Auckland	B-location
to	O
Christchurch	B-location
&	O
tested	O
positive	O
,	O
people	O
need	O
to	O
be	O
sensible	O
{@Jacinda Ardern@}	B-person
{@NZ National Party@}	B-group
#	O
COVID2019	B-product
is	O
not	O
a	O
joke	O

A	O
massive	O
congratulations	O
to	O
{@TYSON FURY@}	B-person
-	O
After	O
watching	O
the	O
documentary	O
on	O
him	O
this	O
bloke	O
is	O
an	O
absolute	O
inspiration	O
to	O
those	O
fighting	O
another	O
fight	O
called	O
‘	O
mental	O
health’	O
the	O
perfect	O
family	O
man	O
and	O
has	O
since	O
become	O
my	O
hero	O
-	O
#	O
tysonfurythegypsyking	O

so	O
i	O
finished	O
watching	O
#	O
JaneTheVirgin	B-creative_work
the	O
other	O
day	O
and	O
hands	O
down	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
in	O
my	O
top	O
five	O
/	O
top	O
ten	O
of	O
best	O
television	O
shows	O
of	O
all	O
time	O
.	O
{@JaneTheVirginWriters@}	B-group

.	O
.	O
could	O
not	O
hold	O
in	O
Ekiti	B-location
State	I-location
as	O
the	O
lockdown	O
order	O
issued	O
by	O
the	O
state	B-person
governor	I-person
,	O
Kayode	B-person
Fayemi	I-person
was	O
fully	O
enforced	O
.	O
Even	O
the	O
food	O
markets	O
earlier	O
allowed	O
were	O
not	O
spared	O
today	O
as	O
the	O
security	O
personnel	O
set	O
some	O
foodstuffs	O
on	O
fire	O
...(	O
see	O
our	O
country	O
{{USERNAME}}	O

"...	O
.	O
Why	O
then	O
,	O
is	O
it	O
such	O
a	O
jump	O
from	O
that	O
to	O
think	O
that	O
systemic	O
racism	O
has	O
n’t	O
been	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
fabric	B-product
of	O
the	O
United	B-location
States	I-location
since	O
its	O
inception	O
?	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
our	O
fabric	B-product
and	O
it	O
is	O
being	O
taught	O
on	O
purpose	O
by	O
those	O
in	O
power	O
.	O
"	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
#	O
Racism	O
{{URL}}	O

Waking	O
up	O
this	O
sunday	O
morning	O
with	O
a	O
new	O
song	O
by	O
{@Harry Styles.@}	B-person
.	O
"	O
Watermelon	B-creative_work
Sugar	I-creative_work
"	O
is	O
amazing	O
!	O
This	O
new	O
album	B-creative_work
is	O
catching	O
my	O
attention	O
and	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
wait	O
to	O
hear	O
the	O
new	O
tracks	O
.	O

Lucas	B-person
the	I-person
Spider	I-person
and	O
His	O
Friend	O
the	B-person
Fly	I-person
Try	O
to	O
Understand	O
Why	O
Red	O
Leaves	O
Are	O
Falling	O
Off	O
of	O
Trees	O
{{URL}}	O
via	O
{@Laughing Squid@}	B-person

.	O
{@Ariana Grande@}	B-person
i	O
love	O
you	O
so	O
much	O
pls	O
lemme	O
have	O
your	O
hand	O
in	O
marriage	B-event

i	O
love	O
you	O
so	O
much	O
.	O
i	O
wo	O
n’t	O
ever	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
thank	O
you	O
for	O
everything	O
that	O
you	O
’ve	O
ever	O
done	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
&	O
all	O
the	O
courage	O
you	O
’ve	O
given	O
me	O
,	O
it	O
means	O
more	O
than	O
you	O
will	O
ever	O
know	O
.	O
{@Harry Styles.@}	B-person

I	O
always	O
put	O
on	O
some	O
{@Wale@}	B-person
an	O
{@J. Cole@}	B-person
when	O
im	O
doing	O
up	O
spring	O
clean	O
.	O
But	O
always	O
end	O
up	O
having	O
to	O
sit	O
down	O
and	O
recover	O
from	O
the	O
way	O
the	O
lyrics	O
hit	O
different	O

{{URL}}	O
An	O
amazing	O
projet	O
I	O
am	O
glad	O
I	O
participated	O
to	O
at	O
the	O
start	O
of	O
Lockdown	B-event
,	O
so	O
great	O
to	O
see	O
it	O
released	O
!	O
Thank	O
you	O
so	O
much	O
{@Eric Whitacre@}	B-person
for	O
guiding	O
this	O
project	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
singers	O
for	O
creating	O
such	O
a	O
gorgeous	O
musical	O
piece	O
!	O

guys	O
guys	O
guys	O
im	O
live	O
!!	O
Thank	O
God	O
It	O
’s	O
Winter	B-event
Break	I-event
gaming	O
with	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
{{URL}}	O

1	O
/	O
{@Dr. Abdul El-Sayed@}	B-person
-	O
“	O
In	O
most	O
circumstances	O
,	O
public	B-creative_work
health	I-creative_work
professionals	I-creative_work
are	O
trained	O
to	O
just	O
interpret	O
the	O
science	O
,	O
and	O
develop	O
a	O
message	O
that	O
is	O
true	O
to	O
the	O
science	O
.	O
Because	O
we	O
take	O
it	O
for	O
granted	O
that	O
politicians	O
are	O
going	O
to	O
do	O
what	O
’s	O
right	O
based	O
on	O
that	O
science	O
.	O

Boooooooommmm	O
!!	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
reference	O
alert	O
!!!	O
RFC	O
2396	B-product
is	O
an	O
update	B-event
"	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
define	O
a	O
single	O
,	O
generic	O
syntax	O
for	O
all	O
URI	O
(	O
Uniform	O
Resource	O
Identifiers	O
)"	O
from	O
the	O
Internet	B-group
Engineering	I-group
Task	I-group
Force	I-group
.	O
{{URL}}	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
{{USERNAME}}	O

1-1	O
between	O
the	O
Storm	B-group
and	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
at	O
the	O
first	O
period	O
media	O
timeout	O
.	O
Jirousek	B-person
on	O
the	O
PP	O
has	O
the	O
goal	O
for	O
GP	B-group
#	O
WeAreTheStorm	B-group

POP	B-corporation
SMOKE	I-corporation
-	O
CHRISTOPHER	B-corporation
WALKING	I-corporation
(	O
Official	O
Lyric	O
Video	O
)	O
{{URL}}	O
via	O
{@YouTube@}	B-product
ayyyeeee	O

Remember	B-creative_work
Your	I-creative_work
True	I-creative_work
Nature	I-creative_work
:	O
Icaro	B-creative_work
(	O
healing	O
song	O
)	O
{{URL}}	O
{@YouTube@}	B-product

I	O
hold	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
and	O
his	O
tribe	B-group
completely	O
responsible	O
for	O
introducing	O
me	O
to	O
Tiger	B-creative_work
King	I-creative_work
via	O
their	O
tweets	B-creative_work
.	O

Disturbed	B-group
-	O
The	B-creative_work
Sound	I-creative_work
Of	I-creative_work
Silence	I-creative_work
[	O
Official	O
Music	O
Video	O
]	O
{{URL}}	O
via	O
{@YouTube@}	B-product
{{USERNAME}}	O
More	O
suited	O
to	O
your	O
'	O
gentle	O
sensibilities'	O
perhaps	O
?	O
Enjoy	O
and	O
Happy	O
Sunday	O
.	O

Happy	B-event
Pride	I-event
everyone	O
!	O
Going	O
LIVE	O
on	O
Human	B-creative_work
Nature	I-creative_work
in	O
T-2	O
hours	O
4pm	O
NYC	B-location
on	O
twitch	B-corporation
!	O
in	O
bio	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
@	O
Miami	B-location
Beach	I-location
,	I-location
Florida	I-location
{{URL}}	O

The	O
Alejandro	B-person
’s	O
(	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
)	O
had	O
their	O
baby	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
.	O
The	O
Trout	B-person
’s	O
(	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
{@Mike Trout@}	B-person
)	O
had	O
they	O
baby	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
.	O
The	O
Bella	O
Twins	O
(	O
{@Nikki & Brie@}	B-person
)	O
each	O
had	O
theirs	O
on	O
31st	O
and	O
the	O
1st	O
.	O
Congratulations	O
to	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
babies	O
destined	O
to	O
do	O
great	O
things	O
.	O

Uh	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
,	B-person
Pence	I-person
said	O
he	O
was	O
looking	O
for	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
White	B-location
House	I-location
bedroom	O
.	O

Watch	O
{@WWL-TV@}	B-creative_work
,	O
s	O
broadcast	O
:	O
Watch	B-event
live	I-event
:	O
Tropical	B-event
Storm	I-event
Cristobal	I-event
coming	O
ashore	O
in	O
Louisiana	B-location
,	O
Gulf	B-location
Coast	I-location
:	O
{{URL}}	O
{{URL}}	O

Time	O
to	O
revisit	B-event
Climate	I-event
change	I-event
and	O
the	O
75	O
%	O
problem	O
{{URL}}	O
via	O
{@Bill Gates@}	B-person

.	O
{@Frost & Sullivan@}	B-corporation
exclusive	O
with	O
Waheed	B-person
Abbas	I-person
:	O
"	O
UAE	B-location
used	O
#	O
cars	O
wo	O
n't	O
take	O
a	O
brake	O
"	O
.	O
SUVs	B-product
are	O
expected	O
to	O
account	O
for	O
50	O
per	O
cent	O
of	O
the	O
market	O
,	O
reflecting	O
changes	O
in	O
consumers'	O
preferences	O
going	O
forward	O
.	O
​	O
More	O
#	O
insights	O
via	O
{@Khaleej Times@}	B-product
:	O
#	O
UAE	B-location
#	O
usedcars	O
{{URL}}	O

Did	O
you	O
experience	O
any	O
Internet	O
outages	O
this	O
morning	O
?	O
{@CenturyLink@}	B-corporation
says	O
they	O
should	O
be	O
fixed	O
.	O
{{URL}}	O

UFC	B-event
249	I-event
PPV	I-event
starts	O
in	O
minutes	O
!!	O
Life	O
is	O
good	O
!!	O
{@UFC@}	B-group
#	O
ufc249	B-event

Hard	O
to	O
believe	O
that	O
I	O
'm	O
about	O
to	O
leave	O
for	O
the	O
last	O
{@All Time Low@}	B-group
show	O
of	O
the	O
decade	O
about	O
to	O
be	O
fully	O
in	O
my	O
feelings	O
the	O
whole	O
night	O
(	O
or	O
at	O
least	O
more	O
so	O
than	O
usual	O
)	O

"	O
In	O
theory	O
"	O
Fall	B-creative_work
From	I-creative_work
Grace	I-creative_work
Was	O
For	O
A	O
targeted	O
audience	O
just	O
like	O
any	O
other	O
movie	O
.	O
I	O
likes	O
it	O
.	O
Waiting	O
for	O
the	O
next	O
one	O
.	O
{@Tyler Perry@}	B-person

Finishing	O
With	O
the	O
Fire	O
on	O
High	O
/	O
Reading	O
Rush	O
Day	O
6	O
Vlog	O
{{URL}}	O
via	O
{@YouTube@}	B-product
{{USERNAME}}	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
{{USERNAME}}	O

Grassley	B-person
chides	O
Trump	B-person
,	O
Fox	B-corporation
News	I-corporation
for	O
answer	O
on	O
second-term	O
agenda	O
{{URL}}	O
via	O
{@POLITICO@}	B-product

ThePrint	B-product
reporters	I-product
hit	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
.	O
Modi	B-person
wants	O
to	O
double	O
farmers’	O
income	O
by	O
2022	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
is	O
only	O
their	O
debt	O
that	O
’s	O
growing	O
Continuing	O
the	O
series	O
on	O
Econ	O
distress	O
from	O
UP	B-location
,	O
Bihar	B-location
by	O
{@Sanya Dhingra@}	B-person
&	O
{@Praveen Jain@}	B-person
#	O
RuralIndiaInCrisis	B-event
{{URL}}	O

Nigeria	B-location
trends	O
follow	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
for	O
insight	O
(	O
Bottom	O
10	O
)	O
#	O
OrijinalOwambe	B-person
Guardiola	B-event
Brighto	I-event
World	I-event
Cup	I-event
Tolanibaj	B-person
Laycon	I-person
yakubu	I-person
Tbaj	I-person
Man	B-group
City	I-group
Ligue	I-group
View	O
Google	O
searches	O
trend	O
insight	O
{{URL}}	O

Reflecting	O
on	O
our	O
last	O
game	B-event
of	O
the	O
decade	O
,	O
a	O
huge	O
road	O
win	O
at	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
and	O
previewing	O
the	O
first	O
game	B-event
of	O
the	O
new	O
decade	O
there	O
was	O
really	O
only	O
one	O
man	O
to	O
talk	O
to	O
,	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
.	O
{{URL}}	O

Purdue	B-corporation
University	I-corporation
researchers	O
find	O
link	O
between	O
herbicides	O
and	O
breast	O
cancer	O
{{URL}}	O
via	O
{{USERNAME}}	O

I	O
keep	O
hearing	O
about	O
Baylor	B-person
Scott	I-person
&	O
White	B-person
clinics	O
sending	O
huge	O
out	O
of	O
network	O
bills	O
..	O
.	O
this	O
is	O
exactly	O
why	O
we	O
need	O
Medicare	B-product
For	O
All	O
and	O
.	O
{@Elizabeth Warren@}	B-person
will	O
lead	O
that	O
fight	O
as	O
President	O
..	O
.	O
the	O
#	O
BlueTsunami2020	O
will	O
finally	O
flip	O
the	O
Senate	O
#	O
UnrigTheSystem	O
{{URL}}	O

repost	O
via	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
from	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
Jesus	B-person
died	O
to	O
rescue	O
us	O
from	O
our	O
sins	O
and	O
reconcile	O
us	O
with	O
God	O
.	O
He	O
rose	O
from	O
the	O
grave	O
and	O
is	O
alive	O
!⁣	O
⁣	O
#	O
ourdailybread	O
#	O
resurrectionsunday	B-event
#	O
resurrection	O
#	O
greifoverturned	O
…	O
{{URL}}	O

The	O
sound	O
clash	O
between	O
Beenie	B-person
Man	I-person
vs	O
Bounty	B-corporation
Killer	I-corporation
was	O
epic	O
!	O
There	O
were	O
three	O
winners	O
last	O
night	O
,	O
Beenie	B-person
Man	I-person
,	O
Bounty	B-person
Killer	I-person
and	O
everyone	O
in	O
attendance	O
!	O
Thank	O
you	O
to	O
{@SWIZZ BEATZ@}	B-person
{@Timbaland@}	B-person
{@VERZUZ@}	B-product
for	O
…	O
{{URL}}	O

//@	O
JustANormalMax	B-person
_	I-person
bronhdhfnd	I-person
are	O
you	O
awake	O
or	O
not	O
i	O
’m	O
scared	O
uh	O
like	O
i	O
’ve	O
been	O
up	O
for	O
20	O
minutes	O
i	O
’m	O
just	O
sitting	O
on	O
ur	O
bed	O
i	O
’m	O
scared	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
there	O
lmAO	O
UHHH	O

The	O
doors	O
are	O
officially	O
open	O
NOW	O
!!	O
Come	O
say	O
hi	O
and	O
show	O
him	O
some	O
love	O
to	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
,	O
maybe	O
help	O
us	O
with	O
a	O
follow	O
.	O
Making	O
the	O
world	O
a	O
better	O
place	O
1	O
stream	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
.	O
{{URL}}	O
#	O
Twitch	B-corporation
#	O
twitchaffiliate	O
#	O
SmallStreamerCommunity	B-group
#	O
SmallStreamersConnect	B-group
#	O
theducks	O
#	O
bighew	O

Great	O
to	O
see	O
our	O
President	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
at	O
the	O
great	O
American	B-group
race	O
!!	O
!	O

Japan	B-location
's	O
new	O
environment	O
minister	O
,	O
Shinjiro	B-person
Koizumi	I-person
,	I-person
pledged	O
on	O
Sunday	O
to	O
mobilise	O
young	O
people	O
to	O
push	O
his	O
coal-dependent	O
country	O
towards	O
a	O
low-carbon	O
future	O
by	O
making	O
the	O
fight	O
against	O
climate	O
change	O
"	O
sexy	O
"	O
and	O
"	O
fun	O
"	O
.	O
{@The Independent@}	B-corporation
{{URL}}	O

The	O
launch	B-event
of	O
the	O
2	O
astronauts	B-person
into	O
space	B-location
is	O
a	O
great	O
moment	O
.	O
Too	O
bad	O
it	O
came	O
when	O
the	O
country	O
was	O
in	O
deep	O
crisis	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
darkness	O
,	O
we	O
all	O
look	O
for	O
light	O
-	O
perhaps	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
turn	O
for	O
the	O
better	O
for	O
us	O
all	O
.	O
{@NASA@}	B-corporation
{@SpaceX@}	B-corporation

I	O
'll	O
laughing	O
so	O
hard	O
if	O
SJ	B-group
label	I-group
release	O
a	O
teaser	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
full	O
film	O
jacket	O
in	O
the	O
midday	O
,	O
and	O
MV	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
please	O
do	O
n't	O
let	O
my	O
imagination	O
come	O
true	O
{@SUPER JUNIOR@}	B-group

Reporters	O
,	O
stop	O
talking	O
about	O
the	O
“	O
war	B-event
on	I-event
cars	I-event
”	O
and	O
start	O
reading	O
.	O
{{URL}}	O
{@New York Post@}	B-product
{@New York Daily News@}	B-corporation
{@The New York Times@}	B-product
Do	O
your	O
job	O
.	O

1	O
/	O
n	O
{@PMO India@}	B-person
India	B-location
should	O
act	O
fast	O
.	O
Just	O
quarantining	O
the	O
infected	O
wont	O
help	O
.	O
Extensive	O
social	O
distancing	O
is	O
the	O
need	O
of	O
the	O
hour	O
#	O
COVID19india	O
#	O
coronavirusindia	O
#	O
COVID19	B-event

I	O
would	O
love	O
to	O
stay	O
at	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
in	O
Calgary	B-location
!	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
win	O
{@Linda Hoang 💕 Cẩm Tú (She/Her)@}	B-person
’s	O
stay	O
+dine	O
giveaway	B-event
!	O
The	O
hotel	O
has	O
a	O
year-round	O
,	O
outdoor	O
heated	O
pool	O
,	O
a	O
bunch	O
of	O
restaurants	O
,	O
and	O
nice	O
rooms	O
!	O
Great	O
hotel	O
for	O
my	O
#	O
CaptureCalgary	O
adventures	O
.	O
{{URL}}	O
#	O
yyc	O
#	O
explorealberta	O

Also	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
’m	O
here	O
Twitter	B-corporation
,	O
Christmas	B-event
is	O
fast	O
approaching	O
....	O
.	O
I	O
really	O
want	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
{@Wells Fargo@}	B-corporation
is	O
the	O
worst	O
banking	O
institution	O
and	O
every	O
thing	O
the	O
news	O
has	O
been	O
reporting	O
about	O
them	O
I	O
truly	O
believe	O
now	O
.	O
Worst	O
customer	O
service	O
.	O

Nextdoor	B-corporation
is	O
the	O
social	O
network	O
for	O
neighbours	O
.	O
Can	O
it	O
make	O
the	O
internet	O
a	O
kinder	O
,	O
gentler	O
place	O
?	O
via	O
{@The Globe and Mail@}	B-product
{{URL}}	O

Dr	O
.	O
{@Dr. Edsel Salvana@}	B-person
,	O
Please	O
tell	O
us	O
more	O
why	O
we	O
should	O
n't	O
do	O
more	O
testing	O
..	O
.	O
And	O
Why	O
were	O
doing	O
better	O
than	O
SG	B-group
..	O
.	O
But	O
let	O
's	O
drop	O
Vietnam	B-location
because	O
it	O
's	O
hard	O
to	O
defend	O
that	O
..	O
.	O
You	O
're	O
the	O
best	O
Doc	O
!!	O
!	O

The	O
baddest	O
is	O
back	O
!	O
{@Da Prettiest@}	B-person
Shares	O
Bar	O
Heavy	O
New	O
Album	O
'	O
Fight	B-creative_work
Night	I-creative_work
'	O
featuring	O
{@MollyBrazy@}	B-person
{@NLE Choppa@}	B-person
{@Yung Mal@}	B-person
and	O
{@BLEU@}	B-person
{{URL}}	O

#	O
Win	O
a	O
LEGO	B-corporation
Stationery	O
Prize	O
Pk	O
!	O
The	O
8-pack	O
brick-shaped	O
erasers	O
are	O
fun	O
for	O
LEGO	B-corporation
lovers	O
,	O
student	O
's	O
school	O
supplies	O
,	O
a	O
nostalgic	O
desk	O
statement	O
at	O
the	O
office	O
,	O
or	O
just	O
a	O
creative	O
and	O
colorful	O
way	O
to	O
erase	O
mistakes	O
!	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
Can	O
6	O
/	O
19	O
{{URL}}	O
#	O
afol	O

#शिक्षाविभाग_	O
alotdistrict	B-location
_	O
rankwise	O
Please	O
help	O
Sir	O
{@Arvind Sharma@}	B-person
!	O
All	O
seats	O
given	O
to	O
female	O
candidates	O
.	O
We	O
work	O
hard	O
to	O
get	O
marks	O
and	O
rank	O
.	O
#शिक्षाविभाग_	O
alotdistrict	B-location
_	O
rankwise	O
@	O
Upenyadav75	O
{@Ashok Gehlot@}	B-person
{@ZEE Rajasthan@}	B-person
{@Govind Singh Dotasra@}	B-person
{@CMO Rajasthan@}	B-person

#	O
AD	B-creative_work
Enter	I-creative_work
to	O
win	O
the	O
Cat	B-creative_work
in	I-creative_work
My	I-creative_work
Pocket	I-creative_work
Embroidery	I-creative_work
Ten	I-creative_work
Purrfect	I-creative_work
Projects	I-creative_work
Book	I-creative_work
by	O
Hiroko	B-person
Kubota	I-person
from	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
on	O
#	O
TwoClassyChics	B-event
Blog	O
Ends	O
8-03	O
#	O
Giveaway	O
#	O
Books	O
#	O
crafts	O
//	O
{{URL}}	O

Remember	O
when	O
{@Cleveland Browns@}	B-group
fans	O
thought	O
Baker	B-person
Mayfield	I-person
was	O
gonna	O
be	O
the	O
Browns	B-group
savior	O
???	O
?	O

Giving	O
up	O
is	O
Not	O
in	O
THALA	B-person
Fans	I-person
Bloods	I-person
❤	O
Halwa	B-location
City	I-location
I	O
'd	O
Again	O
Back	O
to	O
Bang	O
on	O
Twitter	B-corporation
.	O
Follow	O
and	O
Support	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
Valimai	O
|	O
#	O
ThalaAjith	B-person

#	O
Pawcircle	B-corporation
surrounds	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
hudad	B-creative_work
with	O
#	O
LoveAndStrength	O
Got	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
break	O
from	O
treatments	O
and	O
just	O
had	O
scans	O
.	O
Still	O
waiting	O
on	O
test	O
results	O
.	O
Keep	O
up	O
those	O
good	O
thoughts	O
!	O

Greta	B-person
Thunberg	I-person
-	O
Inspiring	O
Others	O
to	O
Take	O
a	O
Stand	O
Against	O
Climate	B-event
Change	I-event
..	O
.	O
{{URL}}	O
via	O
{@YouTube@}	B-product
#	O
GretaThurnberg	B-person

I	O
always	O
get	O
reflective	O
on	O
my	O
b'day	O
.	O
It	O
's	O
the	O
perfect	O
day	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
contemplate	O
how	O
lucky	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
have	O
such	O
wonderful	O
people	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Thank	O
you	O
all	O
for	O
your	O
love	O
and	O
support	O
.	O
I	O
love	O
you	O
all	O
.	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
{@ANGELA WHITE@}	B-person
{{USERNAME}}	O
@	O
BrooklynSnowXXX	B-person

These	O
refs	O
need	O
to	O
apologize	O
to	O
{@Carolina Basketball@}	B-group
these	O
dudes	O
work	O
to	O
hard	O
each	O
day	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
officials	O
decide	O
the	O
game	O
like	O
that	O
.	O
{@Damian Lillard@}	B-person
said	O
it	O
last	O
night	O
,	O
someone	O
needs	O
to	O
hold	O
the	O
refs	O
accountable	O
,	O
they	O
should	O
be	O
fined	O
,	O
or	O
not	O
be	O
given	O
these	O
type	O
of	O
games	O
.	O

The	O
reporters	O
at	O
the	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
have	O
done	O
a	O
beautiful	O
job	O
covering	O
how	O
people	O
of	O
faith	O
in	O
Dubuque	B-location
have	O
been	O
observing	O
their	O
holidays	O
in	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
COVID	O
.	O
This	O
look	O
into	O
the	O
Kassas	B-group
family	I-group
as	O
they	O
broke	O
their	O
fast	O
was	O
stunning	O
:	O
{{URL}}	O
#	O
ProudSubscriber	O

The	O
staff	O
at	O
Lydney	B-location
hospital	I-location
are	O
very	O
grateful	O
to	O
{@Tesco@}	B-corporation
Lydney	B-person
for	O
allowing	O
us	O
to	O
shop	O
and	O
our	O
beautiful	O
flowers	O
along	O
with	O
everything	O
else	O
you	O
support	O
us	O
with	O
throughout	O
the	O
year	O

Happy	O
Pride	B-event
{{USERNAME}}	O
!	O
Thank	O
you	O
for	O
continuing	O
to	O
discriminate	O
against	O
the	O
LGBTQ	B-group
community	I-group
.	O
#	O
translivesarehumanlives	O
#	O
translivesmatter	O
#	O
transrightsarehumanrights	O
#	O
pride	O
{{URL}}	O

Respected	O
sir	O
In	O
indore	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
private	O
software	O
companies	O
are	O
still	O
open	O
and	O
their	O
are	O
not	O
providing	O
work	O
from	O
home	O
facilities	O
and	O
even	O
they	O
have	O
employees	O
which	O
are	O
returned	O
from	O
Japan	B-location
kindily	O
plz	O
check	O
.	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
{@Ministry of Health@}	B-corporation

Hi	O
{@Maldivian@}	B-person
,	O
a	O
2	O
hour	O
delay	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
accepted	O
.	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
men	B-event
kon	I-event
sakaraathehtha	I-event
thijahanee	I-event
?	O

EU	B-group
increases	O
budget	O
for	O
private	B-product
jets	I-product
despite	O
climate	B-event
change	I-event
pledges	O
{{URL}}	O
via	O
{@Daily Mail Online@}	B-product
<=	O
"	O
Do	O
as	O
I	O
say	O
,	O
not	O
as	O
I	O
do	O
.	O
"	O

Friends	O
and	O
family	O
it	O
's	O
that	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
year	O
again	O
!	O
{@Saturday Night Takeaway@}	B-product
is	O
back	O
on	O
feel	O
free	O
to	O
nominate	O
me	O
,	O
surprise	O
me	O
anything	O
Haha	O
I	O
've	O
asked	O
every	O
year	O
and	O
still	O
have	O
no	O
got	O
on	O
this	O
show	O
to	O
meet	O
ant	O
and	O
dec	O
or	O
even	O
a	O
place	O
on	O
that	O
plane	O
!!	O
So	O
hopefully	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
year	O
people	O

Listened	O
to	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
Ep-251	O
#	O
Deathworm	O
Greta	B-person
climate	O
change	O
What	O
kind	O
of	O
D-bag	O
attacks	O
a	O
kid	O
?!	O
#	O
Meatshapedcows	O
We	O
also	O
do	O
a	O
low	O
carb	O
diet	O
but	O
try	O
to	O
eat	O
low	O
fat	O
=	O
no	O
bacon	O
,	O
no	O
pasta	O
.	O
Except	O
on	O
vacation	O
!	O
salad	O
#	O
Slipknot	B-group
#	O
1	O
“	O
Too	O
old	O
for	O
sweaty	O
rock	O
shows	O
”!	O
Cheers	O

Yes	O
!	O
Live	O
sports	O
is	O
back	O
w	O
#	O
NASCARIsBack	B-event
!	O
Luckily	O
unlike	O
other	O
sports	O
it	O
's	O
not	O
the	O
crowd	O
noise	O
that	O
creates	O
a	O
good	O
product	O
unlike	O
{@Philadelphia Phillies@}	B-group
{@Philadelphia Eagles@}	B-group
{@Philadelphia 76ers@}	B-group
exception	O
{@Philadelphia Flyers@}	B-group
.	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
{@John Kincade@}	B-person

Thread	O
by	O
{@David Frum@}	B-person
:	O
To	O
abridge	O
the	O
argument	O
made	O
in	O
Trumpocalypse	O
:	O
Some	O
of	O
Trump	B-person
's	O
poor	O
standing	O
among	O
military	B-creative_work
officers	I-creative_work
obviously	O
due	O
to	O
e	O
.	O
The	O
service	B-creative_work
with	O
the	O
most	O
PhDs	O
is	O
the	O
Air	B-corporation
Force	I-corporation
,	O
and	O
that	O
's	O
the	O
service	B-creative_work
where	O
Trump	B-person
polls	O
worst	O
with	O
the	O
office	O
…	O
{{URL}}	O

Happy	B-event
Mothers	I-event
Day	I-event
to	O
all	O
the	O
Mums	O
who	O
are	O
Carers	O
across	O
West	B-location
Sussex	I-location
,	O
and	O
to	O
all	O
the	O
Mums	O
on	O
our	O
great	O
staff	O
and	O
volunteers	O
on	O
our	O
team	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
I	O
am	O
sending	O
a	O
virtual	O
hug	O
to	O
you	O
all	O
as	O
you	O
are	O
amazing	O
.	O

Watch	O
out	O
for	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
music	O
cause	O
2020	O
is	O
his	O
year	O
coming	O
with	O
the	O
HEAT	B-event
check	O
out	O
his	O
three	O
recent	B-creative_work
songs	I-creative_work
on	O
YouTube	B-corporation
you	O
wo	O
n’t	O
be	O
disappointed	O

Flowing	O
to	O
{@Liquid Stranger@}	B-group
at	O
lost	O
lands	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
euphoric	O
feelings	O
I	O
’ve	O
ever	O
had	O
at	O
a	O
concert	O
,	O
or	O
ever	O
.	O
I	O
felt	O
so	O
in	O
tune	O
with	O
the	O
universe	O
and	O
the	O
music	O
.	O
And	O
felt	O
one	O
with	O
the	O
music	O
and	O
crowd	O

Via	O
{@NBC News Health@}	B-corporation
:	O
Celebrities	O
like	O
Gwyneth	B-person
Paltrow	I-person
made	O
the	O
2010s	O
the	O
decade	O
of	O
health	O
and	O
wellness	O
misinformation	O
{{URL}}	O
{@Timothy Caulfield@}	B-person
{@Jennifer Gunter@}	B-person
{@André Picard@}	B-person
{@Theresa Boyle@}	B-person
{@Vik Adhopia@}	B-person
{{USERNAME}}	O
{@David Gorski, MD, PhD@}	B-person
{{USERNAME}}	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
{{USERNAME}}	O

#	O
1MonthWithMoreandMore	O
{@TWICE@}	B-group
'	O
s	O
'	O
MORE	B-creative_work
&	I-creative_work
MORE	I-creative_work
'	O
charted	O
on	O
Billboard	B-corporation
200	O
charts	O
at	O
#	O
200	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
the	O
group	O
's	O
first	O
ever	O
entery	O
on	O
the	O
US	B-location
all	O
genre	O
Albums	O
chart	O
.	O
TWICE	B-group
is	O
the	O
4th	O
Korean	O
Girl	O
Group	O
to	O
chart	O
on	O
Billboard	B-corporation
200	O
.	O
{{URL}}	O

Rocketman	B-product
is	O
finally	O
on	O
Sky	B-corporation
.	O
An	O
hour	O
in	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
'	O
s	O
comment	O
was	O
bang	O
on	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
see	O
why	O
he	O
is	O
so	O
f	O
**	O
ked	O
up	O
now	O
.	O
Highly	O
recommended	O
.	O

Excited	O
repost	O
via	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
from	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
We	O
’re	O
providing	O
FREE	B-creative_work
GROUND	I-creative_work
SHIPPING	I-creative_work
on	O
all	O
orders	O
today	O
for	O
an	O
extra	O
sweet	O
#	O
SelfCareSolDay	O
⁠	O
⁠	O
Use	O
code	O
"	O
SOLSHIP1	O
"	O
at	O
checkout	O
⁠	O
(	O
Hurry	O
-	O
offer	O
valid	O
…	O
{{URL}}	O

The	B-group
Cowboys	I-group
have	O
Mike	B-person
McCarthy	I-person
,	O
the	O
Texans	B-group
need	O
a	O
new	O
coach	O
now	O
,	O
{@Lincoln Riley@}	B-person
?	O
I	O
hope	O
at	O
least	O
,	O
#	O
Texans	B-group
#	O
FireBillOBrien	B-event
#	O
BoBSucks	O

#	O
Disney	B-group
Movie	O
#	O
Trivia	B-event
{{USERNAME}}	O
on	O
Sunday	O
,	O
12	O
/	O
1	O
at	O
7pm	O
!	O
RSVP	O
at	O
;	O
{{URL}}	O
#	O
DisneyMovies	B-product
#	O
DisneyPlus	B-product
#	O
NYC	B-location
#	O
EastVillage	B-location

A	O
year	O
ago	O
today	O
,	O
I	O
decided	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
concert	O
in	O
Salt	B-location
Lake	I-location
three	O
hours	O
before	O
doors	O
opened	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
idea	O
who	O
the	O
opening	O
bands	O
were	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
say	O
I	O
became	O
a	O
fan	O
of	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
and	O
{@THE  F A I M@}	B-group
that	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
mean	O
it	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
best	O
decisions	O
I	O
’ve	O
ever	O
made	O
.	O

The	O
best	O
part	O
about	O
watching	O
this	O
The	B-creative_work
Match	I-creative_work
:	I-creative_work
Champions	I-creative_work
for	I-creative_work
Charity	I-creative_work
is	O
no	O
douche	O
canoe	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
calling	O
in	O
and	O
taking	O
false	O
credit	O
for	O
it	O
.	O

Great	O
job	O
{@Matt DiBenedetto@}	B-person
and	O
{@Wood Brothers Racing@}	B-group
{@Las Vegas Motor Speedway@}	B-event
today	O
!	O
Strong	O
showing	O
!	O
Keep	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
good	O
luck	O
next	O
weekend	O
!	O

Secret	O
police	O
in	O
Oregon	B-location
arresting	O
peaceful	O
demonstrators	O
.	O
Is	O
this	O
Russia	B-location
,	O
China	B-location
,	O
Cuba	B-location
,	O
Saudi	B-location
Arabia	I-location
?	O
{@Marco Rubio@}	B-person
{{USERNAME}}	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
act	O
of	O
a	O
fascist	O
dictator	O
not	O
the	O
USA	B-location
I	O
was	O
raised	O
in	O
.	O
{@Senate Republicans@}	B-group
{@Senate Democrats@}	B-group
{{USERNAME}}	O
{@U.S. Army@}	B-group
{@U.S. Navy@}	B-group
{@U.S. Air Force@}	B-group
{{USERNAME}}	O

NEW	O
:	O
{@Holiday World@}	B-location
sets	O
new	O
opening	O
date	O
:	O
June	O
17th	O
.	O
.	O
water	O
park	O
..	O
.	O
July	O
4th	O
.	O
{{URL}}	O

bighit	O
just	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
full	O
art	O
house	O
film	O
experience	O
.	O
i	O
got	O
the	O
rite	O
of	O
spring	O
type	O
of	O
vibes	O
tho	O
that	O
's	O
probably	O
just	O
me	O
but	O
anyway	O
it	O
's	O
such	O
an	O
amazing	B-creative_work
music	I-creative_work
video	I-creative_work
to	I-creative_work
watch	I-creative_work
.	O
{@TOMORROW X TOGETHER@}	B-group
,	O
babies	O
you	O
did	O
so	O
good	O
!	O
i	O
loved	O
every	O
second	O
of	O
it	O
!	O
{{URL}}	O

Ahh	O
ca	O
n’t	O
wait	O
to	O
use	O
my	O
annual	O
pass	O
at	O
Galaxy	B-location
’s	I-location
Edge	I-location
once	O
it	O
’s	O
open	O
again	O
!	O
So	O
glad	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
ride	O
Rise	B-creative_work
Of	I-creative_work
The	I-creative_work
Resistance	I-creative_work
at	O
least	O
once	O
in	O
the	O
before	O
era	O
!	O
:	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
#	O
Nerdpins	B-group
#	O
Pingame	O
@	O
Star	B-creative_work
Wars	I-creative_work
Galaxies	I-creative_work
…	O
{{URL}}	O

During	O
this	O
crisis	B-event
{{USERNAME}}	O
could	O
single	O
handedly	O
stimulate	O
the	O
stock	B-product
market	I-product
and	O
secure	O
the	O
future	O
housing	B-event
market	I-event
while	O
gaining	O
a	O
huge	O
voter	B-group
block	I-group
.	O
Add	O
student	B-event
loan	I-event
forgiveness	I-event
to	O
the	O
stimulus	B-product
package	I-product
.	O
#	O
studentstimulus	O
#	O
studentloans	B-product
#	O
StudentLoanDebt	O

Jerry	B-person
Stiller	I-person
’s	O
Greatest	O
Moments	O
on	O
‘	O
Seinfeld’	B-creative_work
{{URL}}	O
via	O
{@The Ringer@}	B-product

Why	O
is	O
n't	O
{@Sky Sports Rugby League@}	B-group
showing	O
the	O
Toulouse	B-group
vs	O
{@York City Knights⚔️@}	B-group
match	O
this	O
weekend	O
?	O
Thought	O
they	O
were	O
showing	O
all	O
playoff	O
matches	O
?	O
{{URL}}	O

I	O
know	O
that	O
the	O
World	B-event
Series	I-event
is	O
on	O
and	O
the	O
NBA	B-corporation
season	O
is	O
just	O
starting	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
{@Tiger Woods@}	B-person
is	O
leading	O
a	O
golf	O
tournament	O
right	O
now	O
#	O
GOAT	O

#	O
Twitter	B-corporation
allows	O
hatred	O
to	O
be	O
spread	O
by	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
while	O
all	O
of	O
us	O
must	O
toe	O
the	O
line	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
beyond	O
normal	O
and	O
we	O
should	O
hold	O
him	O
to	O
account	O
,	O
by	O
unfollowing	O
or	O
refusing	O
to	O
read	O
any	O
tweets	O
posted	O
by	O
him	O
or	O
in	O
his	O
name	O
.	O
There	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
two	O
sets	O
of	O
rules	O
!	O
#	O
UnfollowTrump	B-corporation

Happy	B-event
Fathers	I-event
Day	I-event
!	O
Kimberly	B-person
Sells	I-person
McKinney	I-person
cranking	O
{@Bootsy Collins@}	B-person
and	O
FrankieBeverly	B-person
and	O
Maze	O
on	O
the	O
Veranda	B-event
Happy	I-event
Hour	I-event
.	O
She	B-person
was	O
jamming	O
The	O
King	O
of	O
Go	O
Go	O
-	O
Chuck	B-person
Brown	I-person
earlier	O
!	O
Thank	O
You	O
{@Sonos@}	B-product

Holy	O
Spirit	O
Invades	O
the	O
White	B-location
House	I-location
as	O
Worship	B-group
Leaders	I-group
Call	O
Upon	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Jesus	B-person
{{URL}}	O
via	O
{{USERNAME}}	O

Epic	O
battle	O
in	O
the	O
WCC	B-corporation
quarterfinal	O
.	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
ripped	O
my	O
Pepperdine	O
heart	O
out	O
with	O
that	O
crazy	O
clutch	O
3	O
to	O
put	O
the	O
game	O
away	O
.	O
Lost	O
an	O
instant	O
classic	O
and	O
an	O
hour	O
in	O
one	O
night	O
.	O
#	O
TiredWave	O
#	O
congratschesschamp	O

seeing	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
tonight	O
at	O
the	O
mercury	B-corporation
lounge	I-corporation
and	O
have	O
an	O
extra	O
ticket	B-product
!	O
DM	O
me	O
if	O
interested	O
.	O
a	O
side	O
note	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
surrounded	O
by	O
so	O
many	O
other	O
folks	O
using	O
assistive	O
devices	O
tonight	O
,	O
everyone	O
looks	O
gorgeous	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
here	O
is	O
an	O
absolute	O
blessing	O

I	O
’m	O
so	O
mad	O
I	O
missed	O
day	O
1	O
of	O
Rolling	O
loud	O
{@Rolling Loud@}	B-event

“	O
If	O
it	O
were	O
up	O
to	O
government	B-group
,	O
money	O
,	O
or	O
education	O
alone	O
it	O
would	O
have	O
worked	O
already	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
hasn’t	O
.	O
The	O
answer	O
is	O
Jesus	B-person
.	O
The	O
heart	O
of	O
the	O
problem	O
is	O
a	O
problem	O
of	O
the	O
heart	O
.	O
”	O
Powerful	O
message	O
about	O
unity	O
this	O
morning	O
by	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
Jesus	B-person
you	O
alone	O
!	O

I	O
guess	O
those	O
with	O
no	O
breast	O
cancer	O
are	O
appreciating	O
themselves	O
......	O
.	O
❤	O
Stop	O
using	O
Sunday	O
as	O
an	O
excuse	O
and	O
stop	O
acting	O
like	O
it	O
's	O
ungodly	O
,	O
maybe	O
it	O
's	O
either	O
it	O
has	O
fallen	O
,	O
tiny	O
or	O
not	O
presentable	O
*	O
No	B-event
Bra	I-event
Day	I-event
*	O
#	O
NoBraDay	B-event
#	O
NoBraDay2019	B-event
{{USERNAME}}	O
{{USERNAME}}	O

Hinahanap	O
ko	O
na	O
yong	O
bonggang	O
selfie	O
nyo	O
with	O
the	O
Boy	O
's	O
{@BoybandPH@}	B-person
Shout	O
to	O
Ms.France	B-person
{{USERNAME}}	O
Ayeeeeee	O
ASAPSundateWith	O
BoybandPH	B-group

An	O
excellent	O
,	O
a	O
beautiful	O
person	O
not	O
only	O
with	O
her	O
great	O
voice	O
but	O
also	O
with	O
her	O
humble	O
personality	O
.	O
Love	O
your	O
existence	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
{@Joss Stone@}	B-person
The	B-creative_work
Love	I-creative_work
We	I-creative_work
Had	I-creative_work
(	I-creative_work
Stays	I-creative_work
On	I-creative_work
My	I-creative_work
Mind	I-creative_work
)	I-creative_work
(	O
Official	B-creative_work
Video	I-creative_work
)	O
Joss	B-person
Stone	I-person
{{URL}}	O

10	O
Best	O
things	O
about	O
my	O
decade	O
1	O
.	O
I	O
finished	O
school	B-group
2	O
.	O
New	B-creative_work
Star	I-creative_work
Wars	I-creative_work
movies	I-creative_work
and	O
shows	O
3	O
.	O
{@Brooklyn Nine-Nine@}	B-creative_work
and	O
{@The Good Place is taking it sleazy@}	B-creative_work
became	O
things	O
4	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
The	B-event
Witcher	I-event
games	I-event
and	I-event
books	I-event
(	O
and	O
show	O
)	O
5	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
new	O
friends	O
6	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
passion	O
for	O
filmmaking	O
7	O
.	O
I	O
tried	O
new	O
things	O
1	O
/	O
2	O

{{USERNAME}}	O
promo	O
code	O
{@Uber@}	B-corporation
{{USERNAME}}	O
{@Uber Eats@}	B-product
{@Postmates@}	B-corporation
{@Grubhub@}	B-corporation
Uber	O
$	O
20	O
off	O
code	O
manala5921ui	O
Hungry	O
?	O
???	O
Get	O
$	O
7	O
off	O
your	O
first	O
order	O
on	O
Uber	B-corporation
Eats	I-corporation
with	O
my	O
code	O
eats-manala5921ui	O
DoorDash	B-corporation
Get	O
$	O
20	O
off	O
when	O
you	O
sign	O
up	O
with	O
this	O
link	O
{{URL}}	O

#	O
NP	O
FROM	O
THE	O
ALBUM	O
Empty	O
Sounds,Bernie	B-corporation
Leroux	I-corporation
{{USERNAME}}	O
-	O
Dark	B-creative_work
Side	I-creative_work
Of	I-creative_work
The	I-creative_work
City	I-creative_work
,	O
#	O
listen	O
{{URL}}	O
<<	O
and	O
{{URL}}	O
#	O
PlayingEverythingMusic	O
#	O
IndieMusic	O
#	O
unsignedartist	O
#	O
internetradio	O
#	O
NoneStopMusic	O

Happy	B-event
Women	I-event
's	I-event
day	I-event
to	O
all	O
from	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
.	O
Here	O
’s	O
to	O
strong	O
women	O
:	O
May	O
we	O
know	O
them	O
.	O
May	O
we	O
be	O
them	O
.	O
May	O
we	O
raise	O
them	O
.	O
#	O
happywomensday	O
#	O
teamhippieinhills	B-group
#	O
hippieinhills	B-group
@	O
Sethan	B-location
{{URL}}	O

Wowww	O
what	O
a	O
punch	O
,	O
great	O
to	O
see	O
{@Cody Garbrandt@}	B-person
back	O
with	O
a	O
KO	O
at	O
the	O
buzzer	O
!!	O
!	O

So	O
Friday	O
was	O
my	O
leaving	O
do	O
from	O
{@Oxleas NHS@}	B-corporation
after	O
5	O
years	O
The	O
teams	O
working	O
within	O
forensic	B-group
services	I-group
are	O
just	O
immense	O
and	O
I	O
feel	O
proud	O
to	O
have	O
worked	O
alongside	O
you	O
.	O
Good	O
days	O
and	O
challenging	O
,	O
all	O
very	O
special	O
.	O
Thank	O
you	O
for	O
my	O
send	O
off	O
and	O
humbled	O
by	O
the	O
50	O
+who	O
came	O
incredible	O

Lullaby	B-creative_work
(	I-creative_work
Juice	I-creative_work
Wrld	I-creative_work
Type	I-creative_work
Beat	I-creative_work
)	I-creative_work
by	O
ReidGoCrazy	B-event
{@BeatStars@}	B-product
{{URL}}	O
#	O
NowPlaying	O
#	O
NP	O
{@SoaR@}	B-group

Happy	B-event
Mother	I-event
’s	I-event
Day	I-event
!	O
Truly	O
the	O
most	O
important	O
of	O
jobs	O
!	O
Blessed	O
to	O
have	O
such	O
a	O
great	O
mother	O
myself	O
and	O
very	O
proud	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
absolute	O
BEST	O
mom	O
raising	O
our	O
boys	O
!	O
#	O
love	O
#	O
HappyMothersDay	B-event
{{USERNAME}}	O

Charge	O
the	O
cops	O
who	O
shot	O
Jacob	B-person
Blake	I-person
-	O
Sign	O
the	O
Petition	O
!	O
#	O
blacklivesmatter	B-group
#	O
justiceforjacobblake	B-group
{{URL}}	O
via	O
{@Change org Россия@}	B-product

#	O
DoctorWhoLockdown	O
#	O
HelloSweetie	O
Today	O
is	O
the	O
anniversary	O
of	O
the	O
debut	O
of	O
River	B-creative_work
Song	I-creative_work
or	O
so	O
the	O
internet	O
told	O
me	O
.	O
anyone	O
up	O
for	O
a	O
popup	O
rewatch	O
of	O
Silence	B-creative_work
in	I-creative_work
the	I-creative_work
Library	I-creative_work
and	O
Forest	B-creative_work
of	I-creative_work
the	I-creative_work
Dead	I-creative_work
?	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
Say	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
in	O
Britain	B-location
?	O
Give	O
everyone	O
an	O
hour	O
to	O
prep	O
,	O
spread	O
word	O

Listen	O
To	O
{@FUTURE/FREEBANDZ@}	B-corporation
’s	O
New	O
Album	B-product
“	O
High	B-creative_work
Off	I-creative_work
Life	I-creative_work
”	O
[	O
Apple	B-product
Music	I-product
]	O
{{URL}}	O

Greta	B-person
Thunberg	I-person
&	O
Allies	B-group
File	O
Climate	O
Complaint	O
Against	O
5	O
Countries	O
(	O
Not	O
China	B-group
)	O
{{URL}}	O
via	O
{@Breitbart News@}	B-product
SAD	O
LITTLE	O
GIRL	O
BEING	O
USED	O
BY	O
THE	O
GLOBALISTS	B-group
....	O
.	O
WHEN	O
MATURE	O
SHE	O
WILL	O
BE	O
VERY	O
ANGRY	O
I	O
THINK	O

ask-peach-kisses	B-person
:	O
“	O
HAPPY	O
VALENTINE’S	B-event
DAY	I-event
!”	O
-	O
From	O
the	O
resident	O
ocs	O
of	O
this	O
(	O
and	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
-	O
sokku-sweets	O
‘	O
blog	B-group
!)	O
[	O
HELLO	O
LOVES	O
!	O
This	O
took	O
me	O
awhile	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
and	O
forgive	O
me	O
for	O
sped	O
lookin	O
stuff	O
here	O
,	O
its	O
a	O
lot	O
of	O
ocs	O
for	O
this	O
years	O
Valentine	B-event
’s	I-event
Day	I-event
..	O
.	O
{{URL}}	O

A	O
little	O
late	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
but	O
loved	O
watching	O
#	O
Kaafir	B-creative_work
.	O
Was	O
moved	O
by	O
the	O
amazing	O
storytelling	O
,	O
poetry	O
,	O
language	O
and	O
most	O
importantly	O
,	O
stunning	O
performances	O
by	O
{@Dia Mirza@}	B-person
{@mohit raina@}	B-person
and	O
my	O
sweetheart	O
#	O
Renukasharma	B-person
Feel	O
the	O
story	O
deserves	O
a	O
second	O
season	O
{@ZEE5@}	B-product
{@siddharth malhotra@}	B-person

Started	O
the	O
first	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
decade	O
by	O
discussing	O
furries	O
with	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
and	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
this	O
morning	O
.	O
Ending	O
it	O
with	O
watching	O
an	O
“	O
American	B-creative_work
Dad	I-creative_work
!”	O
Episode	O
about	O
ham	O
.	O
This	O
bodes	O
well	O
for	O
the	O
years	O
to	O
come	O
.	O

#	O
:	O
Quite	O
interesting	O
simulations	O
for	O
virus	O
spread	O
with	O
social	O
distancing	O
.	O
Great	O
article	O
{@Harry Stevens@}	B-person
.	O
{{URL}}	O

Massive	O
Tropical	O
Storm	O
Cristobal	O
Bringing	O
Flooding	O
Rains	O
,	O
Storm	O
Surge	O
Threat	O
To	O
Millions	O
Along	O
The	O
Gu	O
..	O
.	O
via	O
{@Forbes@}	B-product
{{URL}}	O

Start	O
of	O
a	O
new	O
year	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
decade	O
where	O
we	O
cure	O
cancer	O
.	O
Happy	O
new	O
year	O
to	O
you	O
all	O
.	O
{@Cancer Research UK@}	B-corporation

South	B-group
Africa	I-group
squeezing	O
access	O
to	O
citizenship	O
for	O
migrants	O
over	O
25	O
years	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
via	O
{@The Conversation Africa@}	B-product
{{URL}}	O

Our	O
last	O
live	O
chat	O
/	O
Q	O
&	O
A	O
got	O
more	O
views	O
&	O
positive	O
feedback	O
than	O
expected	O
,	O
so	O
why	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
again	O
?	O
This	O
time	O
{@Dr. Tanya Harrison@}	B-person
,	O
Phil	B-person
,	O
&	O
I	O
will	O
chat	O
about	O
Mars'	B-group
identity	O
crisis	O
in	O
the	O
early	O
space	O
age	O
Aug	O
24	O
,	O
6:00	O
PM	O
EDT	O
New	O
Identity	O
:	O
Mars	B-group
in	O
the	O
60s	O
and	O
70s	O
{{URL}}	O

Winning	O
tickets	B-product
from	O
{@NOW 100.5 FM@}	B-product
to	O
see	O
{@Harry Styles.@}	B-person
in	O
August	O
has	O
been	O
the	O
highlight	O
of	O
my	O
year	O
Forever	O
thankful	O
#	O
liveinthenow	O
#	O
tpwk	O

open	O
@	O
Both	O
location	O
Houston	B-location
and	O
Kenner	B-location
Great	O
hair	O
at	O
affordable	O
prices	O
thehairkingpin	B-corporation
_	O
We	O
show	O
love	O
and	O
spread	O
love	O
thehairkingpin	B-corporation
_	O
.......	O
.	O
HOLLA	O
AT	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
FOR	O
YOUR	O
#	O
PROMOTION	O
NEEDS	O
{{URL}}	O

I	O
have	O
the	O
best	O
friend	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
!	O
Madisen	B-person
unboxed	O
her	O
Halloween	B-event
Prom	I-event
Night	I-event
Vinyl	I-event
from	O
{@Jeffree Star@}	B-person
,	O
and	O
knowing	O
what	O
a	O
freak	O
I	O
am	O
for	O
anything	O
related	O
to	O
makeup	O
and	O
a	O
turntable	O
,	O
gifted	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
blue	O
.	O
What	O
a	O
true	O
spooky	O
sister	O
!	O

Petition	O
for	O
Hannah	B-person
Montana	I-person
and	O
curly	O
haired	O
{@Taylor Swift@}	B-person
to	O
go	O
on	O
tour	O
?	O
{@Disney@}	B-corporation
has	O
me	O
missing	O
the	O
old	O
days	O
.	O
{@Miley Ray Cyrus@}	B-person
#	O
HannahMontanaTheMovie	B-creative_work

Everyone	O
at	O
my	O
hotel	O
(@	O
HiltonRiversid	B-location
)	O
is	O
cheering	O
for	O
the	O
Texans	B-group
because	O
of	O
{@Deshaun Watson@}	B-person
,	O
{@Deandre Hopkins@}	B-person
,	O
&	O
{@Dj Reader@}	B-person
.	O
By	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
I	O
’m	O
a	O
salty	O
Cardinals	B-group
fan	O
who	O
wanted	O
Watson	B-person
(	O
Watson	B-person
or	O
bust	O
)	O
in	O
the	O
2017	B-event
draft	I-event
.	O
#	O
WeAreTexans	O
#	O
Clemson	B-group
#	O
ClemsonFB	B-group
#	O
CFP	B-event
#	O
LSUvsCLEM	B-event

stay	O
safe	O
and	O
always	O
healthy	O
all	O
of	O
you	O
!!	O
{@NCT@}	B-group
{@NCT DREAM@}	B-group
{@NCT 127@}	B-group
{@WayV@}	B-group

Fake	O
News	O
{@CNN@}	B-product
(	O
The	O
Enemy	O
of	O
the	O
People	O
)	O
Praised	O
Michael	B-person
Avenatti	I-person
,	O
Now	O
A	O
Convicted	O
Felon	O
,	O
As	O
The	O
Man	O
Who	O
Could	O
Take	O
Down	O
Trump	B-person
{{URL}}	O

Final	O
day	O
at	O
the	O
#	O
wwcpdxhack2019	B-event
!	O
I	O
had	O
such	O
a	O
blast	O
with	O
my	O
team	O
learning	O
about	O
new	O
technologies	O
,	O
hardware	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
to	O
send	O
our	O
data	O
to	O
the	O
cloud	O
.	O
Thanks	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
for	O
organizing	O
the	O
event	O
and	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
for	O
hosting	O
.	O

Shame	O
on	O
karnataka	B-corporation
government	I-corporation
.	O
How	O
can	O
they	O
be	O
so	O
irresponsible	O
about	O
students'	O
health	O
?	O
Students	O
will	O
show	O
the	O
power	O
in	O
next	O
elections	O
.	O
#	O
postponekcet2020	O
{@Dr. Ramesh Pokhriyal Nishank@}	B-person

Thread	O
by	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
:	O
Here	O
's	O
just	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
half	O
dozen	O
antisemitic	O
things	O
Farrakhan	B-person
said	O
today	O
with	O
the	O
support	O
of	O
{@LOVE@}	B-corporation
.	O
Calling	O
me	O
an	O
ew	O
"	O
that	O
Allah	O
must	O
banish	O
,	O
equivalent	O
to	O
Satan	B-person
,	O
does	O
n't	O
make	O
it	O
any	O
less	O
Jew-hatred	O
.	O
Farrakhan	B-person
defining	O
who	O
Jews	B-group
…	O
{{URL}}	O

Mason	B-person
loves	O
the	O
Masked	B-creative_work
Singer	I-creative_work
.	O
His	O
favourites	O
were	O
duck	O
and	O
monster	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
spent	O
them	O
morning	O
mashing	O
together	O
a	O
tv	O
trailer	O
for	O
the	O
final	O
to	O
include	O
{@CBeebies Grown-Ups 🎉@}	B-group
{{USERNAME}}	O
Octoblock	O

Completely	O
lost	O
my	O
head	O
at	O
yesterday	B-event
’s	I-event
game	I-event
!!	O
The	O
fire	O
still	O
very	O
much	O
alive	O
inside	O
of	O
me	O
for	O
this	O
game	O
we	O
call	O
football	B-product
!!	O
The	O
dons	O
know	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
squeeze	O
yesterday	O
That	O
aside	O
,	O
the	O
quality	O
of	O
football	B-product
on	O
show	O
yesterday	O
was	O
unbelievable	O
Roca	B-group
_	I-group
Seniors	I-group
{{USERNAME}}	O
well	O
done	O
boys	B-group

Happy	B-event
National	I-event
Ice	I-event
Cream	I-event
Day	I-event
Celebrate	O
with	O
a	O
healthy	O
and	O
digestible	O
alternative	O
to	O
ice	O
cream	O
for	O
your	O
pup	O
!	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
frozen	B-product
yogurt	I-product
is	O
a	O
cool	O
treat	O
for	O
a	O
hot	O
day	O
or	O
any	O
day	O
!	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
#	O
waglocal	B-location
#	O
shoplocal	B-location
…	O
{{URL}}	O

Lmao	O
so	O
many	O
questions	O
I	O
have	O
for	O
{@Tyler Perry@}	B-person
about	O
a	B-creative_work
fall	I-creative_work
from	I-creative_work
grace	I-creative_work
.	O

Kindly	O
let	O
us	O
leave	O
and	O
work	O
in	O
other	O
countries	O
,	O
because	O
we	O
desire	O
to	O
help	O
our	O
FAMILY	O
.	O
We	O
know	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
lack	O
of	O
nurses	O
here	O
in	O
Philippines	B-location
.	O
Hire	O
those	O
unemployed	O
nurses	O
and	O
let	O
those	O
with	O
employers	O
go	O
#	O
POEAfollowIATF	O
Please	O
help	O
us	O
Sir	O
{@Teddy Locsin Jr.@}	B-person
{{URL}}	O

Browns	B-group
CB	O
Denzel	B-person
Ward	I-person
(	O
hamstring	O
)	O
and	O
CB	O
Greedy	B-person
Williams	I-person
(	O
hamstring	O
)	O
are	O
both	O
NOT	O
expected	O
to	O
play	O
against	O
the	O
Seahawks	B-group
.	O
FOLLOW	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
to	O
stay	O
updated	O
on	O
all	O
…	O
{{URL}}	O

At	O
10am	O
ET	O
the	O
Supreme	B-group
Court	I-group
releases	O
decisions	O
,	O
if	O
any	O
are	O
ready	O
.	O
Many	O
are	O
watching	O
for	O
a	O
possible	O
Court	B-group
ruling	O
on	O
President	B-person
Trump	I-person
's	O
effort	O
to	O
end	O
DACA	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
legal	O
status	O
of	O
hundreds	O
of	O
thousands	O
of	O
immigrants	B-group
on	O
the	O
line	O
.	O
If	O
there	O
's	O
a	O
ruling	O
we	O
'll	O
be	O
live	O
soon	O
after	O
.	O
{@NPR@}	B-corporation

Take	O
a	O
look	O
at	O
the	O
full	O
shootout	O
from	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
'	O
s	O
scoreless	B-event
win	I-event
over	O
Houghton	B-group
to	O
start	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
play	O
!	O
#	O
greatdaytobeahawk	B-event
Goals	O
from	O
Wheeler	B-person
,	O
Gagnon	B-person
,	O
and	O
Singer	B-person
Three	I-person
Osborne	I-person
saves	O
{{URL}}	O

Yo	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
people	O
have	O
to	O
cook	O
Easter	B-event
dinner	O
.	O
Cmon	O
man	O

#	O
IndvsSA	B-event
:	O
Heavy	O
downpour	O
in	O
Dharamsala	B-location
ahead	O
of	O
first	O
T20	B-event
{{URL}}	O
via	O
{@The Tribune@}	B-product

The	O
last	O
session	O
of	O
conference	O
is	O
like	O
the	O
last	O
Harry	B-creative_work
Potter	I-creative_work
movie	I-creative_work
.	O
It	O
’s	O
really	O
good	O
but	O
you	O
ca	O
n’t	O
help	O
but	O
fall	O
asleep	O
after	O
a	O
day	O
long	O
marathon	O
of	O
watching	O
.	O
I	O
’m	O
up	O
and	O
ready	O
for	O
temple	O
announcements	O
though	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
#	O
GeneralConference	B-event

Gashi	B-person
Feat	O
.	O
Dj	B-person
Snake	I-person
,	O
Afro	B-person
B	I-person
&	O
Chris	B-person
Brown	I-person
-	O
Safety	B-creative_work
2020	I-creative_work
#	O
Gashi	B-person
#	O
DjSnake	O
#	O
AfroB	O
#	O
ChrisBrown	O
#	O
DaHubRadio	B-corporation
#	O
NowPlaying	O
:	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
If	O
Ur	O
#'	O
d	O
Above	O
So	O
We	O
Can	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
You	O
In	O
Future	O
..	O
.	O
Update	O
Tune	O
Tags	O
{{URL}}	O

I	O
'm	O
really	O
proud	O
of	O
the	O
work	O
we	O
've	O
done	O
in	O
the	O
last	O
few	O
weeks	O
.	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
was	O
forged	O
at	O
the	O
closing	O
moments	O
of	O
the	O
decade	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
've	O
already	O
come	O
so	O
far	O
.	O
I	O
'm	O
looking	O
forward	O
to	O
where	O
we	O
go	O
from	O
here	O
.	O
#	O
BestOf2019	B-event
#	O
NewYear2020	B-event

#	O
MrRobot	B-product
Elliot	B-person
ca	O
n't	O
fix	O
the	O
world	B-location
because	O
he	O
uses	O
{@Dell@}	B-corporation
computers	O
..	O
.	O

FanPlus	B-group
Vote	O
Event	O
for	O
Idols	O
Born	O
/	O
Debuted	O
in	O
September	O
(~	O
11th	O
,	O
August	O
17:00	O
KST	O
)	O
VOTE	O
FOR	O
JONGDAE	B-person
!	O
He	O
's	O
currently	O
in	O
the	O
1st	O
place	O
but	O
we	O
have	O
to	O
widen	O
the	O
gap	O
!	O
{@EXO@}	B-group
{{URL}}	O

#	O
MUSTREAD	O
“	O
a	O
delight	O
to	O
read	O
…	O
Love	O
,	O
family	O
,	O
romance	O
,	O
and	O
magic	O
!”	O
Old	B-creative_work
and	I-creative_work
New	I-creative_work
by	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
{{URL}}	O
{{URL}}	O

Congrats	O
to	O
#	O
TysonFuryGypsyKing	B-person
this	O
was	O
well	O
deserved	O
.	O
Looking	O
forward	O
to	O
his	O
fighting	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
very	O
soon	O
.	O
#	O
FuryWilder2	B-creative_work
"	O
Wilder	B-event
vs	I-event
Fury	I-event
II	I-event
:	O
Tyson	B-person
Fury	I-person
hands	O
Deontay	B-person
Wilder	I-person
his	O
first	O
career	O
loss	O
"	O
#	O
WilderFury2	B-event
{{URL}}	O

"	O
I	O
saw	O
Ryan	B-person
Taylor	I-person
at	O
a	O
water	B-location
park	I-location
a	O
couple	O
of	O
years	O
ago	O
with	O
my	O
kids	O
.	O
I	O
turned	O
my	O
head	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
!	O
The	O
first	O
thing	O
I	O
did	O
–	O
I	O
had	O
n’t	O
seen	O
him	O
for	O
six	O
years	O
–	O
before	O
I	O
even	O
said	O
‘	O
Hi’	O
I	O
just	O
sang	O
to	O
him	O
:	O
“	O
Ryan	B-person
Taylor	I-person
,	O
over	O
the	O
wall	O
!”	O
{@Demba Ba@}	B-person
#	O
NUFC	O

Riots	B-event
are	O
happening	O
in	O
all	O
50	O
states	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
all	O
around	O
the	O
world	O
and	O
still	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
is	O
not	O
listening	O
to	O
us	O
.	O
Trump	B-person
you	O
are	O
a	O
sorry	O
excuse	O
for	O
a	O
president	O
.	O
#	O
BlackLivesMatter	B-group
#	O
letter2thewhitehouse	O

Liberals	B-group
Say	O
They	O
Would	O
Abstain	O
From	O
Having	O
Children	O
to	O
Save	O
the	O
World	O
From	O
'	O
Climate	B-event
Change	I-event
'	O
{{URL}}	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
#	O
AAG	O

STREAM	O
WATERMELON	B-creative_work
SUGAR	I-creative_work
BY	O
HARRY	B-person
STYLES	I-person
OR	O
PERISH	O
{{USERNAME}}	O

{{USERNAME}}	O
great	O
job	O
fam	O
sold	O
out	O
sexy	O
Sweetest	B-event
Day	I-event
in	O
Detroit	B-location
!!	O
@	O
Aretha	B-person
's	O
Jazz	B-location
Café	I-location
{{URL}}	O

.	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
You	O
are	O
the	O
SHADIEST	O
,	O
worst	O
pres	O
in	O
US	B-location
history	O
!	O
It	O
's	O
illegal	O
to	O
turn	O
the	O
military	O
into	O
a	O
mercenary	O
army	O
!	O
The	O
9	B-event
/	I-event
11	I-event
were	O
SAUDI	B-corporation
!	O
Where	O
is	O
that	O
$	O
1B	O
?	O
Who	O
's	O
bank	O
?	O
#	O
RESIGN	O
Rep	B-person
.	O
Justin	B-person
Amash	I-person
Blasts	O
Trump	B-person
For	O
'	O
Selling	O
'	O
American	B-group
Troops	I-group
To	O
Saudis	B-group
{{URL}}	O

.	O
{@PECO@}	B-corporation
is	O
worse	O
than	O
the	O
airlines	B-corporation
.	O
Over	O
12	O
hours	O
into	O
a	O
power	O
outage	O
and	O
still	O
refusing	O
to	O
share	O
information	O
with	O
its	O
customers	O
.	O
Will	O
not	O
provide	O
an	O
ETA	O
.	O
Have	O
a	O
sick	O
child	B-person
with	O
me	O
too	O
and	O
no	O
heat	O
.	O

Jesus	B-person
Christ	I-person
Superstar	O
has	O
never	O
ever	O
appealled	O
.	O
But	O
,	O
y'know	O
,	O
locked	O
down	O
with	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
..	O
.	O
OMG	O
{@Tim Minchin@}	B-person
..	O
.	O
that	O
was	O
one	O
incredible	O
performance	O
!	O

Excited	O
to	O
announce	O
the	O
launch	O
of	O
#	O
ProjectPsychology	B-event
brought	O
to	O
you	O
by	O
the	O
OUPS	B-group
.	O
In	O
first	O
episode	O
I	O
will	O
have	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
interviewing	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
.	O
Reply	O
to	O
this	O
tweet	O
with	O
any	O
questions	O
you	O
may	O
have	O
for	O
our	O
guest	O
by	O
23:59	B-event
BST	I-event
today	I-event
for	O
a	O
chance	O
to	O
be	O
included	O
in	O
the	O
podcast	O
!	O

Everyone	O
check	O
out	O
my	O
boys	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
&	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
these	O
guys	O
are	O
gonna	O
be	O
huge	O
!	O
#	O
nextbigthings	O
{@WWE NXT@}	B-corporation

plasticsimz	B-product
:	O
Hot	B-product
Girl	I-product
Summer	I-product
Collection	I-product
(	O
BRANDY	B-product
X	I-product
PLASTIC	I-product
)	O
ATTENTION	O
ALL	O
MY	O
LADIES	O
!!!	O
It	O
’s	O
Hot	B-event
Girl	I-event
Summer	I-event
Time	O
in	O
sims	B-creative_work
!	O
CLICK	O
LINK	O
BELOW	O
TO	O
DOWNLOAD	O
A	O
big	O
thank	O
you	O
to	O
brandy	B-person
sims	I-person
this	O
was	O
a	O
dream	O
come	O
true	O
!	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
Tou	O
Found	O
in	O
Full	O
..	O
.	O
{{URL}}	O

I	O
just	O
want	O
to	O
say	O
thank	O
you	O
to	O
{@Yeroc@}	B-person
{@Sam@}	B-person
{@Colby@}	B-person
{{USERNAME}}	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
{@Katrina Stuart@}	B-person
{{USERNAME}}	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
watch	O
your	B-creative_work
guys	I-creative_work
videos	I-creative_work
they	O
always	O
make	O
me	O
smile,laugh	O
and	O
happy	O
I	O
love	O
youuuu	O
guys	O
so	O
much	O
I	O
hope	O
one	O
day	O
I	O
meet	O
all	O
of	O
you	O
guys	O

Morrison	B-person
uses	O
UN	O
speech	O
to	O
slam	O
Australia	B-location
's	O
climate	O
change	O
critics	O
{{URL}}	O
via	O
{@ABC News@}	B-product

2015	B-event
ADCC	I-event
World	I-event
Champion	I-event
{@Davi Ramos@}	B-person
is	O
main	O
eventing	O
Fight	O
2	O
Win	O
132	O
tonight	O
.	O
Do	O
n't	O
miss	O
this	O
amazing	O
main	O
event	O

Distance	B-product
Learning	I-product
Plan	I-product
(	O
DLP	O
)	O
Destroys	O
Education	O
,	O
Based	O
on	O
Flawed	O
Covid	O
Figures	O
:	O
Letter	O
to	O
Superintendents	O
of	O
Public	O
Schools	O
in	O
Minnesota	B-location
{{URL}}	O
a	O
través	O
de	O
{{USERNAME}}	O

“	O
Brady	B-creative_work
v	I-creative_work
Roethlisberger	I-creative_work
,	O
The	O
Movie	O
”	O
Obviously	O
Chris	B-person
Pratt	I-person
as	O
Tom	B-person
.	O
But	O
I	O
’m	O
struggling	O
with	O
who	O
plays	O
Ben	B-person
..	O
.	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
?	O

#	O
PositiveVibes	O
#	B-corporation
TwitterPhilanthropy	I-corporation
(	O
remember	O
,	O
u	O
've	O
got	O
1M-to-one	O
shot	O
!	O
We	O
r	O
stronger	O
as	O
a	O
#	O
TEAM	O
{{USERNAME}}	O

#	O
RealHeroArnab	O
Arnabji	B-person
you	O
are	O
the	O
real	O
hero	O
of	O
our	O
nation	O
all	O
citizens	O
are	O
with	O
you	O
go	O
ahead	O
without	O
fear	O
we	O
love	O
you	O
❤	O
so	O
much	O
and	O
we	O
salute	O
you	O
heartly	O
.	O
@	O
arnab5222	B-person
{{USERNAME}}	O
#	O
worriors4SSR	O
#	O
JusticeforSushantSingRajput	O

Shabby	B-group
Chic	I-group
Wreaths	I-group
,	O
Boho	B-product
Wedding	I-product
Decor	I-product
,	O
Bohemian	B-creative_work
Bridal	I-creative_work
Shower	I-creative_work
,	O
Roses	O
Floral	O
Wedding	O
Wreath	O
for	O
Front	O
Door	O
,	O
Shabby	B-product
Chic	I-product
Wedding	I-product
Decorations	I-product
{{URL}}	O
via	O
{@Etsy@}	B-product

Happy	O
women	B-event
's	I-event
day	I-event
to	O
all	O
the	O
women	O
out	O
there	O
.	O
This	O
women	B-event
's	I-event
day	I-event
stand	O
by	O
a	O
women	O
with	O
cancer	O
.	O
Donate	O
your	O
hair	O
to	O
a	O
chemo	O
patient	O
.	O
To	O
donate	O
reach	O
out	O
to	O
us	O
at	O
@	O
DonationHair	B-corporation
or	O
email	O
us	O
at	O
…	O
{{URL}}	O

I	O
choose	O
to	O
not	O
let	O
go	O
of	O
X1	B-group
.	O
I	O
'll	O
stay	O
forever	O
and	O
no	O
one	O
can	O
stop	O
me	O
!	O
Fly	O
High	O
!	O
#	O
RebootX1	O
_	O
2020	O
#	O
BraveForX1	O
{{USERNAME}}	O

At	O
12pm	O
,	O
hear	O
from	O
Dr	B-person
.	I-person
Myra	I-person
Rutland	I-person
{{USERNAME}}	O
,	O
a	O
NCC	B-group
board-certified	O
Family	B-person
Nurse	I-person
Practitioner	I-person
,	O
will	O
discuss	O
the	O
topic	O
"	O
Why	O
HIV	O
is	O
no	O
longer	O
a	O
death	O
sentence	O
.	O
Watch	O
the	O
full	O
video	O
and	O
add	O
comments	O
via	O
Facebook	B-corporation
:	O
Urban	B-event
League	I-event
of	I-event
Philadelphia	I-event
#	O
health	O
#	O
equity	O
#	O
disparities	O

Thou	B-creative_work
o	I-creative_work
Lord	I-creative_work
by	O
Man	B-group
O	I-group
War	I-group
Choir	I-group
{{URL}}	O
via	O
{@YouTube@}	B-product
There	O
's	O
a	O
me	O
in	O
this	O
choir	O
and	O
I	O
miss	O
being	O
with	O
my	O
choir	O
family	O
!	O
If	O
you	O
see	O
me	O
comment	O
below	O
!	O

Rapper	O
Kevin	B-person
Gates	I-person
Sextape	O
Leaks	O
–	O
Goes	O
viral	O
on	O
Twitter	B-corporation
!	O
(	O
Graphic	O
)	O
{{URL}}	O
via	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
News	O
Info	O

I	O
think	O
I	O
’m	O
the	O
only	O
person	O
in	O
KC	B-location
not	O
rooting	O
for	O
the	O
chiefs	B-group
.	O
But	O
still	O
having	O
fun	O
with	O
these	O
guys	O
.	O
#	O
Gopats	O
{@New England Patriots@}	B-group
@	O
Kansas	B-location
City	I-location
,	I-location
Missouri	I-location
{{URL}}	O

Someone	O
take	O
my	O
phone	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
’m	O
trying	O
to	O
not	O
look	O
at	O
{@Chicago Blackhawks@}	B-group
home	O
game	O
tickets	O
in	O
October	O

I	O
donated	O
my	O
monthly	O
MetroCard	B-product
to	O
an	O
essential	O
worker	O
here	O
in	O
New	B-location
York	I-location
,	O
and	O
more	O
are	O
needed	O
!	O
Thank	O
you	O
to	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
,	O
who	O
made	O
this	O
a	O
reality	O
:	O
{{URL}}	O

Scott	B-person
Morrison	I-person
says	O
Greta	B-person
Thunberg	I-person
's	O
fiery	O
UN	B-corporation
speech	O
is	O
giving	O
kids	O
'	O
needless	O
anxiety	O
'	O
about	O
climate	O
change	O
(	O
via	O
{@Business Insider Australia@}	B-corporation
)	O
{{URL}}	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
on	O
a	O
course	O
to	O
be	O
this	O
out	O
of	O
touch	O
{@Scott Morrison@}	B-person
or	O
does	O
it	O
come	O
naturally	O
to	O
you	O
?	O

#	O
nowplaying	O
SOBER	B-corporation
REFLECTIONS	I-corporation
(	I-corporation
DEDICATED	I-corporation
TO	I-corporation
MY	I-corporation
LORD	I-corporation
JESUS	I-corporation
CHRIST	I-corporation
)	O
by	O
NOBLE	B-corporation
via	O
{@Audiomack@}	B-product
{{URL}}	O

Jed	B-person
York	I-person
:	O
Give	O
Frank	B-person
Gore	I-person
a	O
Superbowl	B-event
ring	O
if	O
the	O
49ers	B-group
win	O
the	O
Superbowl	B-event
.	O
-	O
Sign	O
the	O
Petition	O
!	O
{{URL}}	O
via	O
{@Change org Россия@}	B-product

Brilliant	O
#	O
Chess	O
commentary	O
from	O
#	O
PeterSvidler	B-person
as	O
#	O
MagnusCarlsen	B-person
pushes	B-event
his	I-event
F	I-event
pawn	O
toward	O
the	O
queening	O
square	O
to	O
win	O
a	O
game	O
he	O
was	O
losing	O
for	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
match	O
:	O
"	O
Frodo	B-person
charging	O
toward	O
Mount	B-corporation
Doom	I-corporation
"	O
.	O
{@chess24.com@}	B-product

Birikwalira	B-person
says	O
that	O
Vipers	B-group
president	B-person
is	O
surrounded	O
by	O
treacherous	O
people	O
.	O
He	O
adds	O
that	O
he	O
will	O
not	O
miss	O
the	O
club	O
despite	O
bring	O
there	O
for	O
five	O
years	O
.	O
He	O
advised	O
the	O
club	O
to	O
always	O
respect	O
the	O
long-serving	O
players	O
Like	O
-	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
{{URL}}	O

Dear	O
{@Twitter India@}	B-corporation
{@Twitter@}	B-product
{@Twitter Verified@}	B-corporation
please	O
remove	O
the	O
blue	O
tick	O
of	O
{@Ramesh Bala@}	B-person
!	O
Wit	O
a	O
verification	O
tag	O
he	O
is	O
providing	O
full	O
of	O
fake	O
nos	O
&	O
screen	O
counts	O
over	O
years	O
!	O
Misusing	O
it	O
big	O
time	O
!	O
IMMEDIATE	O
ACTION	O
REQUIRED	O
..	O
.	O

Kobe	B-person
Bryant	I-person
passed	B-event
away	I-event
..	O
.	O
Raed	O
my	O
story	O
about	O
meeting	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
article	O
on	O
{@Coil@}	B-product
{{URL}}	O

Read	O
some	O
of	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
tweets	B-creative_work
about	O
protests	B-event
.	O
Then	O
ask	O
if	O
he	B-person
fears	O
the	O
common	B-group
man	I-group
woman	I-group
or	O
child	B-group
protesting	I-group
.	O
Then	O
ponder	O
what	O
Jefferson	B-person
meant	O
when	O
he	B-person
said	O
“	O
Under	O
A	O
Democracy	O
the	O
Government	B-corporation
fears	O
the	O
People	O
.	O
Under	O
Tyranny	O
the	O
People	O
fear	O
the	O
Government	B-corporation
.	O

Watching	O
Hamilton	B-creative_work
for	O
the	O
4th	O
time	O
(	O
3	O
in	O
person	O
)	O
and	O
still	O
watching	O
like	O
it	O
’s	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
.	O
The	O
raw	O
emotion	O
you	O
get	O
by	O
being	O
up	O
close	O
&	O
personal	O
with	O
each	O
character	O
is	O
like	O
nothing	O
else	O
.	O
Thanks	O
to	O
{@IN THE FRIGHTS, Disney's ESPANTO, tick tick...BOO!@}	B-person
for	O
such	O
perfection	O
!	O

Manchester	B-group
City	I-group
star	O
Laporte	B-person
criticizes	O
VAR	O
after	O
shock	O
Lyon	B-group
loss	O
{{URL}}	O
via	O
{{USERNAME}}	O

via	O
{@New York Times Opinion@}	B-product
All	O
it	O
would	O
take	O
is	O
one	O
sweet	O
click	O
to	O
force	O
the	O
greatest	O
troll	O
in	O
the	O
history	O
of	O
the	O
internet	O
to	O
meet	O
his	O
maker	O
.	O
Maybe	O
he	O
just	O
disappears	O
in	O
an	O
orange	O
cloud	O
of	O
smoke	O
,	O
screaming	O
,	O
“	O
I	O
’m	O
melllllllting	O
.	O
”	O
{{URL}}	O

Happy	B-event
Pride	I-event
month	I-event
.	O
We	O
will	O
donate	O
100	O
%	O
of	O
profits	O
from	O
any	O
of	O
our	O
LGBTQ	B-group
tees	O
to	O
the	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
in	O
support	O
of	O
the	O
#	O
BLM	B-group
movement	I-group
.	O
.	O
#	O
goth	O
#	O
neogoth	O
#	O
riseup	O
#	O
theoccult	O
#	O
metal	O
#	O
blackmetal	O
#	O
thrashmetal	O
#	O
occult	O
…	O
{{URL}}	O

(	O
Late	O
post	O
)	O
Congratulations	O
to	O
Senior	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
for	O
placing	O
2nd	O
at	O
State	B-event
for	I-event
Region	I-event
7A	I-event
.	O
This	O
is	O
his	O
2nd	O
time	O
placing	O
at	O
state	B-event
with	O
him	O
coming	O
in	O
3rd	O
last	O
year	O
.	O
We	O
’re	O
super	O
proud	O
,	O
keep	O
up	O
the	O
good	O
work	O
!	O

Join	O
our	O
fundraising	B-event
campaign	I-event
for	O
the	O
orphans	B-group
of	I-group
the	I-group
Hochhauser	I-group
family	I-group
in	O
Stamford	B-location
Hill	I-location
{{URL}}	O
via	O
{{USERNAME}}	O

Happy	O
Sunday	O
!	O
Start	O
the	O
day	O
right	O
with	O
a	O
smile	O
!	O
Good	O
Morning	O
everyone	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
#	O
KiaraTakahashi	B-person
#	O
GinoRoque	B-person
#	O
KiaNo	B-person
#	O
MYXAwards2020KiaNo	B-event
#	O
MYXAwards2020	B-event
{{USERNAME}}	O

I	O
had	O
n’t	O
remembered	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
also	O
an	O
earthquake	O
reported	O
in	O
Matthew	B-location
’s	O
Gospel	B-person
on	O
the	O
day	O
Jesus	B-person
rose	O
from	O
the	O
dead	O
!	O
{{URL}}	O
#	O
AtoZChallenge	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
Happy	O
#	O
Easter	B-event
!	O

Germaine	B-person
de	I-person
Randamie	I-person
vs	O
.	O
Amanda	B-person
Nunes	I-person
-	O
12	O
/	O
14	O
/	O
19	O
UFC	B-event
245	I-event
Pick	O
,	O
Odds	O
,	O
and	O
Prediction	O
-	O
Pick	O
Dawgz	B-person
{{URL}}	O
via	O
{{USERNAME}}	O

Thinking	O
of	O
you	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
as	O
I	O
sit	O
down	O
to	O
watch	O
{@Harrogate Town AFC@}	B-group
.	O
#	O
ProudToBeTown	B-event

I	O
’m	O
humbled	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
verse	O
on	O
the	O
new	O
album	O
by	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
{@QUIP@}	B-person
K.I.M	B-group
.	O
3	B-creative_work
Sigue	I-creative_work
La	I-creative_work
Movida	I-creative_work
{{URL}}	O

New	B-event
Years	I-event
2020	I-event
How	O
the	O
Decade	O
is	O
Defined	O
by	O
the	O
Collapse	O
of	O
Black	O
Wealth	O
..	O
.	O
{{URL}}	O
via	O
{@YouTube@}	B-product
~~	O
Excellent	O
show	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
I	O
appreciate	O
your	O
candidness	O

El	B-product
camino	I-product
.	O
.	O
total	O
fan	O
service	O
for	O
all	O
breaking	B-creative_work
bad	I-creative_work
fans	O
!	O
{@Breaking Bad@}	B-creative_work

Stop	O
the	O
sales	B-event
of	O
foot	O
hold	O
/	O
leg	O
hold	O
traps	O
and	O
snares	O
in	O
the	O
United	B-location
States	I-location
-	O
Sign	O
the	O
Petition	B-creative_work
!	O
{{URL}}	O
via	O
{@Change org Россия@}	B-product

I	O
'm	O
honestly	O
so	O
consistently	O
DISGUSTED	O
at	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
racist	O
or	O
discriminatory	O
names	O
plus	O
clan	O
tags	O
I	O
see	O
while	O
playing	O
Modern	B-creative_work
Warfare	I-creative_work
.	O
{@Activision@}	B-corporation
you	O
should	O
definitely	O
look	O
into	O
this	O
better	O

Expected	O
to	O
b	O
a	O
typical	O
{@Vidyut Jammwal@}	B-person
movie	B-creative_work
whr	O
he	O
starts	O
wid	O
a	O
Bang	O
.	O
Bt	O
this	O
1	O
is	O
n't	O
tht	O
.	O
It	O
's	O
Different	O
.	O
It	O
's	O
Good	O
.	O
He	O
's	O
shown	O
range	O
f	O
emotions	O
in	O
this	O
1	O
.	O
Cast	B-group
&	O
Crew	B-group
"	O
God	B-creative_work
's	I-creative_work
Sake	I-creative_work
"	O
do	O
n't	O
miss	O
1	O
{@faruk kabir@}	B-person
{{USERNAME}}	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
{@Aahana Kumra ❤︎❤︎@}	B-person
{{USERNAME}}	O
#	O
KhudaHaafiz	B-person

Very	O
HOT	O
day	O
around	O
the	O
Bay	B-location
Area	I-location
and	O
a	O
little	O
cooler	O
out	O
near	O
Dillon	B-location
Beach	I-location
!	O
Output	O
Bodega	B-location
Bay	I-location
8K	O
6	O
(	O
1	O
)	O
via	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
{{URL}}	O

Anyone	O
wants	O
an	O
example	O
of	O
someone	O
bigger	O
than	O
the	O
sport	O
?	O
M	B-person
.	O
S	B-person
.	O
#	O
Dhoni	B-person
.	O
To	O
quote	O
{@ESPNcricinfo@}	B-corporation
:	O
Dhoni	B-person
is	O
not	O
retired	O
.	O
Or	O
injured	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
not	O
rested	O
.	O
Nobody	O
dares	O
utter	O
the	O
word	O
"	O
dropped	O
"	O
.	O

A	O
contributor	O
on	O
#	O
LetsTalkAbuja	O
on	O
95.1	B-product
{{USERNAME}}	O
called	O
Efe	B-person
shared	O
this	O
&	O
it	O
's	O
so	O
true	O
..	O
.	O
"	O
The	O
world	O
truly	O
is	O
a	O
global	O
village	O
not	O
only	O
with	O
the	O
internet	O
&	O
technology	O
..	O
.	O
It	O
's	O
also	O
a	O
global	O
village	O
with	O
infectious	O
diseases	O
.	O
"	O
{@NCDC@}	B-corporation
{@Nigeria Health Watch@}	B-corporation
{{USERNAME}}	O
{@Chikwe Ihekweazu@}	B-person

The	O
value	O
of	O
public	O
libraries	O
in	O
the	O
Age	O
of	O
the	O
Internet	O
#	O
libraries	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
{@Arts Council England@}	B-corporation
{{USERNAME}}	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
{@American Library Association@}	B-corporation
{{USERNAME}}	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
{{URL}}	O

Dearest	O
{@President Biden@}	B-person
,	O
If	B-person
you	B-person
ever	O
try	O
to	O
help	O
your	O
fellow	O
countrymen	B-person
w	O
/	O
a	O
stimulus	O
,	O
do	O
NOT	O
involve	O
the	O
{@IRS Tax Pros@}	B-group
who	O
do	O
n't	O
do	O
their	O
job	O
in	O
cold	B-event
&	I-event
flu	I-event
season	I-event
.	O
If	B-person
I	B-person
were	O
a	O
business	B-person
man	I-person
,	O
I	B-person
'd	O
ask	O
that	O
the	O
poorest	O
recieved	O
money	O
first	O
,	O
not	O
the	O
80	B-group
million	I-group
on	O
the	O
IRS	B-corporation
friends	O
&	O
family	B-group
list	O
.	O

Kevin	B-person
De	I-person
Bruyne	I-person
is	O
the	O
best	O
player	O
in	O
the	O
Premier	B-event
League	I-event
.	O
{@NBC Sports Soccer@}	B-product
#	O
MyPLSummer	O
#	O
ManCity	O

The	B-group
Chargers	I-group
lead	O
the	B-group
Lobos	I-group
10-7	O
at	O
halftime	O
!	O
We	O
should	O
have	O
an	O
exciting	O
second	O
half	O
ahead	O
of	O
us	O
!	O
{@NFHS@}	B-group
#	O
AZPreps365	O

Successful	O
second	O
Halloween	B-event
!	O
Went	O
to	O
see	O
Birds	B-creative_work
of	I-creative_work
Prey	I-creative_work
with	O
the	O
amazing	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
.	O
Thank	O
you	O
alyssasbeautyspace	O
for	O
styling	O
my	O
hair	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
Khaleesi	B-person
it	O
can	O
be	O
.	O
I	O
finally	O
found	O
the	O
funkos	B-product
I	O
was	O
looking	O
for	O
.	O
…	O
{{URL}}	O

Classic	O
service	O
from	O
{@Ryanair@}	B-corporation
book	O
the	O
early	O
flight	B-event
to	O
make	O
the	O
most	O
of	O
a	O
weekend	O
in	O
Dublin	B-location
.	O
2	O
hour	O
delay	O
but	O
the	O
next	O
flight	B-event
is	O
boarding	O
an	O
leaving	O
on	O
time	O
ryanair	B-corporation
#	O
gatwick	B-location

Seems	O
like	O
an	O
appropriate	O
time	O
to	O
rewatch	O
Jesus	B-creative_work
Christ	I-creative_work
Superstar	I-creative_work
.	O
Had	O
almost	O
forgotten	O
how	O
awesome	O
(	O
and	O
buff	O
!)	O
{@Tim Minchin@}	B-person
was	O
in	O
this	O
!	O

Kimball	B-group
Volleyball	I-group
headed	O
to	O
the	O
second	O
round	O
of	O
playoffs	O
on	O
Halloween	B-event
Night	I-event
@	O
7:00pm	O
location	O
is	O
still	O
TBD	B-location
depending	O
on	O
tonight	O
’s	O
game	O
between	O
Nevada	B-group
Union	I-group
and	O
Liberty	B-group
Ranch	I-group
..	O
.	O
and	O
the	O
PG	B-corporation
&	I-corporation
E	I-corporation
power	O
outage	O
status	O
.	O
#	O
gojags	O
#	O
issafamily	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
{{USERNAME}}	O

Phil	B-person
is	O
that	O
guy	O
that	O
tries	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
how	O
to	O
play	O
the	O
whole	O
day	O
..	O
.	O
and	O
ruins	O
the	O
fun	O
like	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
#	O
TheMatch2	O

Love	B-creative_work
’s	I-creative_work
A	I-creative_work
Game	I-creative_work
-	O
It	O
’s	O
never	O
left	O
the	O
live	O
set	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
has	O
everything	O
that	O
I	O
love	O
about	O
our	O
band	O
in	O
there	O
.	O
Love	O
you	O
guys	O
{@Michele Stodart@}	B-person
{{USERNAME}}	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
TimsTwitterListeningParty	B-creative_work

DANGER.RUSS	B-person
..	O
.	O
The	O
wind	O
is	O
reeling	O
havoc	O
during	O
the	O
nflprobowl	B-event
skills	I-event
competition	I-event
on	O
espnnfl	B-corporation
!	O
Watch	O
the	O
movement	O
on	O
this	O
ball	O
as	O
{@Russell Wilson@}	B-person
drops	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
bucket	O
!	O
@	O
Pro	B-creative_work
Bowl	I-creative_work
2020	I-creative_work
{{URL}}	O

Love	O
this	O
!!	O
Group	O
of	O
Black	B-group
Women	I-group
Leaders	I-group
Launches	O
a	O
Scholarship	O
For	O
Young	O
Women	O
Like	O
Them	O
{{URL}}	O
Proud	O
of	O
#	O
BWISE	B-group
{{USERNAME}}	O

Morning	O
to	O
everyone	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
family	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
just	O
enjoyed	O
looking	O
at	O
the	O
tweets	O
of	O
what	O
you	O
all	O
did	O
on	O
your	O
first	O
day	O
at	O
home	B-location
.	O
Keep	O
up	O
the	O
good	O
work	O
.	O
Please	O
keep	O
tweeting	O
us	O

Delusional	B-person
{{USERNAME}}	O
thinks	O
Lou	B-person
Lamoriello	I-person
is	O
doing	O
a	O
great	O
job	O
despite	O
the	O
fact	O
that	O
LOSER	O
Lou	B-person
hasnt	O
made	O
a	O
trade	O
since	O
July	O
2018	O
.	O
Very	O
sad	O
when	O
the	O
NHL	B-corporation
establishment	O
tries	O
to	O
push	O
FAKE	O
NEWS	O
on	O
such	O
passionate	O
#	O
isles	O
fans	O
.	O

Happy	B-event
Mommy	I-event
’s	I-event
Day	I-event
to	O
all	O
you	O
Queens	B-person
out	O
there	O
,	O
especially	O
to	O
our	O
Queen	B-person
here	O
whom	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
to	O
now	O
pay	O
back	O
her	O
years	O
of	O
thankless	O
child-rearing	O
as	O
her	O
official	O
photographers	O
(	O
and	O
editors	O
)	O
.	O
Thank	O
you	O
…	O
{{URL}}	O

Uh	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
,	O
Pence	B-person
said	O
he	O
was	O
looking	O
for	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
White	B-location
House	I-location
guest	O
room	O
.	O

Hi	O
{@Namibian Presidency@}	B-person
,	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
thank	O
you	O
for	O
committing	O
to	O
ratify	O
the	O
{@International Labour Organization@}	B-corporation
Convention	O
on	O
Violence	O
and	O
Harassment	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
of	O
Work	O
!	O
This	O
will	O
help	O
women	B-group
get	O
the	O
legal	O
protection	O
at	O
work	O
they	O
deserve	O
.	O
As	O
a	O
{@Global Citizen ⭕@}	B-corporation
I	O
hope	O
to	O
see	O
other	O
world	O
leaders	O
do	O
the	O
same	O
#	O
LeveltheLaw	O

another	O
great	O
essay	O
from	O
Rex	B-person
Murphy	I-person
:	O
Toronto	B-location
’s	I-location
public	I-location
libraries	I-location
hold	O
the	O
line	O
on	O
free	O
speech	O
{{URL}}	O
via	O
{@National Post@}	B-product

"	O
Supreme	B-group
Court	I-group
Punted	O
Like	O
a	O
Football	B-event
Game	I-event
"	O
-	O
President	B-person
Trump	I-person
{{URL}}	O
{{USERNAME}}	O

Finishing	O
an	O
hour	O
of	O
rising	O
English	O
bands	O
with	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
and	O
now	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
'	O
Raise	B-creative_work
Your	I-creative_work
Glass'	I-creative_work
-	O
Scottish	B-creative_work
bands	I-creative_work
hour	I-creative_work
follows	O
at	O
1pm	O
Up	O
next	O
its	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
hr	O
-	O
a	O
phone	O
interview	O
with	O
Barry	B-person
from	O
deepest	O
isolation	O
in	O
far	O
flung	O
Sussex	B-location
{{URL}}	O

Check	O
out	O
Olathe	B-event
North	I-event
vs	I-event
Lawrence	I-event
Free	I-event
State	I-event
Game	I-event
Highlights	O
-	O
Sept	O
.	O
10	O
,	O
2019	O
by	O
Olathe	B-creative_work
North	I-creative_work
High	I-creative_work
School	I-creative_work
-	O
Varsity	B-creative_work
Volleyball	I-creative_work
on	O
{@Hudl@}	B-corporation
{{URL}}	O
#	O
hudl	O

While	O
we	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
Marvel	B-creative_work
can	O
manage	O
to	O
make	O
an	O
actual	O
good	O
Howard	B-creative_work
the	I-creative_work
Duck	I-creative_work
reboot	O
.	O
{@Disney@}	B-corporation
{@Marvel Entertainment@}	B-corporation

Game	O
Day	O
..	O
.	O
vs	O
#	O
OxleathersFC	B-group
{{USERNAME}}	O
Div	O
3	O
⏰|	O
1030	O
Sponsored	O
by	O
The	O
Roebuck	O
at	O
Draycott	B-location
in	O
the	O
Clay	B-location
The	I-location
Lowers	I-location
,	O
Abbots	B-corporation
Bromley	I-corporation
School	I-corporation
#	O
CmonTheStags	O

Matt	B-person
Araiza	I-person
's	I-person
25-yd	O
field	O
goal	O
gives	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
a	O
17-0	O
lead	O
over	O
UNLV	B-group
with	O
3:01	O
remaining	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
half	O
.	O
Araiza	B-person
is	O
now	O
13-for-15	O
on	O
field	O
goals	O
this	O
season	O
.	O
Big	O
play	O
on	O
the	O
scoring	O
drive	O
was	O
a	O
26-yard	O
sideline	O
catch	O
by	O
WR	B-group
Kobe	B-person
Smith	I-person
.	O

STAR	O
WARS	O
by	O
PRIMARK	B-corporation
Kids	O
Boys	O
Brown	O
Fur	O
Fabric	O
'	O
Chewbacca	B-creative_work
'	O
Top	O
Age	O
7-8	O
Years	O
{{URL}}	O
via	O
{@eBay.co.uk@}	B-product
BID	O
NOW	O
,	O
ENDING	O
SOON	O
!!	O
!	O

Bruce	B-person
Reidel	I-person
on	O
his	O
meetings	O
with	O
Sultan	B-group
Qaboos	I-group
over	O
the	O
years	O
:	O
Remembering	O
Oman	B-group
’s	O
Sultan	B-group
Qaboos	I-group
,	O
a	O
critical	O
interlocutor	O
for	O
the	O
US	B-location
in	O
the	O
Middle	B-location
East	I-location
{{URL}}	O
via	O
{@The Brookings Institution@}	B-product

“	O
All	O
Legends	O
fall	O
in	O
the	O
makin’	O
”~	O
rest	O
easy	O
{@JuiceWorlddd@}	B-person

⁦	O
{@Barack Obama@}	B-person
How	O
dare	O
you	O
criticize	O
⁦	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
when	O
more	O
⁩	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
United	B-location
States	I-location
died	O
of	O
H1N1	O
and	O
Ebola	O
under	O
your	O
watch	O
.	O
Less	O
people	O
are	O
dying	O
from	O
Coronavirus	O
under	O
President	B-person
Trump	I-person
’s	O
watch	O
.	O
You	O
’re	O
such	O
a	O
hypocrite	O
.	O
{{URL}}	O

CORONAVIRUS	O
SPAIN	B-location
:	O
THE	O
GOVERNMENT	B-group
INTRODUCES	O
FINES	O
OF	O
UP	O
TO	O
30,000	O
EUROS	O
FOR	O
BREACHING	O
THE	O
CURFEW	O
-	O
Euro	B-corporation
Weekly	I-corporation
News	I-corporation
Spain	B-location
Spain	I-location
newsarticle	O
{{URL}}	O
via	O
{{USERNAME}}	O

Check	O
out	O
this	O
new	O
music	O
video	O
from	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
with	O
awesome	O
LEGO	B-corporation
animation	B-product
by	O
{{USERNAME}}	O
!!	O
Ray	B-person
and	O
Dynasty	B-person
are	O
amazing	O
people	O
,	O
like	O
and	O
share	O
this	O
new	O
video	O
!	O
{{URL}}	O

Daughter	B-person
loving	O
goth	O
girl	O
this	O
morning	O
{{USERNAME}}	O

dems	O
have	O
n't	O
gotten	O
the	O
white	O
vote	O
in	O
a	O
half-century	O
.	O
AOC	O
dings	O
Democratic	B-event
National	I-event
Convention	I-event
targeted	O
to	O
'	O
white	O
moderates'	O
{{URL}}	O
via	O
{@New York Post@}	B-product
